Translated By The Community Of WWW.MY-SUBS.COM
Hey Quagmire.
Peter, I want you
and the guys to come
over to my house right now.
We're drinking. What for?
Just come over.
I want you to see something.
Alright.
C'mon guys, we're going to Quagmire's.
Alright, hang on. I gotta
go to the bathroom first.
OK, let's go.
Oh, finally!
C'mon, c'mon. C'mon inside.
Well, what is it?
What's the big damn deal?
Look.
It's a cat.
Yeah, I just got him today.
His name's James.
Isn't he just the cutest
thing you've ever seen?
Hi, James.
Oh my God!
Watch when I scratch his
bottom. He sticks his fanny in the air.
Oh, oh. We have
lift off. We have lift off.
Oh, come here, James.
What the hell we doin'.
Quagmire, since when do you like cats?
Since I found this little
guy living under my house.
I'll tell you this ...
I understand now why the
pharoahs worshipped these animals.
Oh look, Joe. He's making friends.
Oh, sorry.
Y'know ... y'know what?
It's alright, Quagmire
That leg is mostly pus.
Oh, OK.
Here it comes, James.
Here comes the part
I was telling you about.
Aaaaah! You're one of those.
I hate Quagmire lately.
Me too.
That cat has totally
changed his personality.
Yeah, like when I went
over to his house the other day.
Who is it?
It's me, Quagmire. I need
to borrow your lawnmower.
Oh, Quagmire's not
here It's just me, James.
I'm supposed to watch the house.
C'mon, Quagmire. It's 97Â° out here.
We're 2 grown men.
Are you selling yarn? 'Cos I love yarn.
No, I need to borrow your lawnmower.
Oh, I don't think
Quagmire wants me to do that.
Oh, come on!
I don't think Quagmire appreciated
the condition you returned it in last time.
Glenn, can I just ...
No, you can't have it.
Hey guys, it's James' birthday tomorrow.
Would you all sign his card?
You want us to sign a card for your cat?
Yeah. Don't just put your
name, write something clever.
God, I hate having to come
up with something on the spot.
Ummm.
Have a 'mice' day.
Best fishes.
Peter.
Thanks ...... that's great.
Well, I gotta get going.
I'm heading off to Vermont
to get James' birthday present.
There's this neat little store called "Cattitudes"
that makes all this neat cat stuff.
See you guys later.
What a queer.
He's goin' all the way to
Vermont for cat gifts and what-not?
You can get a scratcing post down at Wal Mart for $2.00
A pair of Lee jeans for $9.00
Y'know they got seats for children
now? You put 'em right in your car.
Supposed to make 'em safer.
Only problem is, you can't lean
your seat all the way back ... oh.
We gotta do somethin' about this.
His whole life is about that stupid cat.
Hey, y'know the cat's
alone at Quagmire's right now.
Y'know what we should do?
We should go over there and shave it.
That's a great idea!
Let's do it!
Let's shave the cat!
Oh boy, I usually only get this excited
when they say the title
of the movie in the movie.
I'm telling you
these drug dealers represent
a Clear and Present
Danger to the United States.
Eh? Eh? He said it. He said it.
All I'm sayin' is what
if this As Good As It Gets?
Eh? Eh? There it is! There it is!
The only way for me to solve
this crisis is to be Superman IV.
The Quest for Peace.
So that's why they call it that.
Alright, the cat's gotta be in here.
Hey, lets take a man-
sized poop in his cat box
so he thinks there's
something really wrong with him.
There it is!
Rock and roll!
Yeah! Shaving time!
Alright, hand me the razor.
Oh, my God!
Peter, you killed it!
Will you guys relax.
He's got 8 more lives.
OK, 7 more lives.
6.
5.
4.
3.
Peter, stop doin' what you're doin.
What'll we do?
Altight, alright. I have an idea.
How 'bout we hide the cat's
body and leave that window open
and that way, it'll
seem like the cat ran away.
We'll never get away with that.
Oh, we just might.
You see, I've got a lucky cat's foot.
Y'know, Peter, it's
sorta adding insult to injury
raiding Quagmire's fridge
for beer after you killed his cat.
Or is it?
Is my response.
Ah, crap!
God, I hate cops.
Almost as much as I hated
my overly sensitive car alarm.
Son of a bitch!
Whatta we got, partner?
Empty alcohol containers.
The driver's inebriated
and covered in blood.
He's got scratches
on his face and arms.
There's a blood soaked
corpse in the back seat.
He's got shovels in there,
and a hand drawn map titled
"This is where we'll hide the body."
Well, that all seems fine.
Sorry to bother you. sir.
Pot! Small amount of pot!
You're under arrest, dirtbag!
Oh, come on!
I don't appreciate
drug addicts in my town!
I'm a family guy.
Eh? Eh? He said it.
Alright, Brian, your
family's here to bail you out.
Brian, if you don't mind,
we'll start thinkin' up our
prison rape jokes immediately.
I'll break the ice.
Hey, Brian, did you do
'Hard Time' or 'Hardly Working?'
Penis.
Alright, well all the pieces are there.
Somebody make somethin' outta that.
Hey, Brian, who's your
favorite baseball player?
Albert Pujols?
Chris, stop it! Come on.
Brian, we're happy you're out of jail.
And when we get to the car
would you like a donut to sit on?
Ha ha ha. Y'see, I'm part of it.
I'm part of it like everyone else.
I can't believe they threw me
in jail for a quarter ounce of pot.
Well, Brian, it's your own fault.
I mean, pot is illegal for a reason.
Lois, don't be a hypocrite.
You've smoked pot.
Well sure, Brian,
but I'm thinkin' about the children.
Pot's illegal mainly to protect them.
No, no. Pot is illegal
because William Randolph Hearst
ran a smear campaign
against marijuana in the 1930's
to protect his interests
in the timber industry
because hemp was
poised to replace wood
as an inexpensive raw material
for the manufacture of paper.
There's your smear
campaign right there, Brian.
Ah-ha-ha.
Mom's right.
Drugs are bad, Brian.
I mean, haven't you
seen those commercials?
Open up, Brian, it's Joe.
Crap!
Uh, uh, j-just a sec.
Brian, under your probation
you're required to
submit to random drug tests.
I need some urine.
You mean .... right now?
Yes. Right now.
Here's some
magazines to get you going.
Uh, how's that gonna ... ?
Oh, sorry. It's been a while.
Look, I don't really feel
comfortable doing this in front of you.
Fine, I'll wait outside.
Here's a bottle of lotion.
Aah, Joe ...
Right. Sorry.
Stewie, I need your urine.
Huh ... Really?
Yeah. Joe's doing a drug test
and if I give him some of mine
he's gonna know
I've been smoking pot
so I need some
of your urine so I can ...
Uh ... you don't have
to be naked for this.
But I don't have to NOT
be naked for it, either. Ah-ha ...
Come on, Stewie,
hurry up and pee.
Joe's waiting for me.
Brian, you know I
can't go unless you stare at it.
Brian, what the hell ... ?
Uhh ... hey, Lois
The jig's up, Brian.
Run!
Brian, is this how you're
trying to pass your drug test?
By stealing a baby's urine?
My God, that is just sick!
No, what's sick is
making marijuana illegal
when it's been proven that it
does less damage to you than alcohol.
No, what's sick is the
plot of the movie "Baby Mama."
What happens when
a 40 year old woman
asks her 41 year old
friend to carry her baby?
Push, Angie, push harder ...
Oh, it's dead.
Brian, when you
have to go to these lengths
just to get away with smoking pot
it's time to make a change.
You're right, Lois.
It is time to make a change.
Thank you.
It's time for Quahog
to legalize marijuana!
But that's not exactly what I meant.
Hey, check out
the size of Stewie's penis.
Oh, come on guys,
it's just the way God made me.
No more oppression!
We, as American adults with free will
have the right to
use marijuana if we choose to!
Enough government profiteering
under the guise of morality!
Enough with this phony war on drugs!
You know, you're going
about this all wrong, Brian.
If you want to win people over,
you can't just drone on like Ben Stein.
You've got to have a
little more showmanship.
Here, watch.
♪ Now everybody
gather round ♪
♪ and listen if you would ♪
♪ When I tell you every person
needs a way of feeling good ♪
♪ Every kitty needs a ball of
string and every dog a stick ♪
♪ but all you need is a bag
of weed to really get a kick ♪
♪ 1 - 2 - 3 - 4 ♪
♪ 5 - 6 - 7 - 8 ♪
♪ A bag of weed,
a bag of weed ♪
♪ oh, everything is
better with a bag of weed ♪
♪ it's the only help
that you'll ever need ♪
♪ because everything is
better with a bag of weed ♪
There you go ...
... you're all gettin' it now.
They go all sort of queer.
They rent "The Rocketeer."
He humps a guy like me
Right!
♪ but all we need
is a bag of weed ♪
♪ to keep us worry free ♪
♪ 1 - 2 - 3 ♪
♪ Oh, a bag of weed,
a bag of weed ♪
♪ oh, everything is
better with a bag of weed ♪
♪ oh, you you don't need meth
and you don't need speed ♪
♪ because everything is
better with a bag of weed ♪
Have a go, Brian.
♪ As Mr H.L. Mencken said: ♪
♪ "The common man's a fool" ♪
♪ and just like
Helen Keller said: ♪
♪ "Doof doogie beebo bool" ♪
♪ but try and use your heads ♪
♪ and don't buy into all the fear ♪
♪ because all we need is a bag
of weed to make us wanna cheer ♪
♪ and 1 - 2 ♪
♪ a bag of weed, a bag of weed ♪
♪ oh, everything is better
with a bag of weed ♪
♪ you can try and
fight 'cos we're all agreed ♪
♪ because everything is
better with a bag of weed ♪
♪ 1 - 2 -3 -4 ♪
♪ 5 - 6 - 7- 8 ♪
♪  and a 1 - 2 -3 -4 ♪
♪ and a 5, and a 6 ♪
♪ and a 7, oh! ♪
♪ a bag of weed, a bag of weed ♪
♪ oh, everything is
better with a bag of weed ♪
♪ You're a happy guy
when you plant the seed ♪
♪ because everything is better ♪
♪ with a bag of weed ♪
♪ Oh, everything is
better with a bag of weed ♪
As mayor of Quahog
I hereby sign into law,
the legalization of marijuana.
Good evening everyone.
Our top story:
"Marijuana is now legal"
Le..le... is now legal.
Legal in Quahog
And it's made everything ...
... just so great.
OK, you ... you can
read the next one.
No, you can.
No, you.
OK, OK, OK.
L..let..let's read it both together.
- Ready?
- OK ... OK
How's the weather look, Ollie?
Not too bad.
Right on!
See Lois?
Tell me things in
Quahog aren't better now.
It's just weird, Brian.
I still don't think I'm
comfortable with the whole idea.
Look Lois, ever since
marijuana was legalized ...
... crime has gone down,
productivity is up,
and ratings forl Dr. Who
are through the roof.
Yeah, but Peter's so vague lately
he can hardly set up a cut away.
Man, this is even better than ...
Uh, no, wait ...
No, this is worse than ...
Thi ... Ah, better ...
I dunno.
Here's a list of
celebrities I don't like:
Hello, Griffin
Mr Pewterschmidt?
- Hey, how ya been?
- Not good.
Oh, I'm sorry to hear that.
Wow, a limo, huh?
Hey, are these
Diet Rites just to take?
No!
Those are my Diet Rites!
Now listen, Griffin.
Thanks to your dog's
stupid marijuana crusade,
people are using hemp for everything.
Fabric, fuel ... and paper.
Which means I'm
losing billions in timber dollars.
I had to sell my Bangles records.
I was still working on
memorizing all the words.
My back is hurting
from the chair I'm sitting on.
Where's the Tylenol?
If I lay down flat on the floor
It usually kinda fixes it.
Tony Danza
from Who's the Boss says
Eh-oh ... Eh-oh ...
Oh-eh .. oh-eh-ohhhhh ...
I'm losing money,
and it's your dog's fault.
Now, I have to get
hemp illegalized again.
And the only way to do that
is to start a fear campaign
designed to turn people against pot.
Will you help me?
Gosh, Mr. Pewterschmidt
I .. I could never go
against Brian like that.
I'll give you this
light up butterfly yo-yo.
- Ohhh, to keep?
- Not to keep!
You can use it today, and
one more day in the summer.
- Yeah!
- Pull over.
Bye.
Alright, Carter
I've finished cutting
together our anti-pot video.
Take a look.
Hey, I got a great idea.
Let's kill 6 million Jews.
Hooray! Yeah!
Yeah, I'm on board.
How did you come up with that?
I got the idea ...
from ... from ... while ...
... from while I was smoking pot.
Anyone else who likes
pot, reach for my joint.
Oh, there it is.
Give us some of that.
Ha  ha  ha, perhaps later.
Now let's go to France and steal
all their objects ... de... arte ...
Yay! Alright! Let's go to France!
- Not bad, uh?
- Ah, damn it.
That was FOX News.
Apparently they own
the rights to Hitler's likeness
and they won't
have him slandered.
Hi, I'm Peter.
You know me from the movie
"Harold, Kumar and
Peter go to White Castle"
As you can see, I'm
enjoying a White Castle burger.
Why?
Because I don't do drugs.
It took me 5 minutes
to get to White Castle.
I didn't get diverted
by all those crazy hijinks.
'Cos I don't get high.
It was a good movie, though.
Y'know, Neil Patrick Harris
got the job on "How I Met Your
Mother" 'cos of that movie?
Y'know, I've only
seen that show once
but I gotta tell ya,
what's really weird to me
is why is the voice of the
guy from the future, Bob Saget?
I mean, the guy on the show
... he's already an adult.
Y'know, so it's not like he's
gonna grow in to Bob Saget.
Doesn't make sense.
Thank you for your time.
Well, what do you think?
Look, daddy, I agree with
what you're trying to do,
but I just don't
think this is gonna work.
It's so artificial.
You're asking for
a spanking, young lady.
Yeah!
All right!
Peter, the reason
Brian succeeded in his cause
is that he spoke with such passion.
No offence,
but you two just
don't have that talent.
Are you kiddin'?
I can be very persuasive.
That's how I used
to lure wayward sailors
to their deaths with my Siren song.
Hello, Brian.
You're looking good.
Nice shiny coat.
Don't try to butter me up, Carter.
Why did you call me here?
Come inside.
There's something
I want to show you.
What's this?
It's your novel, Brian,
"Faster than the speed of Love"
Ready to ship out tomorrow.
All you have to do is
publicly come out against pot.
Forget it, Carter
I'm not gonna take your bribe.
I don't care if
you printed a million copies.
I printed TWO million.
And I even commissioned an oil
painting for your author's photo.
And what's this?
Is this an Oprah Book Club sticker?
I think it is.
Wait! Really?
Oh, my God.
Plus I can get you a
night in bed with Oprah.
- Eeerrrr ......?
- OK, just the sticker then.
So whatta you say?
Is it a deal?
You don't have to
sell out like this, Brian
Your novel .. is good enough .. to
be published .. on it's own .. merits
You think so?
Yeah, you bet.
This is your shot, Brian
You can be a superstar author.
All you gotta do is make an
impassioned anti-pot speech in public.
Forget it, Carter
Even Stewie says the
book is good enough on its own.
Right, Stewie?
... Ermmm ... maybe do
a song about why pot is bad.
♪ And that's why pot is bad ♪
I've heard all I need
to make an informed decision.
Marijuana is hereby re-illegalized.
In other news,
a local Quahog author
has set a record for the
worst selling novel of all time.
Brian Griffin's "Faster
than the speed of Love"
has astonishingly
not sold a single copy
thanks to universal
panning by literary critics.
Coming up, children
are getting sexier ...
and that's ...
... that's pretty cool.
This is so humiliating.
I sold out everything I believed in,
and I have nothing to show for it.
My book's a bomb!
Well, look at it this way ....
you did accomplish something.
Marijuana's illegal because of you,
and Stewie got
to build a nice little fort
with all of your unsold books.
My house is made of mediocrity.
Hey, guys.
I want you to know I'm
raising my reward to 50 dollars
for anyone who can
help me find James.
No questions asked.
I killed your cat.
www.tvsubtitles.net