Translated By The Community Of WWW.MY-SUBS.COM
Hey, everybody.
Look what came in the mail.
We got invitations
to Jillian's wedding.
Jillian's wedding?
She's getting married?
Wow, that's great.
Looks like she finally found
someone after dating that last loser.
She dated someone after me?
No. See how I set up my own
joke? You walked right into it, Brian.
Walk right in. Sit right down.
Stewie's gonna make you the fool.
Peter, here's your invite.
Chris, Meg, Stewie, and me.
Uhhhh ......
probably one more in there.
No, doesn't look like it.
Oh, yeah, here it is.
Brian. Oh, no, wait.
It's for B. Ryan.
Ah, cool, Mrs G. Thanks
for lettin' me stay here
the last couple of weeks.
I've enjoyed his company.
She invited everybody except me?
What the hell?
We dated for 6 months.
Ouch! Well, Brian, looks
like you're the odd man out.
Like a non-praying mantis.
Bless us, oh Lord, for these
gifts we are about to receive.
Help us to be mindful
of all our blessings ...
and ...
Brian, I'm filling
out my RSVP card ...
and I don't know
whether I should get the
salmon or the snausages.
They're having snausages?
Yeah, sounds like fun.
Big deal! I couldn't care less
about going to that wedding.
Look on the bright
side. It frees you up to
go to Cleveland's barbeque.
Cleveland's having a barbeque?
Oh, boy, this is really awkward ...
None of this is awkward.
I've moved on from Jillian.
I've dated plenty
of other girls since her.
- I never do computer dating.
- Yeah, me neither.
So .... you're 27?
Well, that picture,
y'know, it was posted
a couple of years ago.
So ... so you're ...
you're a Golden Retriever?
Well, it's a Retriever mix ...
... b ... bra ... doodle.
Wh ... where is that waitress?
Fine! If you're so over her,
we should all go out to dinner.
You, me, Jillian and her fiance.
Unless you're uncomfortable.
I would have no problem with
that. I'd love to meet the fiance.
Great! And I'm sure
Dushawn would love to meet you.
- Dushawn?
- Ahh ... his name's Derek.
But look at your face.
We now return to ... "The Hills"
Justin Bobby was
supposed to be here, already.
Are you still going out with him?
I guess so.
I hate how he pushes
his bangs out of his face
with every word he says.
Ummm ...  order me a beer.
I have to find a
spot for my motorcycle.
- Hi, guys.
- Hi, Jillian.
Oh, hey, Jillian. Congratulations
on your upcoming nuptuals.
Oh! Are they showing?
It's a really thin bra.
Peter, I came over
to ask you something.
Will you give me
away at my wedding?
Wow, sure. That'd be great!
Jillian, don't you want your
own father to give you away?
Lois, don't ruin this for me.
Don't ruin this like
you ruined Kicks cereal.
Mmmm. This Kicks
cereal is good tasting.
And it's good for you.
Naaaah!!!
My father can't give
me away 'cause he's dead..
Ha ha ...
Well then, Peter would
be happy to do the honours.
Plus, when's the next time you're
gonna get to give a bride away?
I know. This is a once
in a lifetime opportunity.
You can give me away
when I get married, dad.
N-a-a-a-a-h!
Merci, mademoiselle.
And for the gentleman ... ?
Yeah, can I have, ah,
this 3rd thing down, please?
Ah, very good,sir.
And for you?
ORDERS IN FRENCH
Ah ha ha ha. Bon.
Excellent. Merci, monsieur.
Wow, Derek, that's pretty
good French you speak there.
He also speaks 'Orange'.
- Mandarin, honey.
- Mandolin.
O-o-o-h ... o-o-o-h!
Hey, hey. What luck, huh?
Wow, sweetie! That was amazing.
Ha, I don't think I could do
that again in a million years.
- Ahhhhhhh ... oh ... oh ... oh ...
- Aah ... ah ... ah ... ah
I caught ... this piece.
Oh, my God! Sir, are you alright?
Ahhh ... I don't know.
I actually just had elbow surgery.
I wasn't even supposed
to come in to work today ...
Why would you
trip me deliberately?!
I ...I'm ... I'm sorry.
Dinner's goin' great.
You know, I can probably
help you with that elbow.
- Does that feel better?
- Yeah, it feels a lot better.
Wow, you're the best man ever.
Oh ho ho, hardly.
Excuse me, I'm just gonna
use the restroom really quick.
- I'll go with you.
- Oh, my God. Gay!
Shutup! He's obviously some
sort of Superman. I just ...
... I just need to know
if he has any shortcomings
that'll make me feel better.
You are not even ...
You're goin' in there to look ...
That's even gayer.
Oh, come on!
Can I have anoth ...
another bourbon, please?
Hey, blondie. You wanna get
together with my "Dogwood?"
What?
Dogwood, y'know, like
... like Dogwood and Blondie.
Like in the funnies.
You mean Dagwood?
Dagwood. That's what it is.
Hey, how about this one ...
You wanna take a Wizard on my Id?
Ah, ha ha ha.
You remind me of my step dad.
Oh ... oh, man.
What the hell did I do last night?
Good morning.
Oh, my God! You're Lauren Conrad!
- Yeah.
- From "The Hills".
Yeah, you seem surprised.
No, no .. it's just .. I ..
I mean .. I probably had
a lot to drink last night so
if I did anything that might have
offended you, I'm .. I'm sorry.
No, it's OK, I have a dog
so I've had to cut
poop out of his fur before.
Oh ... oh, thanks.
Well, otherwise it was
a fun night though, right?
So fun.
Y'know, I had a
really fun night, Brian.
You seem like a really cool guy.
Yeah, um ... Hey,
y'know, if you don't mind ...
I'm sorta a low
profile kinda person, so ...
I'm gonna take off before
anybody gets the wrong idea here.
Hey ... Brian, is that you?
Is that Lauren Con ...?
I was shoppin' for hats ...
Hang on! I'm coming over!
Oh, no.
Don't go anywhere. Stay right there.
Who's that?
Oh, it's just this jerk
that goes to my school.
You go to school?
No, I just lied to you
and I'm not really sure why.
Is this the longest
light ever, or what?
Ah, there we go!
Oh, my God! How do
you two know each other?
Ah, we actually just met.
Well, I'm Stewie.
I'm Lauren, it's good to meet you.
I love the show. Do you
need a gay friend on the
show .. a friend on the show?
Hey, you know what? I'm
actually on my way to go shoot now
if you want, you guys can tag along.
Oh, ah, I don't know if we have time.
Yes, we would love to.
Brian, don't wreck this for me.
Oh, my God! I have
the perfect hat for this.
Listen, Lauren, I'm not .. not
super comfortable being on camera.
Oh, relax. After a little while
you'll forget they're even there.
What's everybody looking at?
The salesman told me it was unisex.
Hey, those people look familiar.
Ah, that's Heidi and Spencer.
I don't really talk to them.
Wow, Spencer does
look like a monkey.
Spencer, I am so
over your selfishness.
Whatta ya want? I came out to
Hollywood, I'm on camera all day
and I turned my
back on my own kind.
Uuugh... there's Brody
Jenner. God, what a douchebag.
I can't believe that came
out of Bruce Jenner's vagina.
Bruce Jenner is a man.
No, Brian. That's what
the Press would have
you believe. But he's not.
Bruce Jenner is a woman. An
elegant, beautiful, Dutch woman.
This is where they
edit the show together.
Lauren, we've got a rough
cut of next week's episode.
- Can you queue that up, Terry?
- Sure.
I need to be, like, fine,
to be alone, and, like, not
even want to date someone
and then I know I'll be
fine to get into a relationship.
That's it? That was like, 5 seconds.
It's OK. They fill the
rest with shots of street
signs, and fronts of restaurants
and old footage from the A Team.
Hey, Brian, where
were you last night, buddy?
Oh, I was .. um .. I was out. I
got a little wrecked after dinner
and I didn't wanna drive home.
Oh, yeah? Did you stay in town
or did you head for 'The Hills?'
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Wait a minute! How the hell do
you guys know about that already?
It's all over the internet. Look!
Does Lauren Conrad
have a new beau?
An anonymous
source has the answers ..
Oh, yeah, I know that
guy. His name's Brian Griffin
and he definitely
boned Lauren last night.
Great ... great...
That ... that's fantastic.
Well, I think it's wonderful that
you're datin' such a classy, well
educated girl like Lauren Conra ...
ha ha. She's such an idiot, Brian.
She's such an idiot!
Yeah, you know
something, Brian. I bet you
make the late night monologues.
I mean, it's a little weird isn't it,
this new Lauren Conrad relationship?
When asked about their sex
life, Brian was quoted as saying
"Oh, yeah, we just do it "me" style."
Have you seen the news about
Lauren Conrad and Brian Griffin?
Y'know, a lot of these
young Hollywood girls carry
their little dogs around in their purse.
But Lauren carries one in her pants.
Yeah, so Lauren Conrad and
Brian Griffin are now a couple.
Apparently she gave
that dog a bone and
... he gave it right back!
Look, I was drunk
outta my mind, I didn't
know what I was doing.
It was a one night
thing. I have no interest in
dating one of those shallow
idiot celebrities who's
only famous for being famous.
I'm going over to let her down easy.
Hey, tell her I like her
work in "Jake and the Fatman".
Oh no, wait.
That was William Conrad.
Tell her I like "Jake and the Fatman".
Can I help you?
Yeah, I'm Brian. I'm, ah,
the guy all the comedians
have been talking about.
Oh, si! Ha ha ha ha ha.
Lauren is in the back.
Just follow the
music and you will find her.
Thanks.
- Oh, hi Brian.
- Wow! Hi.
- That's beautiful. What was that?
- It's Mozart's violin
concerto number 1 in B flat.
Plato's symposium ... this yours?
- Oh, yeah.
- It's pretty worn out.
Yeah, I've read it,
like, a hundred times.
I find Aristófanes'
quasi satirical origin myth
regarding the three genders
both fantastic and serious.
Yeah, that .. er .. that
always cracked me up.
So, you read a lot, huh?
Yeah, but I try not
to let it interfere with
my biomolecular research.
Biomolecular?
I ... I don't understand.
Come on. I'll show
you what I did yesterday.
It'll make you feel ... young,
as when the world was new.
- You did all this in a day?
- The matrix formed in a day.
The life forms grew later at
a substantially accelerated rate.
Can I cook? Or can't I?
This doesn't make any sense. If
you're so smart why do you hide it?
Come on, Brian. You know
America doesn't like smart people.
They elected Bush twice.
Yeah, once, but .. so this whole
persona is just a publicity stunt?
Publicity is what keeps
this franchise running, Brian.
We're even using state of the
art computer animation to create
a fake sex tape
with me and Bill Cosby.
Now, you will get ready for the
zim zam and the babbidy bibbedy.
and you will take off your
clothes, like vooo and voooom
and get ready for
the most splendiferous
pudding pop you have ever seen.
Alright, Jillian, since I'm giving
you away on your wedding day
I wanna make sure it
all goes off without a hitch.
Now, what are your
thoughts on a wedding singer?
Oh, I thought that maybe I
would just DJ the wedding myself.
I already made a playlist on this.
- A box of Junior Mints?
- This isn't an iPod?
- Do Junior Mints play MP3s?
- My iPod is chocolate?
Well, be that as it may,
or not be that, I was thinkin'
I could be your wedding singer.
That's a great idea, Peter!
Sweet! And I promise you'll be
able to understand all the words.
Not like Sting where you
can only understand the last 3.
... brand new day ..
So, did you break up with  Lauren?
No, I didn't. As a matter of fact,
she's coming over for dinner tonight.
Say what?!
Well, Lauren, it's a real
pleasure havin' you here for dinner.
Of course, I'm sure this isn't
as exciting as your usual cuisine.
Y'know, all that caviar
with the little silver spoons
Actually, Mrs Griffin, caviar
spoons are carved from bone.
They don't use metal because
it reacts chemically with the
fish eggs and changes their taste.
Oh, well that's fascinating.
You could have just
complimented the free food,
but one upping
me is another way to go.
- So, y'know, guys ...
- Bitch.
Lauren just finished
a fascinating doctoral thesis
on sub-orbital
propulsion mechanisms
that NASA is using for the
next generation of space shuttles.
Oooohhhhhh ... Aaaaahhhh!
So, Lauren, um, whenever
I'm watchin' your show ...
... you give me wood.
Where do we go from here?
Well, I could sign a picture for you.
Uh, yeah, sure,
that'd be fine. Thank you.
So, Lauren, do you and
Paris Hilton and Lindsay Lohan
all hang out and
go drunk driving together?
I heard that Lindsay
Lohan wasn't driving that night.
She was taking the rap for a friend.
Road hog!
Oh, no! I already have 2 strikes.
- I'll take the wheel, Mr Magoo.
- I'm too old to go to prison.
They'll rape me! And I'll
never see 'em coming, no I won't.
Well, uh, Lauren and I had a
great time today at the Art museum.
There was a special exhibition
of rare Monet paintings ...
- Manet, honey.
- What?
It was actually the
Manet exhibit, not Monet ...
But no big deal. People
make that mistake all the time.
Oh, right.
Y'know, I don't mean
to be rude, but do you
have a more comfortable chair?
This one's really hurting my back.
Oh, my God! Quagmire, you
come out from under there!
I'm sorry everybody. I just
wanted to meet her so bad.
I can't do anything right.
I'll go have a talk with him.
Hey, buddy, where are all your pals?
- Playin' baseball.
- Well, why aren't you
playin' with 'em?
- 'Cause I don't have a glove.
- Oh, yeah?
- Gee! Just for me? No fooling?
- Nah, just kidding. It's mine.
- Oh.
- Yeah.
Oh, sweetie, dinner with your
family was so much fun tonight.
Yeah, I think they really liked you.
It was so cute when
you thought Manet was Monet.
Yeah .. yeah .. that .. that was a hoot.
Oh, hey, how are you
liking my unabridged history
of 2nd World War naval
tactics in the Pacific theatre?
Oh, it's really, um .. interesting ..
I'm at the part where
they detail the account
of Admiral Halsey's
victory at Midway.
You mean Admiral
Spruance, sweetie.
Huh?
Well, Halsey was
hospitalized with cirrhosis
at the outset of the battle
so Spruance, who
prior to June of 1941,
was primarily a desk Admiral
was charged with leading the
naval fleet at Midway against Japan.
A victory which
surprised even his peers.
And in fact, was a
turning point for the American
naval forces in the Pacific.
No, yeah. That's ..
that's the part I'm at.
Oh, my God, you're so cute
when you don't know
what you're talking about.
Well, wait a minute. What
the hell does that mean?
Are you saying I'm not smart?
You don't have to be. You're
adorable. Like those calendars
that have monkeys in clothes.
Look, why don't we talk
about this in the morning?
I wanna finish that book.
- Sweetie, since when
do you wear reading glasses?
- What? These?
- I've had these forever.
- Honey, those aren't real.
- Sure they are.
- No .. they're not.
I can see the little
Austin Powers logo on the side.
What are you talkin'
about?  These are my glasses.
Yeah, baby, yeah!
- Alright, I can't do this.
- Can't do what?
I can't date someone
who's smarter than I am.
I feel like Jillian.
O-o-o-o-o-h-h-h-h ..
- What? What, what,
what? What is that?
I think I get it.
This isn't about me
being smarter than you.
This is about you still
being in love with Jillian.
- How do you know that?
- Because I'm smarter than you, Brian.
Oh, my God ...
You're right!
Y'know, I thought I was
over her, but .. I'm .. I'm not.
Somewhere along the line she
must have gotten under my skin.
I'm in love with her. How
could I have been so miopic?
- "Myopic".
- Thank you, Lauren!
My God, Lauren. What am I gonna
do? I'm still in love with Jillian.
Well, there's only one
thing you can do, Brian.
Tell her how you feel.
What's the use? It's
over. She's moved on.
Well, who knows? Women
are complex creatures, Brian.
Maybe she just needs to be
reminded how much she misses you.
And I know exactly
how to do that, Brian.
She needs to see you on
the arm of a beautiful woman.
- What is this gonna do?
- It's gonna make her jealous.
You, out on the
town with a hot date.
How are you a hot date?
Whoa! You're angry at her, not me.
No wonder you're alone.
This isn't working at all. She
doesn't even know we're here.
Oh, she will, Brian. And she's gonna
be upset that your date is so into you.
Ok, ready? I've
been reading up on things that
sound sexy.
"Oh, Brian, I can't wait
til after dinner
'cause then we'll go home and you
can watch me have my period".
What the hell's wrong
with you? That's not sexy!
Hey, Brian. I just
noticed you over here.
- Hi, I'm Jillian.
- Desiree. Charmed!
Well, I wish we could
stay. But we have quite
an exciting evening planned.
Oh, oh, yeah, right.
We're really hittin' the town.
Yes, we're gonna
douche the night away.
Uh, well, have fun. You
two are a really cute couple.
Hey, Desiree.
Oh ... hey, Lee...
Brian,this is Lee.
Lee, this is Brian.
I know Lee from ...
- ... Starbucks.
- Hey, is that Desiree?
That's it. I mean, I
don't know what else I can
do. The wedding's tomorrow
and she hasn't shown
any signs of leaving Derek.
- I've completely run out of options.
- Not quite, Brian.
- There's still one thing you can do.
- What's that?
Go for broke. Just throw all
your cards on the table at once.
Show her that you love her in
a way she can't possibly ignore.
Hello?
Oh, hey, Lee...
No, it's not a bad time.
Yeah, I still have those boots.
Well, maybe I'll wear
'em and maybe I won't.
And now, Jillian ..
Do you take Derek ..
Wait!
Jillian, I'm in love with you.
I want you .. no .. I need you
with all my heart and soul.
And my only regret is that I
didn't realize it
when we were together.
Those were the
happiest days of my life and
I want more of
those days. Please, Jillian ...
I love you. Will you
please take me back?
Brian, no.
You had your chance.
I mean, I thought
you were my 'Soul Train' ..
- but you didn't want me.
- 'Soul Mate.'
Soul Food? I'm sorry ...
but I'm in love with Derek now.
I see.
- And you really feel that way?
- Yeah.
I mean, he's everything I have
especially since my
mom died of cancer.
Ha ha ...
Alright, party people.
Please clear the dance floor
for the bride and
groom's first dance.
And here to sing
a romantic ballad is
the one and only Sting.
... fields of gold.
Hey, buck up there, sport.
- At least you gave it your all.
- I guess you're right.
- I still feel like crap, though.
- Well, look at it this way ...
You may have lost Jillian but
you can at least be
happy that she's happy.
- Plus you can always call Lauren.
- No, I can't.
Why not?
She's never
gonna speak to me again.
I gave her worms.
www.tvsubtitles.net