Translated By The Community Of WWW.MY-SUBS.COM
Hey, where's Cleveland?
Doesn't he have a
relative in town or something?
I dunno, but I ordered him a
beer and now it's just sittin' there
lookin' lonlier than Alan
Rickman's answering machine.
Hello. You've reached Alan Rickman
at 0-5-5-5-0-1-2-2.
Please leave a message at the beep.
Hello, Alan Rickman.
It's Alan Rickman
reminding you to move
the pork chops from the
freezer to the refigerator
so they defrost properly.
Do not disappoint me.
Hello. You've reached Alan Rickman
at 0-5-5-5-0-1-2-2.
Please leave a message at the beep.
Alan, it's me again.
Remember that
turtle joke for the party.
Hah hah hah hah hah.
Hey, y'all, I want you to
meet my cousin from Jamaica,
- Madam Claude.
- Nice to meet you all.
Eh heh, you sound like
the crab from Little Mermaid.
I had crabs once. It was awful.
You gotta by that cream
that comes with the little comb.
- 'Course I can still use the comb.
- Well, that's Quagmire.
And you know what else?
Madam Claude is psychic.
She can tell you what
you were in a past life.
I already know what I was.
A strawberry.
Ah ... it's another pleasant day
for me, Peter the Strawberry.
Hey, Mr. Worm.
I welcome you arrival
'cos we're all part of the same garden.
Wait ... whadda ya ... uh ... uh...
hey .. hey ... hey, get outta here!
Hey, hey! Aaah! Aaaaahhh!
Aaaahhhh! Aaaahhhh! Aaaaahhh!
He was my neighbour,
and he violated me.
Now I'll never end up in a fancy pie.
What d'you say, Joe?
You want your past life read?
It'll be fun.
Sure, why not?
OK, dear. Close your
eyes and clear your mind.
OK. I'm seein' somethin'.
Joe, you were an octopus.
Yes! Yes, this is so awesome!
Damn it!!
Ah, that's so cool!
That's so cool! Do me next!
I'm gettin' somethin'.
I see you in London.
I think it's the 1800's.
Oh, my! You were Jack the Ripper!
Giggity!
- What about Peter!
- Yeah, Peter next.
Oh, I don't think there's
anything in that black bag for me.
You're wrong, Peter.
Let us begin.
Oh, my! You were
a very important man.
You were Griffin Peterson,
the founder of the city of Quahog.
Now wait a second, Cool
Runnings. We learned in school
that Miles Chatterbox
Musket founded Quahog, after
he was saved by the magic clam.
No, that is a myth.
Peter, you were
the founder of Quahog.
I see ... I see
England a long time ago.
It is a crisp, clear Spring morning,
and Griffin Peterson is
ridin' to the home of his beloved.
Peterson, what are you doing
here? Shouldn't you be down at
your job, making oblong
bricks out of manure and straw?
No, we're off. It's Martin Luther Day.
- Ah hah!
- Yes, that's a very smart joke.
- Isn't that right, comedy professors?
- Mmmmm. Oh, yeah. Well done. Indeed.
- Now, what d'you want?
- I wanna marry your daughter.
and I'm here to
ask for your blessing.
What could you possibly
have to offer my daughter?
Well, I'm one of
the few guys in this town
who isn't dying a
slow, painful diarrhoea death.
Alright, come on in.
- Knock, Knock. Lady Redbush?
- Griffin! It's so good to see you.
I'm so horny. Kiss my hand.
What are you doin' here?
I was just walkin' off the rotted
goose anus I had for breakfast
and I thought I'd come by
and ask you a little question.
- What's that?
- Will you marry me?
Ah! Oh, my God, yes!!
Yes, I will, Griffin. Oh,
I thought you'd never ask.
- Did you do it?
- I did it.
Ooh yah yah yah
oh boy yah yah yah yah ...
But in another part of
London there was a man
who was not in such good spirits.
The King of England.
Stewart, the turd.
Oh .... I'm so bored.
I wish to be entertained.
Where's my troop of actors?
Presenting ... the cast
of How I Met Your Mother.
- You told her, I told you I kissed her?
- Dude, you broke the bro' code.
- That's not against the bro' code.
- Yes it is. Article 15B.
That's the heart
of the bro' code, man.
Well, you're right, I
guess I did break the bro' code.
Hey! Whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa ... whoa ... whoa!
What is this?
Are these jokes?
Do people in other
castles think this is funny?
Well, yeah. We get a pretty
sizeable chunk of Princes 18 to 34.
I think I'd like to
delete this from my TIVO.
- Are you sure you
want to delete this program?
- Yes.
Bring me my mid
season replacement fool!
- Hi there.
- I want to hear some jokes, fool.
Well, y'know, I don't really tell jokes.
I .. I like to tell stories from my life
and let the humour flow
organically from everyday situations.
A-hem.
Yeah, my aunt Frieda was a real card
She always had
the most wonderful spirit,
even when her mind started to go.
I remember once, she
wrote a letter to my uncle Tom
from whom she'd been
divorced for several years.
And in the letter, she'd
misspelled his name T-O-M-M.
And I said, "Frieda, you've
spelled Tom's name wrong."
"You need to take out one of the M's."
And she said, "Which one?"
Y'know, you're gonna
be #@%*!@$ dead in 5 seconds
if aunt Frieda doesn't
throw a pie at somebody!
I mean, part of that is you
sorta have to know my family ...
Make me laugh!!!
Hey, look .... keys!
Ha ha ha ah ah.
Oh, that's so satirical.
Ah ha ha. What social commentary?
Ah ha ha. Well, now
I'm in a wonderful humour.
I wish to go for a walk into town.
Hey, coachman. Let's drive
on the left side of the road
and see if that catches on.
Good Lord! Who is that?
That's Lady Redbush, and her
husband-to-be, Griffin Peterson.
That piece of arse is marrying
that tall glass of poop juice?
Well, not if I have
anything to say about it.
A woman of that calibre
should be married to a King.
- Well, what are
you gonna do about him?
- I'm the King, jester.
I'm going to have him exiled
to the farthest corner of the world.
And then she'll be all mine.
Why is he such a jerk to everybody?
Because he has
a very, very small penis.
I've seen it, actually, and .. and it's,
like,  you don't even
want to make fun of it,
- y'know ... it's just
... medically fascinating.
- I kinda wanna see it.
Yeah, it's like
that one grape in the
bunch that never got to be a grape.
I wonder what's keepin' Griffin.
Oh, I'm sure he'll be along, sweetie.
Remember, he's tubby. It
takes him a while to move around.
I hope he didn't get diarrhoea and die.
- Can I feel those boobs?
- No! Daddy, what are you, sick?
Hey, it's a different time!
What a wonderfully exciting day.
I'm young, I'm all dressed up,
and I'm on my way
to marry the woman I love.
And there's 290 years separating
me from the films of Kevin Smith.
Hey, Peterson!
- Who are you?
- I'm King Stewart.
- Don't you recognise
me from the coins?
Oh, yeah. The one's with your profile.
You know, you look
really weird from the side.
Well, that's something we
didn't really think out too well
when we started ...
but never mind that!!
You're going into exile, Peterson.
I'm shipping you out on
the first boat to the new world.
But I'm supposed to get married today.
Oh, yeah? Where you
going for your honeymoon?
- That medium sized hill.
- Wrong. Seize him!
And King Stewart's
cruelty was only just beginning.
Maybe he changed his
mind. Maybe he's not comin'.
Ohhhhh, come on now. There,
feel better after I just said that?
- Give me one little touch.
- No!
I hate this. I .. I .. I hate my life!
- Oh ... the King!
- The King is here.
I didn't vote for him.
Your Majesty, this is
a real honour. Carter Redbush.
Very glad to meet you.
Hello. Harry McAfee.
As a citizen, I'm proud
to have you reign over me
and the McAfee Fertilizer company.
Lady Redbush, I wish I
was here on a happier errand.
But I'm afraid I must inform
you that Griffin Peterson is dead.
What?!
Now that some time has
passed, do you wanna go out?
With Griffin Peterson
exiled to the new world
and Lady Redbush
believing he was dead,
King Stewart was
now free to marry her.
The bride and groom
have written their own vows.
Our love is like two
figs hanging from a fig tree,
cradled by Cupid's own hand.
You and I are like t...
Oh ...oh ... I'm sorry.
Is my wedding interrupting
your .. your promotion?
We're right in the middle of our show.
OK, right now. You
have a time slot. Go there!
Maybe finish this candy bar
before you open another one.
Well, at least it wasn't one of those
promos where they've got the whole
cast shoving each other
playfully,  like they're all good pals.
Oh, oh, look! There we go! Oh, look
at 'em jostling each other around.
Oh, they give each other a
hard time, but they're friends.
Is that areal show?
No, it's just ... no, it's ..
somebody's makin' a joke. Forget it.
Meanwhile, Griffin Peterson and
the other exiles passed the time
on the ship to the new world.
Ah, crap! A splinter.
- Well, it's been nice knowin' you guys.
- So, what'd you do to get exiled?
I got caught pleasuring
myself to a painstakingly
etched engraving of the wife of Bath.
What you do?
Ah, I slept with an underaged virgin
to cure my puff penis.
Hey, fellers. You wanna join
me in a game of mumble peg?
- Oh, no thanks.
- Fine, I'll play by myself.
.. mumble .. mumble .. mumble ..
One - nothing.
Eventually, after many months at sea
Griffen Peterson and his shipmates
finally reached the new world.
I declare this land .. Quahog.
This place is nothin' but a
wilderness. What're we gonna do?
We're gonna build a new settlement.
We'll have a happy new life,
and we'll have equal rights for all.
Except Blacks, Asians, Hispanics,
Jews, Gays, Women, Muslims ..
Um ... everybody
who's not a white man.
And I mean "white" white,
so no Italians, no Polish. Just people
from Ireland, England, and Scotland.
But from only certain
parts of Scotland and Ireland.
Just full blooded whites.
No, y'know what? Not even whites.
Nobody gets any rights.
Ahhhh ... America.
How's your
stewed fox-quail, my dear?
Oh, it's quite good.
I'm also enjoyin' the turtled hen.
Isn't the turtled hen good?
So, listen. You and I
need to have a conversation
about you not bearing me a son.
Well, my Lord, we've discussed this.
We have to have sex in
order for me to bear you a son.
Oh, I know. I've just been so
tired, and I've had so much work,
and I think .. I think
I wanted to the other day
but I couldn't find you.
So, y'know, it's like both of
us on our schedules, y'know?
Well, why don't we do it tonight?
Maybe. Tonight might work. Yea...
Oh, no! I got that thing in the morning.
Oh .. how 'bout tomorrow at four?
You know I'm with
my mother tomorrow at four.
Oh, darn it! I'm going to
be so horny tomorrow at four.
Y'know, I gotta say, I'm a little mad
at you for not bein' more available.
We can have sex
right now on the table.
Hey! hey, hey, hey ... hey.
We eat here.
Griffin Peterson and the other
colonists worked day and night
to build their new
settlement, until finally,
after much hard work, the
colony of Quahog was complete.
It didn't take long before Quahog
was a thriving new world settlement,
bustling with life.
Boy, everything's
shapin' up real nice.
Yeah, and we finally
finished the town Abortion Clinic.
Time had helped
Griffin forget Lady Redbush,
and soon he found
himself a hearty new wife.
Boy, that was fantastic.
You must have had a lot of practice.
No, not really. I've been
saving myself for marriage.
Ahhhhhh ....... We should
probably open up some windows.
I don't know what to do, jester. I
can't be married to the King anymore.
My heart still
belongs to Griffin Peterson,
but he's dead.
- Ahh. No. He's not.
- What?
I was ordered to keep silent by
the King, under threat of execution
but .. you're gonna see this anyway.
Oh, my God! He's alive!
Jester, I've got to get to him.
I'll help you. But
only if I can go with you.
If I stay here, the King'll
execute me for telling you all this.
Well .. OK. But how
are we gonna get there?
We'll hitch a ride on one of
the slave ships tomorrow night,
after an all new Shovin' Buddies.
Followed by an all
new slowly rotating black man.
And so Lady Redbush
sailed off to the new world.
to find her beloved.
And the timin' was good, because
his new wife was a pain in him arse.
.. and then I
finished scrubbing the kettle
but .. then I saw that I'd missed a spot
and, oh .. I was so worried that
the whole thing wasn't clean enough
so I went back and started
washing it again, and sure enough ...
.. I'd missed another spot, and
there was a clump of cornmeal
- under the rim
from when I made breakfast.
- Shut up, Meg! I prithee, shut up!
Griffen!
Lady Redbush.
And so, Griffin Peterson and
Lady Redbush were happily reunited.
Of course, Griffin had to go
through the complex, extensive divorce
procedure required
by 18th century society.
Gone! What do you mean she's gone?
Sire, Lady Redbush has
been gone these 6 months.
- 6 months?
- Yes. Forgive me, Sire, but how
could you not be aware of this?
Don't you share a
bed chamber with her?
Well, I mean, sometimes we .. we..
we sleep .. we.. we go to different ..
er, we go to bed at.. at different
times. We've both been so busy ...
it's been .. rediculous! I .. I thought
she was takin' a class or something.
Oh, man, that sucks!
Because I'm so horny.
Damn it! Oh, I wanted
to do sex to her tonight.
Well then, I guess
we've gotta go get her.
Yeah .. alright.
Months rolled by, and Griffin
and Lady Redbush continued to
flourish happily in
the colony of Quahog,
completely unaware that
King Stewart was on the march.
There was a peaceful
town called Quahog
Where people lived in harmony
They never had no kind of trouble
There was no hint of misery.
Then all at once the trouble started
A pack of murderers and thieves
Like swarms of
locusts they descended
Their aim to
make the townfolk flee
They've gotta be here somewhere.
Where's my 1st lieutenant?
Here I am, sir. Yessir, right
indeed, here indeed, yes I am, sir.
I want you to turn this
settlement upside down until
you find Lady
Redbush and Griffin Peterson.
That fat bastard thinks he can
steal my bride and get away with it
I wouldn't bet a corn
farthing on him escaping.
No, I wouldn't. Not a corn
farthing would I bet. No sir.
- What's wrong with you?
- Little wrong in the head, I am,
from eatin' some
bad sausages. Yes, bad
sausages that I eat, indeed, sir.
Yes, I did some bad sausages ate I.
Oh, Griffin, this time together
has been the happiest of my life.
Me too, Lady Redbush.
All those months I was
without you, I never stopped
seein' your face in
the back of my wife's head.
And all those months I
was sailin' for the new world
I saw your face
in every slave's stomach.
Tell me we'll be together forever.
We will.
I found 'em, your Majesty.
Indeed, yes I did found 'em, did I
- did, yessir, I did.
- Yeah. OK, OK ... whatever.
Alright, Peterson. Two
things are gonna happen here:
I'm gonna take my wife back,
and then I'm gonna kill you!
Alright, alright,
Mr. King, sir. You win.
I'm sorry, Lady Redbush.
But he is your husband.
Let me just, uh, walk over
here and get your things for you.
Nyaah-ahhhhh!
Alright, your Majesty. If
you wanna leave with your pal in
one piece, I suggest you
throw down your weapons.
Go ahead and kill him, Griffin.
You kill him, and I'll kill her.
Go ahead. You kill her, I'll kill him.
Go ahead. You kill him, I'll kill her.
Knock yourself out.
You kill her, I'll kill him.
Ha ha ha. This is me laughing.
You kill him, I'll kill her.
Ha ha ha. This is me
before Ultra Slim-Fast.
You kill her, I'll kill him.
Wait! Wait! There's gotta
be a better way to settle this.
- Talent show?
- Talent show!
Hear ye! Hear ye!
This talent competition will
decide rightful possession of
the good Lady Redbush and
control of the colony of Quahog.
We first present
King Stewart of England with
some observational humour.
Hi, there, everybody.
You know, my aunt
Frieda was a real card.
She always had
the most wonderful spirit,
even when her mind started to go.
What the !*$#@?
I remember once, she
wrote a letter to my uncle Tom
from whom she'd been
divorced for several years.
And in the letter, she'd
misspelled his name T-O-M-M.
This .. this is my bit.
These .. these are all my bits.
Ssshh. This is funny.
Unbelievable.
And I said, "Frieda, you've
spelled Tom's name wrong."
"You need to take out one of the M's."
And she said, "Which one?"
Clap your hands, everybody.
And everybody clap your hands.
We are the Quahog colonists
- and Mort the Jew.
- Hey there.
We're out here on stage tonight
to do a show for you
We got Peterson on the violin
and Quagmire and
Joe will be joinin' in
We got Stumpy
Shamus on the lead guitar
and he's gonna
give you a great big ...
Aaaaaaarrrrrrrrr! Break!
Oh, God. They put
so much work into theirs.
I .. I didn't know
we could rip off movies.
And from then on, Lady
Redbush and Griffin Peterson
lived in peace and happiness.
- Oh, Griffen, I love you.
- And I, you.
Let's grow old into our 30's together.
I wanna have a baby with you.
And I wanna be there there
when you die, giving birth to it.
And so ends the tale of Griffin
Peterson and the founding of Quahog.
Well, what a bunch of
delightfully colorful characters.
- So, was that it?
- That's it.
Now stay tuned for an
all new Cross Armed Opposites.
- This guy.
- No. This guy.
Both of us.
Ah ha ha ha ha ha. Ah ha ha ha
ha ha ha ha ha ha .... ahhhhhh.
Subtitles by Keef
www.tvsubtitles.net