Translated By The Community Of WWW.MY-SUBS.COM
ENGLISH
We now return
to The Adventures of Aquaman.
- Yeah?
- Hey, can you grab me another beer?
Yeah. Anything else? Maybe a TV guide
and another pillow for your feet?
No, actually, get me, like, a Dewar's and soda.
And try to keep the saltwater out of it
if you could.
Try... Try to keep the salt...
- We're surrounded by saltwater. It's difficult.
- I know. I'm just saying... I'm just saying try.
- Want me to wipe your ass too?
- That's a helpful tone.
I'm just saying.
You're abusing your powers a little bit.
This is time that could be spent
getting me my beverage.
What are you doing? We gotta get ready
for your grandpa's 80th birthday.
- Calm down. He's just your father.
- But I love him.
His folksy racism,
his "I don't care where I am" flatulence.
And the way it seems like he's chewing
even when there's no food.
- Hiya, Dad.
- Francis, it's so good to see you.
Lois, you haven't changed a bit,
you lying bitch.
Why don't you come into the dining room?
The table's all set for your birthday dinner.
Lois, actually, Dad said he would prefer it
if you did notjoin us.
You know, you being a Protestant and all.
- He said it's OK if you sit at the kids' table.
- I cooked the damn dinner.
I knew you were gonna react like this.
That's why I brought Bill Lumbergh
to explain it.
Yeah, I'm gonna need you to go ahead
and not complain about this.
And if you could go ahead
and sit at the kids' table, that'd be great.
I'm just saying, '70s boobs were different.
I don't know.
It won't kill you
to contribute to the conversation.
Dad, tell us about World War I and how
America defeated Kaiser Permanente.
Lois, when are you
gonna get that baby baptised?
Oh, God. Not this again. Francis,
why the hell is this always an issue with you?
Because I love this family
and I don't want my grandson to burn in hell.
I love you, Grandpa. Your toenails
are the same colour as my school bus.
You really think splashing magic water
on Stewie will keep him out of hell?
Watch that talk
or you'll get your heathen head smacked!
Very Christian.
"Believe what I say or I'll hurt you. "
Now you're getting it!
- Peter, we have a problem.
- Hang on, Lois. I'm watching a movie.
And now back to Jaws 5- Fire Island.
- You think we should be this far out?
- Stop worrying, Mark. We'll be fine.
Hey, I'm gonna eat y'all.
I'm gonna eat that hairy leg.
I'm gonna eat that one too.
I can see right up them shorts.
I got a whole bunch of rows of teeth
to chew you with.
Now, wait a minute.
I did have a chubby kid on a raft earlier today.
It's OK, though.
I've been swimming a lot lately.
Yummy.
Your father won't let up
about Stewie getting baptised.
I am sick of him always trying to force
his religious views on us.
I'll talk to him, Lois, but when my dad wants
something, it's like sex with Kobe Bryant.
You can kick and scream all you want,
but it's gonna happen.
- Dad, what are you doing?
- There's no cross! Every kitchen needs one.
Nothing says "eat up" like a bleeding
half-naked Jew nailed to a piece of wood.
Listen, Dad, I gotta talk to you.
Lois was wondering if maybe you could...
I don't know, ease up on the whole
Jesus-ay Christ-ay, if you catch my drift?
You're a lapsed Catholic, Peter.
Your wife's a Protestant whore
and your baby isn't even baptised!
All right, Dad. I don't want you to hate me,
so I'll make a deal with you.
If we get Stewie baptised,
you and all other old people
have to acknowledge and be aware
there's crap in the corners of your mouth.
I'll think about it. Now let's go!
Old people are gross, no matter how cute
they try to be on Desperate Housewives.
Go ahead, switch over to ABC
for five seconds. I'll wait five seconds.
Oh, my God. Did you see?
Did you see how old and ugly they are?
Oh, my God, that redhead looks like
somebody poured Silly Putty over their knee.
I'm sorry, Mr Griffin,
but I can't baptise little Stewie today.
Our last shipment of holy water is tainted.
Tainted? Holy water? How did that happen?
We'll call you when we get a new shipment in.
There's no such thing as tainted holy water.
Come on! We'll do it ourselves.
Stewie Griffin, I baptise you in the name
of the Father, the Son and the Holy Ghost.
- And Space Ghost.
- What are you doing?
Oh, my God. This is almost as bad
as my bath with Kathy Bates.
Yeah, I think I'm going to get out.
Stewie, you don't look so good.
Baby, you're burning up.
Oh, my God. Stewie! Stewie! Speak to me.
Don't... don't take me to a black doctor.
Mr and Mrs Griffin, I've examined your son
and he is suffering from toxic anaemia,
which has weakened his immune system.
- Is he gonna die?
- No, but he's vulnerable to infection.
He must be
in a germ-free plastic environment.
My God, you mean
like John Travolta in that movie?
Oh, no. You're gonna take his face off,
like in Face/Off?
It looks like the operation was a success.
Do you know what the best part of this is?
Try licking yourself.
You bastard.
He meant The Boy in the Plastic Bubble.
How could this have happened?
Stewie's been exposed to tainted holy water.
Peter, you had Stewie baptised
behind my back?
This is no worse than when I rented out
your uterus to those inner-city immigrants.
Peter, you're a complete slave
to your father's religion.
What about your religious beliefs?
- You have a choice, you know.
- I do?
Of course. You're a grown man.
You can pick any religion you want.
Really? You know, Lois, maybe you're right.
Maybe I should pick my own religion.
The question is, which one?
I tell you what you can pick -
a tune on the piano.
How the whiz-bang does the rest of it go?
Quick, make something up.
What are all these women
doing in our living room?
I took your advice and picked a new religion.
- I'm gonna be a Mormon.
- A Mormon? Are you sure?
Nailing a different wife every night?
It's a no-brainer.
Lois, this is Kimmy,
the checkout girl from the Korean market.
Nancy, our postal carrier.
And Tiffany, the woman
who stands downtown and screams at traffic.
I ate a tube of Crest for dinner!
Isn't she funny? She's definitely
the Kramer of my Mormon wives.
- Nancy, get me a beer.
- Mormons aren't allowed to drink alcohol.
- Did you just throw those women away?
- No. Maybe.
Also in the news,
trouble at St Phillips Church.
A shipment of tainted holy water
could put some local babies in jeopardy.
Sounds dangerous.
Be careful next time you're at confession
talking about cheating on your wife
with that drag queen.
At least you're in no danger,
since you only visit church
to leave your self-delivered,
half-dead newborns on the step.
Coming up, how to turn
your unwanted change into folding money.
It's sad seeing Stewie in that plastic bubble.
I think he looks like a bunny.
That's it. Keep laughing.
When I get out of here, you're going to get it!
I'll lull you into a false sense of security
like those network television announcers.
Tonight on Mama's Family, Mama's got
more than she can handle with the in-laws.
A deadly fire could spell death
for a honeymoon couple on all new Hotel.
On Newhart, the stockings
are stuffed with comedy as Bob plays Santa.
Then a sniper's bullet threatens
a partnership on all-new Cagney & Lacey.
Tonight on Night Court,
love is in the air
when Judge Harry's
old school flame comes to town.
Then a child's death could mean
the case of Arnie Becker's life on LA Law.
- Night Court at eight.
- LA Law at nine.
Remember, don't touch Stewie.
He's not allowed to have any human contact.
Finish the job, idiot! There's no ventilation!
It smells like Brian Dennehy in here!
I see London, I see France,
I see Stewie's unsightly chapped ass.
Hey, gay bo, I'm up here. Up here.
Hi. My name's Peter. I'm a Jehovah's Witness,
here to spread the good news
of the story of Jesus.
OK. Go ahead.
Really? Wow! Boy!
You're the first person
who didn't slam the door on me.
OK, well, Jesus was
a miracle worker of sorts.
He would travel from place to place
putting things right that once went wrong
and hoping each time that his next leap
would be the leap home.
- What are you doing with my wife?
- Oh, boy!
The pathway to enlightenment
starts with an unfettered, focused mind.
- Look out!
- What are you doing?
I thought that dot on your head
was from a sniper rifle.
Peter, this spot is a sacred adornment.
It's a portal, an opening,
through which all light, rejuvenation,
joy and ecstasy may enter the human form.
- A vagina?
- Get out!
Hey, Stewie, three o'clock.
Time for The View.
No, no! Not again!
Let me out of here!
I can't watch another second!
Relax, Stewie. The doctor gave me this
so you can get some exercise.
Boy! Stewie's more wound up
than Dad was that time he took steroids.
Peter, could you please pass the potatoes?
Dammit, Meg!
- And now back to Happy Days.
- That Fonzie is magic.
I love how he hits the jukebox
to make it work.
- What is it, Mr C?
- Fonz, I...
I wanted to pleasure Marion
for our anniversary.
But, as you know, I have erectile dysfunction.
- There we go.
- Thank you, Arthur.
Hey!
Brian, will you carry me upstairs?
I want to look at my toys.
- No. I'm watching television.
- Come on! I'm sick!
All right. Come here.
Todd, I feel like we'll never
have a baby of our own.
We will, Kelly.
You just have to visualise it.
Come on, close your eyes.
Picture a happy, healthy baby boy at play.
Put him in a magic bubble
and release him to the universe.
Honey, now I want you to visualise Lindsay
Lohan naked, doing a backwards crab walk.
- What?
- Just do this for me!
Peter, where have you been, lad?
Dad, I was trying to find my own religion,
but it didn't work out.
I haven't been this disappointed
since I lost my virginity.
Wanna get some breakfast or something?
You want to find religion,
all you got to do is look in your heart.
Who's always been there for you
offering wisdom and truth?
You've known him all along, son.
Now worship him!
Oh, my God! Dad's right!
There is only one person!
And it's time for him
to be properly worshipped.
I, Peter Griffin, hereby establish
the First United Church of the Fonz!
Fonzie, if this be your will, give me a sign.
Hi, I'm Lindsay Lohan.
This is how a crab walks.
It sure is! Fonzie be praised!
All right, Dad!
Two days ago this was an old barn.
And now, thanks to you,
it's an old barn with a sign on it.
All things are possible
through the Lord God Arthur Fonzarelli.
- You're going through with this?
- Absolutely.
You know this place only cost me 100 bucks?
That's a better deal
than that Aaron Neville megaphone.
I want to thank you guys
for making me activity director for the day.
OK, first of all, can everybody...
What the hell?
What the hell's wrong with this thing?
OK. We're about to start the sack race.
Peter, it's not a good idea
to be putting these flyers all over town.
- People will think you're crazy.
- You like to lose a bunch of teeth?
I'm sorry.
That was more than what was called for.
But it happens
when you challenge someone's faith.
Peter, I know this is important to you.
But I don't want to see you humiliated.
I don't think anyone's
gonna want to worship the Fonz.
- Is this the church of the Fonz?
- Yes, it is.
I read your flyer!
Finally a religion that makes sense!
Hey, everyone! I found him. Over here!
There you are.
You would not believe the morning I've had.
What is this?
I thought you said we were going to church!
This is church. A new church, created by
a man brave enough to follow his own vision.
Please rise.
Now sit on it.
- The Fonz be with you.
- And also with you.
- Let us "hey".
- Hey.
I can't believe people are buying this.
Fonzie's cool, Brian. Deep down, I think
we all secretly yearn to be Italian and stupid.
A reading from the letters of Potsie
to the Tuscaderos.
"Yea, and did Fonzie downstairs cometh
from his apartment above the garage
and sayeth he, 'Reassembleth will I
the pieces of my motorcycle
though I suffereth
from temporary blindness. "'
"'And, yea, for I am holy, befriendeth I will
Sticks Downy, the only Negro in Wisconsin. "'
- Amen.
- What's that smell?
- Black spray paint.
- What were you painting?
- You think you're so funny.
Well, as soon as I figure out where I am,
you're dead, Brian!
Dammit. I haven't been this dizzy since I did
those helium whippets at that birthday party.
OK, OK, ready? Here goes.
I am a female. I have a high voice.
I have reproductive organs inside of me
and I buy groceries.
Peter, your religion is an abomination!
I never thought you could ever embarrass me
more than you did at Cousin Mary's wedding.
If anyone knows of any reason why these two
should not be married, let him speak now.
Really? Nobody's gonna speak up?
I'm the one who's gonna have to say it?
All right.
Genital warts!
But you said I should look into my heart
to find my religion.
Yes! Real religion!
What I saw today wasn't religion.
It was just a bunch of sheep singing songs
and listening to ridiculous tall tales!
- Actually, that is religion.
- Shut your trap!
- Ha! You tell him!
- Why? I agree with you.
Peter's found another way to exploit
people's ignorance and that's wrong.
You think I'm wr...?
See, Brian? That's a word the Fonz can't say.
Because all is right when you welcome
Fonzie into your life. Fonzie be with you.
I ought to take off my belt
and slap the crap out of him!
Look, I don't like you and you don't like me.
I suggest we set aside our differences
and work together.
- I have an idea to snap Peter out of this.
- Work together? You and me?
Sure. Sometimes opposites
work well together. Peter taught me that.
Reverend, I gotta talk to you. Last night
I had sex with a teenage blonde and her mom.
That's quite a story, but there's no confession
so there's really no reason for you to tell me.
Are you kidding? I'm telling everybody!
Let us pause to reflect on the sacred mystery
of Richie's elder brother Chuck,
who ascended the stairs with his basketball
in season one and never came down again.
There's one problem. When a religion gets
too powerful, it's bound to have imitators.
- What are you talking about?
- Hi. I'm Sherman Hemsley.
I've just established the Church of George
Jefferson. Who wants to move on up?
Hi, I'm Gavin MacLeod and I established
the Church of Captain Stubing.
Who wants to come on board?
Hi, I'm Kirk Cameron!
You here to convert people
to the Church of Mike Seaver?
No. I'm here to convert people to Christianity.
Well, he was on Growing Pains.
I can't believe it. Everybody's gone!
People are always looking for the next voice
to tell them what to do.
And here I was thinking
I was making a difference.
I thought I was connecting with people.
Could there be anyone stupider than me?
- Madonna?
- Yeah. She's pretty stupid.
- That's something we can agree on.
- Absolutely. Francis?
Oh, major idiot. Major idiot.
Yeah. Gosh! I guess we do have
some common ground here after all, huh?
Yeah. And "La Isla Bonita" - not a real place.
I looked it up, bought a globe, couldn't find it.
- That makes her a liar too.
- She's awful!
- Awful, awful woman.
- I agree, yeah.
- And she's a whore.
- Yeah, big time.
Oh, everybody. Canseco? Eww.
- Dennis Rodman.
- Dennis Rodman. Yeah.
- Rodman? My God!
- I think he lost all his money, didn't he?
Rodman? Are you sure
you're not thinking MC Hammer?
No, no... Well, him too. I read somewhere.
I think it was in, like, Stuff or so...
No, you know what it was?
It was on Real Sports with Bryant Gumbel.
And they said
that he's in the poorhouse now.
- You think she'd do him now?
- Would Madonna do Rodman now?
Yeah. Cos it's not the money,
it's about pissing off Daddy.
- She's got a lot of problems.
- Lot of problems.
Yeah, we are smarter.
We are smarter than Madonna.
No question.
Well, I should probably
get out of these robes.
- Look at you. You're all better.
- That's right, Brian. And you are toast!
I'm gonna get in the gym, get my lats back,
and then me and my friends from Cobra Kai
are gonna take you down, man!
Listen. Sorry I had to
rain on your parade, Peter.
It's all right, Brian. I guess
the Church of the Fonz was just a bad idea.
Not really, Peter. You were preaching
honesty, friendship, courage.
If you managed to inspire even one person
to embrace those values, you were a success.
Thanks, Lois.
But I doubt there's any chance of that.
Visiontext Subtitles: Simon Campbell
ENGLISH