Translated By The Community Of WWW.MY-SUBS.COM
Family Guy
Airport '07
Ladies and gentlemen,
welcome to the Redneck Comedy Tour!
Featuring...
You know you're a redneck if you come
from a rural area and behave as such.
Oh, that dog of mine!
You tell me how that got in there!
He's right.
Who knows how that got in there?
Peter, can we please go now?
This is excruciating.
Are you kidding, Brian?
These men and their redneck
lifestyle really speak to me.
This is the greatest show
I've seen in years.
Not like the last time
I was at a comedy club.
I hear this guy's hilarious.
He played Kramer, you know.
Oh, this is gonna be fun!
Peter... what the hell are you
doing with a pickup truck?
Wait. Let me guess.
This is because of the Redneck
Comedy Festival, isn't it?
Oh, that dog of mine.
Peter, you can't suddenly decide to be
a redneck just because of some show.
Some show?
Lois, those men showed me
the way to an identity
I've been searching for my whole life.
I am going to do everything
a redneck is supposed to do.
This is going to be more painful to watch
than when he ate
half a Fudgesicle in one bite.
Oh, boy! A Fudgesicle!
Chris, what happened to the couch?
Dad dragged it out on the lawn,
'cause he said
that's what rednecks do.
Hey, Meg, come here. Have a seat.
Dad, what are you doing?
Meg, I'm a redneck,
which means I am about
to do something to you
that you will not remember
until you're 40.
Meg, come back here!
I meant sex!
We now return to Carl Sagan's Cosmos,
edited for rednecks.
I'm Carl Sagan.
Just how old is our planet?
Scientists believe it's four bil...
...hundreds and hundreds of years old.
Scientists have determined that
the universe was created by...
God...!
...big bang.
- If you look at the bones of a...
- Jesus.
...aurus Rex, it's clear, by the
use of carbon-dating that...
Mountain Dew is the best soda ever made.
- Peter, do we have to watch this?
- This is what rednecks watch, Brian.
Peter, that's disgusting.
Here. Spit in this cup instead.
Oh, there's my apple juice.
Stewie, wait. Don't...
Where's my money?
You going to give me my money?
Never mind.
Hey, Brian, check it out!
Peter, you painted over the back window.
Isn't that dangerous?
I'm a redneck, Brian.
We like people driving behind us
to know what our beliefs are.
Peter, what the hell?! My car!
Aw, damn it!
Hey! Hey, come back!
Oh, sorry, Quagmire.
How the hell am I supposed
to get to the airport?!
I got to fly a plane in 20 minutes.
Oh, I can drive you.
I got a pickup truck. See?
Well, come on!
- Quagmire, I am so sorry.
- Don't worry about it.
- We can go after them.
They're tagged! They're tagged!
Just get me to the airport.
All right. Thanks a lot, Peter.
That's all the motivation
I need to actually do this.
Did we finish fueling?
Do you see the hose in the plane?
No.
Well, then, I guess we're finished.
Thanks, George. You want to say that
one more time without the sarcasm?
Good afternoon, ladies and gentlemen.
This is your captain, Glenn Quagmire.
We're looking at about a
four-and-a-half-hour flight time today.
We've got clear skies, good visibility.
The temperature in Atlanta is 64 degrees.
The flight's going to be a
little longer than we've expected.
We've got some very strong headwinds...
giggety.
Uh, flight attendants,
please prepare for takeoff.
What the hell?!
Oh, my God! We're going down!
Secure your own mask first,
and then assist the child!
- But the bag's not inflating!
- It's all right!
Even though oxygen is flowing,
the bag may not inflate!
That was too close.
Sir, we have a confirmed crash.
Flight 37 is down.
We'd better alert the mayor.
I'll have to interrupt his photo op.
My Pet Goat. Page one.
"You know, said my pet goat, I'm sure,
if I watched Grey's Anatomy, I'd like it,"
"but I just don't have the time."
"You should make the time,
said the farmer."
Our top story : There was drama
in the skies of Quahog today,
as a Trans National 767 was
forced to make a crash-landing.
That's right, Diane. As if the world
weren't already scary enough,
it seems you can't even get
on a plane safely these days.
Channel 5 has the spectacular footage.
Fortunately, no one was injured.
However, using state-of-the-art
Channel 5 computer technology,
we'll show you how disastrous
it could have been.
Here's how it would have looked if
the plane had crashed into a school.
Now here's how it would've
looked if the plane had crashed
into a school for bunnies.
Now here's how it would've
looked if the plane had crashed
into a school for bunnies
but one passenger had survived,
gone home, and mercilessly beat his wife.
I'm alive!
But boy, am I angry!
Someone's gonna have to pay for this!
Why! Why!
Is this because
I overcooked the roast?!
Powerful stuff.
You'd have to be made of stone
not to feel saddened by that.
Boy, Quagmire,
I'm really sorry they fired you.
I feel like this is partially my fault.
No, Peter, it's perfectly normal to
siphon jet fuel from an active runway
with the intention of
flying a pickup truck.
Look, I know I caused a lot of trouble,
but my redneck days are over.
No more crotch shots of me
getting out of a car.
Well, what are you
gonna do now, Quagmire?
Hey, it-it's all right.
I got enough in my savings
until I find another job.
I'll be fine.
Mom! Dad!
There's somebody in my tree house!
Yeah, and there's an annoying
little homo screaming in my kitchen.
Which one do you think
I'm more pissed about?
I'll remind you that I was invited here!
All right, who's up there?
- Oh, hey, Peter. Hey, Lois.
- Glenn, what are you doing up there?
Oh, I kind of moved in, if that's okay.
No airline'll hire me after the accident.
I'm broke and jobless.
Quagmire, you belong in a tree.
You're a nut.
What?!
Come on down, Quagmire.
You're staying with us.
Oh, great. This is gonna be worse
than the time I lived with Marlee Matlin.
Hi, Stewie.
Oh, come on, Marlee,
I know you can't hear them,
but you got to feel those
things slapping out of there!
Listen, I really want to thank you guys
for taking me in in my time of need.
Aw, forget it, Quagmire. It's the least
we could do after what happened.
Hello?
Oh, you must have a wrong number.
There's no one here by the name
of Longrod Von Hugendong.
- Okay, now add 20.
- Okay.
- Now multiply it by four.
- And what do you got?
- 8,008.
And what does 8,008 look
like on a calculator?
Oh, "boob"!
Boob! Yeah!
All right! All right! All right!
Boob!
What if we had two calculators
and we put them next to each other?
Yes, yes, yes.
Find one, yes!
Didn't mean to wake ya.
Peter, you and I need
to talk about Quagmire.
He's been living with us for over a
month, and I think it's enough now.
Lois, I'm the whole reason
he lost his job and his house.
Besides, I can't throw
my best friend out on the street
like a prom night Dumpster baby.
Hey, what are you doing out here?
Don't you want to dance?
Sure!
I'm just a prom night Dumpster baby
I got no mom or dad
Prom night Dumpster baby
My story isn't long,
but boy, it's awfully sad
- And though I came from a hole
- And though he came from a hole
- I'm singing right from the soul
- He's singing right from the soul
My fanny needs a blanket
And somebody to spank it
- I miss my mom
- But she's at the prom
So I'm a prom night Dumpster baby
Prom night Dumpster baby
- And I'm takin' a stroll
- He's takin' a stroll
- I'm takin' a stroll
I'm takin' a stroll.
Besides, Quagmire
doesn't even have a job.
Well, you're gonna have
to help him find one,
because I've had enough of
him living in this house.
You're overreacting, Lois.
And you can't spell
"overreacting" without "ovary."
- 'Cause you're a girl.
- I'm not overreacting!
Hey, uh, just an FYI,
really no reason to go into
any greater detail than this.
Uh, Stewie should probably
never use this pacifier again.
Okay, so I'll talk to him tomorrow?
- So how's the job hunt going?
- It's awful, Cleveland.
- Quagmire blew every gig we got him.
- It's too bad.
I really liked that job working
on the Starship Enterprise.
Dude,
you got to introduce me
to that black chick.
Guys, the only thing I know
how to do is fly a plane.
That's what I was born for.
And I'll never be happy
unless I can do it again.
Then that's the only answer.
Somehow we've got to get
Quagmire his job back.
Fellas, I think I have an idea.
Okay, guys, let's go over
the plan one more time.
Quagmire will pose as an airline
passenger on the 6:00 flight to New York.
Then Joe and I will sneak into
the flight attendants' lounge
while Cleveland distracts
the security personnel.
Once we have the uniforms
and credentials,
Cleveland, Joe and I will board the
plane posing as flight attendants.
Once we're in the air,
we drug the pilots.
At which point, Quagmire is forced to
step in and land the plane safely,
making him a hero.
Everybody clear?
Boy, this sounds like more trouble
than a moose on the interstate.
Hey, can you help me out?
I'm trying to get a couple of
bucks for something to eat.
- What's "moose stuff"?
- Whatever you want it to be.
I could have sex with you
or I could just stand over there
and drink from the lake.
And everything in between.
Get in.
All right, I'm gonna go
bring the pilots their coffee.
Hang on to something, 'cause
this ride's about to get rougher
than dating a hot girl
with a bad laugh.
- I really like you, Sandy.
- I really like you, too, Peter.
Yeah? You like it when I kiss you here?
- Yeah.
- How about here?
Oh, stop, I'm tick...
Ma'am, I hate to be a nuisance,
but your son stopped
kicking the back of my chair.
Thank you.
Oh, no!
Both the pilots are unconscious,
and we're in a nosedive.
If only there was someone
on board who could save us.
I said if only there was someone
Uh, Peter, I don't see Quagmire.
- Oh, that was great.
- Thanks.
I know you have a choice in airport sex,
and I appreciate your choosing Quagmire.
Please exercise caution when standing up,
as the contents of your panties
may have shifted during coitus.
All right, I got a plane to catch.
Say, which gate is flight 209?
209? That flight left half an hour ago.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God!
That plane's going down! My friends are
on that plane! They're all gonna die!
- What?! Oh, no!
- And that's not the worst part.
Here's the condom I said I put on.
Aren't I just the worst?
- Good evening, I'm Tom Tucker.
- And I'm Diane Simmons.
More trouble in the skies
over Quahog tonight,
as a Trans National jet is
apparently out of control.
Channel 5 has this exclusive recording of
a mayday communication from the cockpit.
Hey, there, son. Mind if I have a seat?
Hugh Hefner?!
You look like you got
something on your mind.
Ah, who the hell am I kidding?
I don't deserve to be a pilot.
- I've let everybody down.
- Did you do the best you could?
No. I was gonna, but I ended up
getting laid instead.
That reminds me of a guy
you might've heard of.
John Holmes.
Greatest porn star who ever lived.
You know what he once said?
He said : "You know,
I've got a 13-inch member..."
"and Glenn Quagmire is the best
damn pilot I've ever seen."
- John Holmes said that?
- You bet he did...
right before he died a very
painful, AIDS-related death
from having unprotected sex
with so many people.
Excuse me, Hef.
I got a plane to land.
- We're all gonna die!
- I can't believe this is happening!
- Help us!
- Help!
Men, we're doing everything
in our power to get you down.
Stand aside, sir.
I'll take it from here.
Peter, this is Quagmire.
Now I want you to listen very
carefully and do exactly as I tell you.
Take a firm hold of the throttle, and
pull the red mixture knob out slowly.
Okay.
All right, now do you see a button
that looks like a drunken gay guy
eyeing you from across the bar?
Yeah, I see it.
All right, press the button
right above it.
Some new developments
in the flight 209 drama.
Recently discharged pilot
Captain Glenn Quagmire
is apparently talking the plane down.
Ollie Williams has the story. Ollie?
- I'm at the wrong airport.
- Oops. Well, thanks, Ollie.
Coming up : Why calling every
Asian man you meet "Chung King"
can land an anchorman in hot water.
After this.
All right, Peter, slide
the red knob all the way out.
And the second those wheels touch the
ground, you hit the emergency brake.
- We made it!
- Hallelujah!
Get some!
Well, guess there's nothing left to
do but watch the end of Last Holiday.
Damn!
Oh, no, she di-in't.
- Oh, yes, she did.
- No, she di-in't.
- Yes, she did.
- Yes, she did, Peter! I just saw it!
- All right, take it easy.
Ah, Glenn, we are so thrilled for you.
Yeah, guess it didn't take too much
for you to get your job back,
- now that you're a hero.
- Yeah, and I'm so happy for you,
I don't even mind that I was
raped in a federal prison
after I was arrested for hijacking.
Well, I couldn't have
done it without you, guys.
You put yourselves on the line
and you gave me my life back.
I'll never forget that.
Now, if you'll excuse me.
I got to go to work.