Translated By The Community Of WWW.MY-SUBS.COM
Coming up, a New Orleans man
says his socks are finally dry.
But first, the big news
in entertainment this week
is the lovable child actress,
Olivia Fuller.
Oh, my God, Brian, that's Olivia
from the performing arts school.
What sort of overblown contract
has that dreadful bitch landed now?
Most of you know Olivia as the adorable
little girl in the Tasty Juice ads.
Hey, Mom, can I have some soda?
No, but you can have some Tasty Juice.
It has only one-third the sugar of soda.
Delicious. Thanks, Mom.
But little Olivia's career
may be over just as it begins
with today's announcement
that Tasty Juice
will be dropping her as
their spokesperson
and replacing her with a new ad campaign
featuring rock'n'roll legend Chuck Berry.
Open your mouth, baby. Here it comes.
But there is a silver lining
for local Quahogians,
as Miss Fuller will be appearing
at the Quahog mall this weekend
to mark the grand opening of the
new Brat Wraps Kids Clothing store.
Oh, that's perfect.
Brian, we have to go down there
this weekend and heckle her roundly.
I'll humiliate her worse than
Luke Skywalker did to that Rebel pilot.
The exhaust shaft is only
two meters wide,
so you'll have to use proton torpedoes.
That's impossible. Even for a computer.
It's not impossible. I used to bull's-eye
wamprats in my T-16 back home.
They're not much bigger than two meters.
Hey, uh, can-can I talk to
you privately for a second?
Sure.
Th-that, that, uh, that
was, that was unnecessary.
What's the problem?
Well, you just kind of called me
out in front of everybody back there...
- I was just making a point.
- I know, I know, but you like just...
- kind of sandbagged me.
- I sandbagged you?
In front of all of our friends, yeah,
- you sandbagged me.
- I sandbagged you.
You sandbagged me, yes.
Well, here I am trying
to help you with something...
You know what, I don't need
your kind of help, all right?
Have a great assault. Jerk.
Lois, I don't understand why
I got to sit through a chick flick.
Peter, you promised you'd come
with me to see Autumn's Piano.
Besides, you owe me big after the way
you embarrassed me in front of Sandra Oh.
Oh, my God, Sandra Oh.
We loved you in Sideways.
Thank you.
We see you in many movies.
I think about you while
having sex with my wife.
I thank you with one dollar.
That's a lot of money to them.
Lois, I'm just warning you,
if this movie turns me gay, I'm going
to start bringing gay guys home.
And I don't mean the classy "maybe
they are, maybe they're not" gay guys.
I mean those big, "Oh, my God,"
"here they come, floatin' around,
making noise" gay guys,
not the "fix up your house" gay guys.
Peter, shh, it's starting.
- You must be Autumn Daniels.
- Welcome to Barncliffe school for girls.
We're your roommates: I'm Sassy,
that's Pouty, and this is Suicidy.
I got a bad feeling about Suicidy.
Ain't no mountain high enough.
Yeah! You can tell all the girls
care about each other,
'cause they have so much
fun cleaning the dishes.
I have to leave,
and I'm taking my piano with me.
No...! Why?
Why? She chose the piano
over her insulin.
You could've had both.
See? That wasn't so bad.
Oh, you know, Lois, this movie has
helped me understand a lot of things.
Like that foreign guy at work
who helped me understand sarcasm.
- Huh, nice day we're having.
- Oh, ho-ho! Yes!
- What?
- He say "Nice day,"
- but he covered with rain.
- So?
So, he say this when your brain
know is not really nice day.
Oh, yeah!
Yes. He say the opposite. He's funny.
Oh, yeah, I get it. "Nice day. "
Now you funny, too. Oh...
There she is, Brian.
Oh, boy, I am going to take her
down right in front of everybody.
All right, Olivia, get ready to...
- Good Lord.
- What is it?
Brian, she looks... she looks fantastic.
And now TV's Olivia Fuller
will cut the ceremonial ribbon.
I hope I'm allowed to do this.
My mommy says, "Don't run with scissors. "
She's so cute.
I love children. Look at my kids.
So everyone feel free to browse
and purchase from our fine selection.
Hey, Mom, now would be a good
time to raise my allowance.
Oh, this one's kind of nice.
Wha...?
Olivia! Hey...!
Stewie? Oh, my God.
Wow, this is... it's been a while.
Yeah, no, it has.
Uh, what, so you back in town?
Yeah, we're, um,
we're moving back into the old house.
Oh, that's... God, you look great,
I mean, you're all, you're all in shape.
My God, California's been good to you.
I mean, I guess, I guess
you should be looking good
'cause everybody's a health
nut out there, right?
Yeah.
Well, anyway, it was
nice seeing you again, so...
Hey, listen, maybe you want to come over
on Friday, it's my "Bernie Mac" night.
Um, i-it's a fun show
if you haven't seen it.
I can't understand what
the devil he's saying, but you know,
there's a lot of movement, and it's bright
and colorful, it keeps my attention.
Look, Stewie, you're sweet,
but since I moved to Hollywood,
I've done a lot of growing up.
I'm dating more sophisticated men now.
But it was good to see you.
- What happened?
- She shot me down, Brian.
What do you care? You came here to gloat
about her contract cancellation anyway.
Yes, but that was before
I got a look at her face. I mean,
she's a woman now, Brian.
So sophisticated, so grown up,
and she says she wants a grown-up man.
But...
- apparently, that's not me.
- Ya think so?
Who could forget that one?
Hi, I'm the Mayor of Comedy
here to tell you about a new CD offer:
Sitcom Punch Lines of the '80s.
Including such gems as:
and...
Also...
Plus...
And...
Order now and receive
Sounds of the '80s Studio Audience,
which includes...
As well as...
And of course...
This is an offer you don't want to miss.
But don't take my word for it.
Hear what '80s mainstay Howard
Hesseman has to say about it.
I love it.
Would Howard Hesseman lie for weed?
We don't think so. Order now.
There we go.
You are ready for your date.
Yeah, that's a bed head.
Yeah, hey, look at you,
you just got out of bed.
You're the underachiever every
woman wants to sleep with.
- Hey, big date tonight?
- Uh, yeah, yeah.
Hey, listen, I'm, uh,
sorry about Olivia rejecting you.
Oh, I haven't given up yet, Brian.
She says she wants a more
mature, grown-up man,
so all I've got to do is be more grown-up.
- What are you doing?
- Just cleanin' out your brush, man.
Hi, Jillian.
Hi, Brian, ready to go?
- Hey, baby.
- Hi, Stewie.
What the hell are you doing?
Eh, not much, really.
Just me and my pubes,
ha... ngin' out.
Oh, dear God.
Boy, I am so beat from doing
adult stuff all day.
So am I.
I, just kind of feel like
kickin' it tonight.
Oh, look at that.
I'm growing all the time.
Hey, uh, Jillian,
can you give me a minute?
You ever just let your balls
hang out, B-Ri?
You ever do that, B-Roney?
Drove my Chevy to the levee,
but the levee was Bri?
- Give me my hair back.
- Ow! What the hell, man.
Stewie, this is not going
to convince Olivia
that you're grown-up enough for her.
- Yeah, what do you know about women?
- You want to know how to get women?
There's only one place
in town you need to observe.
Just watch.
I am not doing that, Glenn.
Come on, beautiful, keep an open mind.
- You're a sick man.
- Hey, keep it down.
I don't want my neighbors seeing
a fat, old, dirty whore
screaming at me on my front lawn.
Whore?
- Well, maybe I should come inside.
- Well, maybe you should.
What the deuce?
Why the hell would she respond
positively to such a negative comment?
Unless...
Brian, do women like it
when you treat them like crap?
Well, I don't know if you want
to be that black and white about it.
That's it, isn't it? Women respond
when you treat them like crap.
Well, Olivia, prepare to meet
a much darker Stewie Griffin.
Hey, babe. What do you say,
we going out Saturday night?
Stewie, what are you doing here?
I told you, I'm just into a
different type of guy.
Oh, yeah? I'll tell you what
you're into. Being ugly.
Stewie, you're being mean.
No. If I was being mean, when you
opened the door I would have said,
"Oh, hey, Ray Liotta, is Olivia home?
Oh, wait, you're Olivia. "
You see, I thought you were
Ray Liotta because your skin
has the texture of a decorative
autumn squash.
So, I'll pick you up at 7:00?
That sounds wonderful.
She said yes.
My God, I'm cooler than that
cheetah from the commercials.
Oh, God, there is no
drummer better than Neil Peart!
It ain't easy bein' cheesy.
Oh, Smilla, your sense of snow
is equaled only by your sense of love.
Peter, have you been up all night
watching chick movies?
Lois, before I found these movies,
women only made me cry through my penis.
Now they make me cry through my eyes.
I've decided.
I'm making my own chick flick.
What? You don't know anything
about making movies.
Are you kidding? I got lots of
experience in the film industry.
I was the original "Pretty Woman. "
You look beautiful,
but there's something missing.
This is a beautiful spot, Stewie.
I know. I love coming here because you
can just sit here and people-watch,
you know?
Oh, oh, look at this. Look at this guy.
Look at this. What is that?
What is he doing?
Just standing there smelling his hand?
"What is that? What is that on my hand?"
"Is that... is that barbecue sauce?
When was I near barbecue sauce?"
Oh, look, look!
Jewish cowboy! Jewish cowboy!
Yeah. Not gonna be so tough
when the sun goes down, are you?
Better go rassle up some
Chinese food, Hopalong Nussbaum.
You know, Stewie, I'm really glad
I gave you another chance.
You're a really special guy.
I know.
No, no, I'm kidding. I'm not really that
self-centered, but, you know, Olivia,
I can't think of anyplace I'd rather be
than right here right now with you.
Oh, look at this guy. Now,
there's someone who cuts his own hair.
Yeah, no kidding. Oh, my God.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, check out this
uptight Asian guy, look at that.
I work really hard, 'cause I'm no fun.
Boy, this is a great city.
I don't care what anybody says.
I know.
Look at that sunset against the skyline.
- I know. Wow, look at that.
- A perfect end to a perfect day.
Yeah. Well, we should probably get home.
This area gets really dangerous at night.
Okay, everyone, welcome to the first
day of shooting for Steel Vaginas.
Peter, this movie doesn't seem
to make any sense.
It makes perfect sense, Lois. This the
scene where our heroine, Vageena Hertz,
is told by Dr. McNugget here
that she has uncurable chick cancer.
All right, Joe, let's lose
the wheelchair and shoot this thing.
Peter, I can't lose the wheelchair.
I need it to move.
Okay, yeah, but your character can walk.
Peter, I'm handicapped.
I can't walk.
Okay, Chris, roll film.
And... action!
Joe, get out of the damn chair.
Chris, get the cattle prod.
Okay, now give him some peanut butter
so we can make it look like he's talking.
God, I hate these things.
Sweetie, can't you just have a good time?
I don't know anybody.
These are all your friends.
Just relax. Have some cake or something.
Hey, hey, who do we have here?
- Oh, my God! Victor?
- Hey, kiddo, how are you?
Great! Great! Wow!
Stewie, this is Victor. We did a
Flintstones vitamins commercial together.
Ten million strong and growing!
Oh, yeah, good to meet you.
How are you?
Victor's such a good actor.
He played a dead baby on CSI: Miami.
Yeah, I'm more into writing now.
Oh, hang on a sec.
Uh, idea for a short story:
guy picks his nose, then eats it.
Yeah, good luck with that. Hey, Olivia,
why don't you and I go get some punch?
Oh, actually, would you mind getting
some for Victor and me while we catch up?
Or-or a third option.
Why doesn't Victor go get some
punch for you and me?
Or maybe you and I could go away
from Victor and go get the punch?
Or-or none of us could have punch.
But still Victor could go away.
Victor, would you excuse us for a second?
Uh, sure.
Idea for a novel:
guy loses his favorite blankie, goes
looking for it and finds it in the kitchen.
Is that... I amaze myself.
Is that... It's genius.
It's unbelievable.
I don't know where I get it from.
What the hell is wrong with you?
You're acting like a jerk.
Oh, I'm acting like a jerk?
What about Phony Curtis over there?
He happens to be a very intelligent,
successful actor.
And, you know, he's done
three national diaper commercials.
Yeah, let's put a diaper on his face.
That's where the crap is coming out.
You don't own me.
I can talk to whoever I want.
I don't see a ring on my finger.
I, Stewie, take you, Olivia,
to be my lawfully wedded wife.
Uh, what's that, Rupert?
Oh, oh, kiss the bride. Yes.
- Hi, honey! I'm home!
- Hi, sweetie, how was your day?
Well, I was an astronaut
for a while, then I was a cowboy,
and then all afternoon I was a fireman,
so it's been, uh... it's been a long one.
- Uh, what's for dinner?
- Playdoh spaghetti.
- Oh.
- What?
No. No, it's nothing.
Just had Playdoh spaghetti last night.
- And that's all we had last night.
- What does that mean?
Oh, I don't know, Olivia.
Maybe that we are in a sexless marriage.
We have yet to have sex.
Do you even know what sex is?
That's not the poi... Don't change the...
It's a kind of cake?
Look, can we just drop this
and have a normal pretend dinner?
Fine, fine!
Uch, some days I think it was easier
being Q-Bert's roommate.
God, it's all night with this guy.
If you're gonna leave all those lights on,
I'm not gonna split the electric bill.
Sorry we're late, everyone, but JonBenet
here took forever with her makeup.
Uh, yes, and we probably would've
shaved a few minutes off our trip,
but Mr. Cheapo here refused
to let the valet touch his Big Wheel,
so we had to drive around the block
six times till we could find a spot.
But to his credit, it is a great spot
to get mugged.
Wouldn't that be a shame, if they took
all my money out of both our wallets.
Well, it's just good to have
you guys here.
Can I get you folks something to drink?
- Uh, yes, I'll just have flat water.
- Um, do you have Hi-C Tropical Punch?
And it begins...
What? I can't have a drink with dinner?
So dinner started at 2:00
this afternoon, did it?
Yes, about the same time you
decided to hole up in the bathroom
- for three hours waxing your eyebrows.
- You swore you would never...
I have a prominent brow,
and I do what I can to get by.
Well, hey, what's important
is that you're here now.
- Let's just enjoy dinner.
- Yeah, can't we just have a good time?
Ask Olivia.
Olivia, the three of us are having
a great time. What's your problem?
My problem is you.
You're acting like a baby.
And we come to the center of
the shrubbery maze.
That's what it all comes down to, isn't it?
I'm not grown up enough for you.
- Well, you are a baby, aren't you?
- Stay out of it. Stay out of it.
Well, if you think I'm a baby,
then perhaps I should act like a baby.
Hey, could you keep that kid quiet?
Oh, oh, oh, what's that?
What's that, sir? What's that?
I'm sorry, am I being too loud for you?
You wanna come over here
and quiet me down?
- Oh, let's do this.
- Oh, God. Stewie, come on.
- I'm scared.
- No, it's okay. It's okay.
Sir? You feel strong?
You wanna come over here?
No, I want to stay here
and have my steak.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah.
- What is that, the porterhouse?
- How is it?
- What do you care?
If we weren't fighting,
would you recommend it?
Yeah, I would.
Well, I know what I'm getting.
Hello, everyone.
Well, here we are... opening night.
You know, somebody once told me
that making movies was easy.
Yeah. Yeah, you know what else is easy?
Open heart surgery.
- Oh-ho-ho! Yes!
- Yeah, thanks for coming, Fuad.
Oh! Is funny because open
heart surgery not easy at all.
Yeah, yeah. Calm down, Fuad.
So, without further dudes, ah,
let's, uh, watch this thing.
At first I didn't believe
in women and unicorns,
but that was before I knew
about the power of chick stuff,
and before I knew Vageena Hertz.
Sorry.
When Vageena was first born,
I had a small heart and a lot to learn.
Push, honey!
Hurry up and give me my baby boy!
Cleveland, more SpaghettiO's.
Oh, good, a baby. Oh, no, it's a girl.
And I hate girls.
But one day, Vageena went swimming
too soon after eating a sandwich...
and this happened.
Help! Help! I'm drowning!
Help!
We gotta get this woman to surgery time.
Right stat now!
But it was too late.
And she died from an angry hymen.
Fin.
Wow, that was the worst piece
of crap I ever seen.
Oh, my God, that was an abomination.
- That was awful. Awful. Awful, awful.
- My ass is actually sore.
My ass is actually sore.
- Hey, where's Olivia?
- Oh, she's probably up at the house.
- Stewie?
- Yeah?
- It's not your fault.
- What?
- I know.
No, Stewie, Stewie. It's not your fault.
Don't do this to me, man. Not you, man.
- It's not your fault.
- Screw you! Cut it out, man.
- Why is it so hard?
I didn't know it was gonna be so hard.
Look, Stewie, you stood up
before God and all your toys
and you took an oath to stick it out
when things got tough.
You want her to see you as an adult?
Well, this is adulthood.
You're right, Brian.
I can't hide from this relationship.
It's my responsability to deal with it.
I mean, what kind of a man
would I be If I ran off now?
Well, you'd be a black man.
- Whoa, what was that?
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
That was my father talking.
You, uh...
you gotta work on that, man.
Bad dog.
Sweetie, listen, I'm sorry, I...
Oh, Stewie! I thought you were
at Chuck E. Cheese's with your mom.
No. A four-year-old died in the ball pit.
We had to cancel.
Is that the Silly Putty
I bought you this weekend?
Stewie, this isn't what it looks like.
Uh-uh, yeah, Stewie,
I just dropped by to...
Uh, uh, uh, ain't nobody talking to you.
Is... that... the Silly Putty...
I bought you...
this weekend?
You know, I'm really sensing something here...
I should be go.
No, about you stay here and I leave
and never come back again?
Stewie, this isn't how I wanted
it to end.
But you did want it to end.
You've made that perfectly clear.
- Listen, are you gonna be all right?
- Yeah, I'll be fine.
Is that smoke?
Idea for a farce: cheating wife
and pompous ass burned alive.
So what happened?
Well, you wanna know what I learned
this week? Being a grown-up sucks.
Women, Brian. What a royal
pain in the ass. It's like, it's like,
why can't you just hang out
with guys, you know?
Just live with someone of your own sex.
Just do what you would do with women,
but with your buddy, you know,
why don't guys just do that?
They do, it's called being gay.
Oh, that's what gay is?
Yeah, I could totally get into that.