Translated By The Community Of WWW.MY-SUBS.COM
- Ow, damn it!
- Peter, are you all right?
No, no, I think you should call somebody.
- Ma'am, are you all right?
- I can't...
breathe.
Oh, God, I think she punctured a lung.
Damn it, look at my foot.
It's already starting to swell up.
God, I'm looking forward to this week.
Freaking swelled foot all week.
You know, we should... You should
probably go ahead and shut that off.
Synchronisation: Kemar
Transcript: Raceman
Oh, hey, Quagmire, how was Florida?
Oh, it was great.
And guess what? I smuggled a whole
bunch of fireworks back in my anus.
Uh, Quagmire,
fireworks aren't illegal here.
You could have just put them in your car
and driven them up here.
Yeah, that's just as fun.
All right, Meg.
You be David Koresh
and I'll be a heavy-handed FBI agent.
Go!
Hey, you.
You're a crazy person.
Come out of there, you.
Quagmire, check it out.
I took ten M-80s and stuck 'em all
together.
I call it Peter Griffin's bunker-busting
mega-ultra-super...
Holy crap!
Oh, my God!
You blew off all your fingers!
What happened?
Oh, my God!
You know, no huge hurry, but
I'm sort of out of juice over here.
Bone-dry.
There's one of Dad's fingers.
We have to hurry! I learned in Biology
if you get them back soon enough,
they can be reattached.
What's all the commotion?
Hey, there's one of 'em.
Peter, look out!
Go on, Jesse.
Make your peeps and poops.
That's gonna feel good for Jesse.
Damn it.
Maybe if we make it mad,
it'll come down here
and we can catch it and get the finger.
Hey, bird.
Your poop is white and green.
You're the laughingstock
of the poop world.
Ah, yeah, ah, yeah,
I knew that would get you.
Ah, ah, come here.
You little son of a bitch, come here!
Hey, stop, stop it, stop pecking me!
Ah, thanks, Joe.
Let's plant a knife on him just
to be safe.
Eh... good thinking.
Yeah, I know how these things go down.
Uh, hey there. We were supposed
to have brunch this morning.
Oh, yeah, sorry.
I- I had a late night.
Late night, huh?
- What's her name, Brian?
- What are you talking about?
Oh, spare me the theatrics.
I see the signs.
The excuses for why we can't hang out,
the inside-out collar.
If I didn't recognize
what was going on here,
I'd have to be as dim as those retirees
I entertain every Thursday.
There's a hole in the bottom of the sea
There's a hole, there's a hole
Whoa-ho-ho, all right.
We're getting a little faster here now.
And you know what?
I think there's something else down there
in the bottom of the sea.
Something that
you'll be able to relate to.
There's a tube in the throat
of the elderly man
In the hospital bed on the frog
on the log
In the hole in the bottom of the sea
There's a tube in the throat
of the elderly man
In the hospital bed on the frog
on the log
In the hole in the bottom of the sea
There's a hole, there's a hole
There's a hole in the bottom of the sea
Oh, whoa, what is this?
There's a birthday cake for Mr. Cohen
on the frog
On the log in the hole
in the bottom of the sea
There's a birthday cake for
Mr. Cohen in the hole
In the bottom of the sea
Get a nurse.
There's a hole, there's a hole
There's a hole in the bottom of the sea
Look, Brian, I think it's wonderful
you've found a young lady
willing to stoop to your level.
- When do I get to meet her?
- No, no, no way.
Oh... I see.
I get it, she's hideous.
She is not hideous.
Oh, well, let me ask you something.
Does she have an alibi?
For what? Why would she need an alibi?
So you're saying she does not
have an alibi?
Well, no.
Okay, so we've established
she ain't got no alibi.
She ugly, she ugly!
U- G-L-Y!
She ain't got no alibi!
She ugly!
Screw off.
M, she's major ugly!
O, she's fat and pugly!
O, my God, no.
The cow says "moo. "
Here's to Peter getting his fingers back.
Thanks, Joe.
Oh, boy, I tell you,
I haven't felt this good
since I came up with that new place
to hide my porn.
Have a good day, sweetie.
Hey, Greg.
Afternoon, Mr. Griffin.
Mrs. Griffin out today?
- Shoppin'.
- Ah.
Ah, she's hot.
All right, last call, fellas.
It's closing time.
Aw, crap, I'm not even half-buzzed.
Hey, what do you guys say
we take this party on the road?
Fine by me.
Skinemax doesn't kick in with the
really dirty stuff till about 3:00 anyway.
They had one on last night
where the girl had a buttface
but her breasts was immaculate.
Peter, you sure it's okay
to beat the brewery after hours?
Relax, Joe, this is where I work.
Besides, it sure beats the hell out
of last Saturday
when we partied with that big-horned guy
from Legend.
Hey, you guys want to go to IHOP?
Get some breakfast or something?
Oh, God, I don't know, Big-Horned Guy.
It's like 3:00 a. m.
Oh, that sucks, man, I'm wide awake.
Hey, Quagmire, you want to...
Oh, my God, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, man. Are you okay?
- No!
- I didn't see him.
Okay, okay, guys, here's one.
If you were God,
who would you strike down first?
Debra Messing. I find her insufferable.
French Stewart.
What are you squinting about?
It's not even that bright.
Yeah, he's terrible.
What we need out there now
is another Tim Daly.
- Who's Tim Daly?
- I don't even know who that is.
- From Wings?
- Nope.
Tim Daly. He was on Wings.
What, no-nobody here watched Wings?
Is that the one where there's a guy and
he's like, uh, he's a pilot or something?
There's two guys.
They're brothers and they're both pilots.
And wasn't there a fat guy
with a moustache?
That was Roy. He's hilarious.
- Was this a cartoon?
- No, my, oh, my god, no!
No, no, it took place in an airport.
Th-Th-The thing was on for ten years.
And the, and the funny repair guy
was Lowell.
It made Tony Shalhoub's career.
- Who?
- The tennis player?
God, you know what? Screw you guys.
I don't even know you.
Crazy people.
Living under a rock, don't know Wings.
I love Wings!
All right, I want to be very clear
about this.
You can meet her, chat for a minute,
and that's it. In and out.
Oh, don't worry, Brian.
If she's as ugly as I think she is,
I'll look at her once and then I'll go...
...all over the place.
Then you'll wipe it up and then we'll go.
Hi, Brian.
Oh, my God.
Who's your cute little friend?
Oh, my.
Hello. Stewie. Charmed.
I'm Jillian. Come on in.
Who wants a drink?
So, you gonna take back what you said?
Brian, she's stunning.
Okay, you met her, you can scram now.
I shall do no such thing.
Now, why in the world would you be
embarrassed about dating her?
Oh, my God, Brian.
I was watching something on TV
about this guy named Hitler.
Somebody should stop him.
Are her parents brother and sister?
Can you please leave now?
Oh... now I get it. She's a moron.
But a moron with large breasts
you can use as mountains
for your Matchbox cars, or whatever
it is grown-ups do with large breasts.
Shut up, that's not it at all.
Say, Jillian, I love what you've done
with the place.
What is it? One bedroom, one bath?
No, it's a whole apartment.
Oh, God, outstanding.
So, Stewie. Do you work with Brian
at the detective agency?
Why, yes, as a matter of fact, I do.
At the detective agency.
That's got to be a tough job.
I know Brian's work has him coming
and going at all hours of the night.
I bet it does, I bet it does.
Okay, well, Stewie has to go now.
What are you talking about? I want some
more of Jillian's delicious lemonade.
I know, it's good, right?
I just wish they didn't have to kill
so many lemons to make it.
Oh, this is fun, eh?
So, wait, Dupree moves in with
Kate Hudson and Matt Dillon?
But they're newlyweds, right?
Well, that's no time to have
a houseguest.
Oh, gotta go.
Sorry, Angela. Every Tuesday morning,
I call my friend Cleveland
and he describes every scene from
You, Me, and Dupree.
Griffin, your workout put this week
is even worse than usual.
Where the hell are those purchase orders?
Eh, it's this bum hand.
I can't type with it.
Well, that's not my problem.
I need to see some improvement
by the end of the week
or you're finished.
Don't worry, I'll figure something out.
Oh, that's going to be Quagmire
with Along Came Polly.
I gotta take that.
All right, so as you know by this point
in the story,
Ben Stiller doesn't like spicy food.
Well, guess what's for dinner?
No way.
Boy, Lois, thanks so much for coming in
and helping me get my work done.
Without you, Angela would have been
all over my case.
Oh, it's all right, Peter.
I know it's tough for you to work
with your hand injury.
Hey, you know, uh,
with you sitting there, it's, uh,
it's kind of like you're my secretary.
Let's not get carried away, Peter.
Now, please, I'm trying to finish
your work.
You know, Lois, if I'm your boss,
I gotta look like a boss.
Finally, I have a reason to wear
this big bow tie and cigar
I bought at the Dress For Success store.
Peter, if you want this work
to get done...
Lois, take a letter.
"Dear Life Cereal,"
"Where do you get off?"
"Part of a balanced breakfast
and delicious?"
"Who do you think you are?"
"By now, you may have guessed
I'm speaking ironically"
"and have nothing but good things
to say about what you do. "
"Life Cereal, do not change a thing. "
"Signed, Peter Griffin.
Dictated but not read. "
Lois, read that back to me.
Oh, hey, Brian. Back from a hot booty
call with your idiot girlfriend?
You know, think what you want, but you
don't see the side of Jillian that I do.
Face it, Brian, she's dumber than a
Boston-area book report.
The novel I chose to address
is Oliver Twist
by Charles Dickens.
Queer name, right?
The book was actually not bad.
For your information,
Jillian is very bright
and she happens to be a
very talented photographer.
Oh, that is so lame.
Every hot girl who can aim a camera
thinks she's a photographer.
Ooh, you took a black and white picture
of a lawn chair
and its shadow and developed it at Sav-On.
You must be so brooding and deep.
- Knock it off.
- No, I want to know, Brian.
What, specifically, do you talk about?
Uh, a lot of things.
Um...
food,
um...
the new seat covers
she just got for her Jetta.
Um...
- Real World / Road Rules Challenge.
- You hate MTV.
Pot helps.
Look, you know, I don't have to justify
anything to you, all right?
All that matters is Jillian and I have
a great time together.
- We make each other laugh.
- Fine.
But just tell me this, Brian:
does she laugh on her own
or does she laugh only when you laugh?
I thought so.
Hey.
Yeah.
Uh-huh...
uh-huh.
Uh, you gotta hit, uh, DVD and then menu
and then select.
Yeah.
Yeah, the DVD needs to be face up
when you put it in.
Uh-huh.
You should be able to see
the words Mr. 3000.
Yeah...
still nothing?
Is it plugged in?
Okay, so plug it in.
Okay.
Y- You got it?
Is it... uh, okay. All right.
No, no problem. All right.
Uh, love you, too, Jilly bean.
Okay.
- What?
- Nothing. I didn't say anything.
I need a drink.
Uh, hey, uh, Jilly bean?
Hey, it's Brian again.
Uh, so, yeah, um...
so I figured we could get together
tonight and maybe, um,
do all those things sexually
that we usually do.
Um, what were those again?
No way, gross!
Oh, I mean, I mean, oh, oh, no.
Yeah, I totally love how that feels.
Hi.
You know, I've been noticing you
around the steno pool.
You look good enough for a promotion.
Peter, cut it out.
Hey, that's no way to talk to your boss.
Mmm, is that Pert?
You know it is.
Smell my Speed Stick?
Peter, what the hell are you doing?
Lois, I'm gonna come right out with it.
I think it would be so hot for you and
me to have sex in my office.
Oh, my God.
There is no way that is gonna happen.
You know, it's no wonder
you're so far behind in your work
if this is how you behave at the office.
Come on, just touch it. Touch yours.
Peter, no. I have work to do
so you can keep your job.
Oh, look at me, I'm Lois.
I'm a worker. I make stuff on things.
Oh, I'll file these later.
Oh, I got a phone. Nope, that's it.
Geez, Lois, I thought having you here
was gonna be fun,
but so far you're a bigger buzzkill
than Buzz Killington.
Oh, man, this is the best party
I've ever been to.
Evening, everyone.
I thought it would be very droll if
we all sat down and looked at etchings.
Would you like to join me, Peter?
Uh, well, we-we're kinda partying here.
Good! Hold this up.
Now here's a fellow attempting
to ride a bicycle.
But he's having some trouble, isn't he?
Would you like to know why?
Why?
Because he's a Scot!
Now, who here likes a good story
about a bridge?
What the hell? Jillian, what...
- What are you doing here?
- Oh, hi, Brian.
It was so nice of you to invite
your girlfriend over for dinner.
- I invited her for dinner?
- Yes, you did.
You wanted her to meet the family.
Now, come here, Brian.
Come sit by your friend, Stewie.
And then, think about this:
have you ever seen the sun and the moon
in the same place at the same time?
They're the same person!
- I know, right?!
- You're brilliant!
Hey, Oogie!
So tell us, Oogie,
where'd you find this one, huh?
You two meet at a Mensa meeting?
No, at a Quizno's.
We both ordered the
Turkey Ranchand Swiss, no onions.
Can you believe that?
No, wow.
What are the odds?
Well, hey, what are the odds of
finding true love anywhere in the world
says this observer.
Hey, you wanna know something cool?
I threw up a lot in high school,
so I don't get my period anymore.
Wow, this is the one you've been
waiting for, huh, Brian?
Are you serious?
Are you serious, Brian?
All right, you know what,
Lois, don't judge.
Because you don't know what two people
are like when they're alone.
Come on. Let's go out dancing.
I don't know, I'm feeling kinda
cozy tonight. Kinda mellow.
I just really want to go dancing...
Oh!
There it is again!
What is that?
So, Jillian, what are your views
regarding homeland security?
Do you think we should support
what the president is doing?
Well, I just think, for starters,
that sometimes the government has things
they can't tell us
and, truthishly, we should just
accept that.
Okay, goodnight, everyone.
Oh, say, Jillian, before you go.
I forget.
Do you know what the capital
of this state is?
Um... Rhode Island City?
It's like she's five!
Thanks for hanging out with my friends,
Brian.
Hey, come on.
We're-we're a legitimate couple, right?
I- I should be able to talk
with your friends.
So then the valet pulls up and I'm all,
"That is so not my car. "
But then it totally was.
- That's happened to me!
- Me, too.
Cars go fast.
Oh, God.
Yeah, I tell ya, if I had a nickel for
every time that happened.
- Yeah...?
- What?
What if you had a nickel
for every time that happened?
No, nothing. It's just an expression.
A what?
Well, I was just saying
I do my share of dopey stuff.
Like, oh, this... this one time
I attended a speaker's colloquium
on federal judgeships
and without realizing it,
I kept calling William Rehnquist
"William Rhinequist. "
Come on.
I mean, how... "doi. "
Anyone else have to go to
the littlegirls' room?
I have new gloss!
- I love gloss!
- Oh, that rocks!
Gloss rhymes with hair!
Dude, that was painful.
What are you doing here?
Did you follow us?
Brian, why can't you just admit
what's going on here?
Okay, okay. Fine. Fine.
I'm gonna have to break it off.
But, boy, it's gonna be tougher than
the reviews for Our American Cousin.
Blah, blah, blah, "Lincoln assassinated,"
blah, blah, blah,
"tragedy for our Republic. "
Uh... oh, look!
"Ably performed by the entire ensemble. "
That's us! That's all of us!
Morning, Lois, I need you to
proof read this and collate it for me.
Peter, did you Xerox your penis?
300 times. It's a flip book.
Flip through it or you're fired.
Oh, my God! This is disgusting.
Peter, for the last time, I'm not
having sex with you in this office.
Why the hell are you pushing
this so hard?
Because, Lois, I already wrote the letter
to "Penthouse Forum,"
and I don't wanna be made a liar
in the nudie magazine of record.
All right.
If I give you 30 seconds of making out,
will that shut you up?
Let's see where it goes.
Oh, God, you know this is pretty hot.
Yeah, what'd I tell you, huh?
Oh, God, Peter, let's do it.
Let's do it right here, right now!
Lois, Lois wait. Wait.
Opie's right there.
I want him to look, Peter.
Well, that is the last of it.
You are now all caught up with your work.
Lois, I really appreciate you helping
me out this week,
and I really appreciate
you having sex with me in my office.
Well, that was my pleasure, too, Peter.
Haa, I knew I'd get you.
Just like Danny DeVito got Rhea Perlman.
I don't know, Danny.
Look, it's either me or nobody.
Sold.
All right, Brian, you can do this.
You can dump her.
Because once it's done,
never again will you have to listen
to her talk like this?
You know, where everything has
a question mark at the end of it?
With an upward inflection?
At the end of every sentence?
Yeah, I don't know what I was thinking?
Oh, damn it. Now I'm doing it, too.
Oh, hey, Oogie.
Ooh, you look tense.
Well, uh, Jillian, there's...
something we need to talk about.
What is it?
I, uh...
just wanted to spend some time with you.
What the hell? It took you three hours
to break up with her?
Uh, not exactly.
Well, what were you doing in there?
What's that smell? It smells like
sweat and anger and shame.
Yep.
Life's confusing when you grow up,
isn't it, Brian?
It is.
- Can we play my mix tape?
- Yeah, go ahead.
Brian had sex with a really dumb girl
Now he's taking his friend Stewie
To get some ice cream in his car...
Oh, you're a poor sport.