Translated By The Community Of WWW.MY-SUBS.COM
We now return to Sunday Golf on CBS.
And Mickelson here, trying to save par.
And there's Mickelson's wife.
God, is she hot.
Look at that rack.
There's a downhill lie for you.
Oh, and they're just out there,
begging to be touched. Pleading.
How many golf balls do you think
she can fit in her mouth?
I'd hit that one in the rough,
if you know what I'm saying.
Who are you kidding, Greg?
You'd **** her for a week,
and then get tired her.
Yeah, you're right. That's what I do.
That's my thing.
- But a hell of a week though.
- Hell of a week.
Oh, my God! The power's out!
What are we gonna do now?
Well, we could light
some candles and read.
- Yeah, right.
- Yeah, that would be great
Yeah. Read the inside of my butt.
We could tell stories.
Hey, Dad, why don't you tell
the story about when I was born?
Yeah, we got halfway home
with the afterbirth
before we had to go back to the hospital
and swap it out for Meg.
The end.
Now, I got a better one.
This is a story of love and loss,
fathers and sons,
and a foresight to retain
international merchandising rights.
This is the story
of Star Wars.
Let's begin with part four.
Family Guy
Blue Harvet
www.forom.com
Synchronisation : Kemar
Transcript : Raceman
You hear that?
Sounds like we're being boarded
from the rear.
And not the, "Hey, take a deep breath,
let's experiment"
kind of boarded from the rear.
Beep boop.
Could you hold on to this bag?
What if they come in a different door?
Damn! I was two days from retirement.
R-2?
Help me, Obi-Wan Kenobi.
You're my only hope.
- All right, now what do I click?
- Click "preferences."
- Okay, I clicked preferences.
- Now go to "default media browser".
Okay, there's a little hourglass,
and it's not letting me do anything.
- It says "buffering." What is that?
- Just give it a minute.
All I'm trying to do is make an mpeg.
All I'm trying to do
is tell you to wait a minute.
Okay, relax.
Now click "import video file."
All right.
It's telling me I have
to download RealPlayer 7.
You know what?
I'll just bring it to him myself.
There she is!
Do you still got that bag I gave you?
It's gonna be a long ride.
Hold your fire.
There's no life-forms aboard.
"Hold your fire"?
What, are we paying by the laser now?
You don't do the budget, Terry. I do.
Hey, I'm gonna do some crosswords, but...
- that doesn't mean I don't want to talk.
- Oh, yeah, yeah.
My God! Look at this mess!
"Hey, Darth Vader's gonna be here.
Should we maybe clean the place up?"
"Nah. It's okay. He won't mind."
Well, well! Princess Leia.
Are you prepared to tell me what you've
done with the stolen Death Star plans?
All right, Lord Vader. You win.
I've hidden the plans
in one of these 26 briefcases.
Ooh! Ooh! Okay, okay!
Uh... uh... I'm feeling number 14!
Let's go with number 14!
Oh, it's okay.
I'm just happy to be on TV.
All right. Take her away.
Okay, here's another one.
Who would you rather do :
Jabba the Hutt right after a shower
or a service droid?
My father was a service droid!
Hey, where ya going?
You can kiss the lower part of the back
of the canister that is my body.
Oh, man! This looks like
the wrong neighborhood.
Oh, boy.
It's okay, R-2. Calm down. Be cool.
I ain't done nothing
to antagonize nobody.
What? A droid can't walk down
the desert no more?
I got rights, too.
Who's there?!
Any attack made by the rebels against
this station would be a useless gesture
no matter what technical data
they've obtained.
This station is now
the ultimate power in the universe.
That is fantastic. Terrific work.
- So, no weaknesses at all, huh?
- Nuh...
No.
You, uh... you hesitated there.
Is there something I should know?
No. It's virtually indestructible.
Like, 99.9%.
Uh... okay.
Wouldn't be doing my job
if I didn't ask. What's the .01?
Well, I... I mean,
there's this little hole...
It was kind of an aesthetic choice
by the architect.
And, if you shoot
a laser into this hole...
the station blows up.
That sounds like
a pretty big design flaw there.
No, no, no.
The hole's only two meters across.
Well, that's no bigger
than a womprat.
Exactly.
And even to get within range of it,
you have to skim along this whole trench.
It's not a big deal.
Can't we board it up? Or, you know,
put some plywood over it or something?
Well, that would look terrible.
I mean, we gotta think about resale.
Resale? What are you talking about?
This property is right above Sunset.
The value is only gonna go up.
Lord Vader, your inside references
to the Los Angeles real estate market
haven't given you the clairvoyance to
turn a profit on that condo in Glendale,
nor has it...
I find your lack of faith disturbing.
That property is in a prime location.
20 minutes to the beach,
20 minutes to downtown...
There's nothing to do downtown.
Enough of this!
Vader, release him!
As you wish.
All right, so we gonna plug up that hole?
Yeah. We can get it done tomorrow
if price is no object.
- We'll get estimates.
- Get estimates. Yeah.
Someone was in the pod.
The tracks go off in this direction.
- Look, sir. Droids!
- Look! A penny!
Hey, thanks for the sex,
early '90s printer.
All right, bring 'em on out.
Oh, God, it's a hundred degrees out here!
If I pass out, please note
that I'm wearing a Life Call bracelet
with all my insurance information.
Luke?
Luke!
What?!
Tell Uncle Owen not to tell you
that your father is Darth Vader.
Aunt Beru, when are you guys
gonna let me join
the rebellion like all my friends?
Oh, pff! Stop whining, Luke,
and come have some blue milk.
One of these days,
I'm just gonna take off and join the
rebellion whether you like it or not!
Over my burned carcass!
Hey, shut up with-a da nois-a!
Hey, shut-up-a with-a da shut-up-a!
You shut-up-a with-a da shut- up-a!
Shut-up-a yo face!
Now-a my dog-a won't-a shut-up-a!
- Why you no-a shut up-a?
- I make-a you-a shut-up-a!
- You two-a shut-up-a!
- Hey, I poke out-a my head!
Someday
I'll get off this rock
and fight the empire.
John Williams and the
London Symphony Orchestra, everybody!
Now do the theme to The People's Court.
Oh, this oil bath is going
to feel so good.
Hey, you guys think that '90s printer
looked clean, right?
Hey, there's something stuck
in this R-2 unit.
Help me, Obi-Wan Kenobi.
You're my only hope.
Whoever she is,
she sounds like she's in trouble.
Is there any more to this message?
Intergalactic proton-powered
electrical-tentacled advertising droids!
Hi, I'm Darth Harrington of
Darth Harrington's Intergalactic Proton-
Powered Electrical-Tentacled Advertising
Droids Emporium and Moon Base.
Due to a garbled sup-space transmission,
I am currently overstocked
on all intergalactic proton-
powered electrical-tentacled
advertising droids,
and I am passing the savings on to you!
She said, "Obi-Wan Kenobi."
I wonder if she means
old Obi-Wan Kenobi.
Well, I guess I'll go bull's-eye
some womprats in my T-16.
My God, you shoot small animals for fun?
That's the first indicator
of a serial killer, you freak.
There's two suns and no women!
What the hell am I supposed to do?!
Master Luke, he's gone, he's gone!
What?
R-2, he took off in the middle
of the night! We got to find him!
Oh, what the phantom menace
is that guy's problem?
Hey, mind if I turn on the radio?
WTAT, Tatooine's all-talk radio.
My good friends, the liberal galactic
media is at it again. They never stop.
Now they're trying to convince us
that Hoth is melting.
Well, that's crazy.
Just trying to scare us.
And if that weren't enough
to get you mad,
we now have news that Lando Calrissian
has been made the chief administrator
of the Bespin Mining Facility.
Gee, I wonder how he got that job.
Well, let me tell you
how he got that job.
Affirmative action strikes again.
The time is 8:50.
- R-2, what are you doing out here?
- Beep-boop-beep.
He says, "There are several creatures
approaching from the southeast."
That's not what I said.
I said there ain't a pack
of menthols on this planet.
Well, I see some Bantha tracks,
but I don't see any...
Wait a minute. There's Sand People,
all right. I can see one of them now.
Who the hell are you?
One lucky sumbitch.
So, Luke, what brings
your muscley arms out this way?
I'll show you, Mr. Obi-Wan.
R-2, play him the message.
General Kenobi, many years ago,
you served my father in the Clone Wars.
We need your help again.
And not to get too personal, but...
you owe us after that mess
you got into back on Alderaan.
...and we pay to keep the families
of those children quiet, so...
Oh, this is just...
just like logistical stuff.
I'll check that later.
...Joey Lawrence haircut,
so I'll assume we can count on your help
to get the Death Star plans
to my father on Alderaan.
The plans are stored inside this R-2 unit.
Help me, Obi-Wan Kenobi.
You're my only hope.
All right now, what do I click?
Luke, you must learn the ways of
the Force and come with meto Alderaan.
What's the Force?
The Force is what gives
a Jedi knight his power.
It surrounds us. It penetrates us.
Here, check this out.
Wow! This is cool!
Yeah, everyone in
the neighborhood has one.
Hey, why would you hang that up?
It looks so tantalizing.
You know, the Empire's gonna come
looking for these droids.
But if they find out who the Jewas sold
them to, that could lead them back...
home.
Luke, wait! It's too dangerous!
Get your fat space ass back here.
Uncle Owen?
Aunt Beru?
Oh, my God!
John Williams!
Great, now we got to do the rest
of this thing with Danny Elfman.
Mos Eisley Space Port.
You will never find a more
wretched hive of scum and villainy.
My sister Regina D2 lives here.
- Is she single?
- She's a lezbot.
- He doesn't like you.
- Sorry.
- I don't like you either.
- You don't even know me.
You know what? That's fair.
I'm Pignose and this is
my brother-in-law Scott.
- He's visiting from Hoth.
- I don't know why they call it Hoth.
- They should call it "Coldth."
- Okay, settle down.
I'm up after the band.
Thank you. We're the Cantina Band.
If you have any requests, shout them out.
Play that same song.
All right, same song. Here we go.
Hi. My sexy friend and I
are looking for a ship
to take us to Alderaan,
and I'm willing to pay big money.
Well, you've come to the right place.
I'm Han Solo, captain
of the Millennium Falcon
and the only actor whose career
isn't destroyed by this movie.
- Is it a fast ship?
- Are you kidding?
It's the ship that made the Kessel Run
in less than 12 parsecs.
Um...
Isn't a parsec a unit of distance,
not time?
No, no, no, no.
Chewie, take these guys
to the ship and get her ready.
Always gargle before a takeoff.
Waka-waka. All right, let's go.
Greedo, as a matter of fact, I was
just going to see Jaba and tell him...
- Well, what do you think?
- What a piece of junk.
Thank you. This was my brother's. He
died of leukemia. How do you feel now?
You got any strawberry milkin there?
No, but she'll make .5 past lightspeed.
If you want, I'll show you around
since no one's trying
to stop the ship or blast us.
Stop that ship! Blast them!
Oh, now I can't show you around.
Quick, get in the ship.
Looks like we got
Imperial cruisers on our tail.
Oh, look at that one on the left.
Get off your cell phone. You are driving.
They're gaining on us!
We'll be safe enough once
we make the jump to hyperspace.
Besides, I know a few maneuvers.
We'll lose them.
Uh, that, thatwas your maneuver,
moving slightly to the left?
Well, I mean, we're not in
the same place we were, huh?
- That ought to confuse them.
- Yeah, but you hardly did anything.
You just started listinglazily
to the left.
I'm pretty sure they can keep up.
- Where did they go?!
- There they are.
They're listinglazily to the left.
Go left! Left!
Boy, this guy knows some maneuvers.
All right, strap yourselves in.
I'm about to make the jump to lightspeed.
Did he say "strap in" or "strap on"?
Man, hyperspace always looks so freaky.
Governor Tarkin,
I recognized your foul stench
as soon as I was brought on board.
Um, actually, that's me.
I made a Darth doody.
Princess Leia, we've chosen to test
our Death Star planet blower-upper gun
on your home planet of Alderaan.
No!
She said, "No."
Should we still do it?
Yeah.
So anyway, I says,
"Forget the dental plan."
"Forget sick leave.
I just want a railing," you know?
"One railing right here."
Yeah, I know. I've almost
fallen over that thing so many times.
- So what did they say?
- Oh, get this.
They said they're worried
we'd be leaning all day.
- They said that?
- Yeah.
Well, none of this will matter
when we're famous singers.
- How am I doing?
- Just keep your knees bent.
Imagine you're spreading butter
on a big piece of bread.
That's it.
Spread that butter...
with the Force.
Ha! You guys seem like
crazy morons to me.
You don't believe in the Force, do you?
Oh, you mean that thing
you just found out about, like,
three hours ago and are now
judging me for not believing in it?
Do you believe in anything?
Uh, yeah. Didn't you see
my Kabbalah bracelet?
- What's Kabbalah?
- About a buck seventy-five.
Honestly, I have no idea.
I'm just a slave to trends.
What the hell?
Oh, my God, we came out of hyperspace
into an asteroid field.
Alderaan's been destroyed by the Empire.
Maybe we should head for that small moon
that's clearly a small moon
and not anything else.
That's no moon.
It's a space station.
Oh, crap, that got us in a tractor beam.
Well, they're not gonna get me
without a fight.
You can't win.
But there are alternatives to fighting.
Like what?
Like getting the hell out of here!
No, just kidding.
Can you imagine if I was like that?
All right, just follow my lead
and act real cool.
All right, I'm gonna go knock out
that tractor beam.
And we'll go rescue the princess.
You know Luke, this may be the last time
we see each other.
So there's something I want you to know.
Now I've
had the time of my life
And I owe it all to you...
I've been waiting for so long
Now I've finally found someone
to stand by me
So we take each other's hand
Cause we seem to understand the urgency
Just remember
You're the one thing
I can't get enough of
So I'll tell you something
This could be love
Because
I've had the time of my life
No I never felt this way before
Yes, I swear, it's the truth
And I owe it all to you...
Holly smoke!
So, whate **** we are
on the first floor?
Uh, we are on the second floor.
No, no, no, **** here's the
Banana republic and we just pass that.
Uh...
... it's right back there.
We, we, uh...
we park on Macy's side, ****
So now we must be other here
by the JCPenney.
It looks that the first floor
is mostly main stuff, ****
and there's a lady Foot Locker
right other there. ****
All right, so we are on the third floor.
All right, let's get in the elevator.
And hurry up, 'cause the smell of
that Mrs. Fields is killing me.
Where are you taking this... thing?
Prisoner transfer from cell block 1138.
You think you could get me
a room by the pool?
Is funny because you are prisoner.
And there is no pool
because is Death Star.
We got to find out what cell
this princess of yours is in.
- There it is, 2187.
- I'm on it.
Uh, everything's under control here.
Situation normal.
What happened?
We, uh, had a slight weapons
malfunction, but
everything's perfectly all right.
We're fine.
We're all fine... here... now...
thank you.
How are you?
Uh... I've been better.
- Well, tell me what's up.
- Well,
I'm in this relationship and
it doesn't seem to be going anywhere.
I like her, but...
we're not really connecting.
- How long's it been?
- About ten months.
- And how often do you see each other?
- Couple of times a week.
Well, why don't you try seeing
each other a little more often
and see if you connect a little more.
And if not, it may be time to move on.
Thanks for calling.
This is Han Solo,
and I'm going to be keeping you
company for the next few hours,
right here on the midnight shift.
Something's telling me it might be you...
It's telling me it might be you...
Aren't you a little fat
to be a storm trooper?
Well, stay here and rot,
you stuck-up bitch.
Wait. Who are you?
I'm Luke Skywalker.
Me and Han Solo and Obi-Wan
are here to rescue you.
- Wait, Obi-Wan Kenobi?
- Yeah.
Suddenly I'm not so fat, huh?
Come on, into the garbage chute.
She's right. Come on, Chewbacca.
Are you kidding? It's probably full
of disease. I'm not jumping in there.
Not even if I throw this pig's ear?
- Oh, come on, that's not fair.
- Go get it!
Oh, boy, great idea, Princess,
diving into a pile of garbage.
When we get out of here,
maybe you can show me around
your home planet of Alderaan.
Aw...!
Too soon?
Hey, it could be worse.
It's worse.
The walls are closing!
Listen to them, R-2. They're dying.
What do we do?
Only one thing to do, man.
You still got that bag I gave you?
Man, I wish I could listen to some
Tattooine, Wind and Fire right now.
Mm...
So you think
the Empire's gonna fall, man?
I-I-I don't...I don't know, man.
H-How you, how you, how you,
how you doing right now?
Good. Why?
I think,
I think, I think I... I think I may be
having sort of... a mini freak-out here.
- Oh.
- Just-Just...
Just tell me I don't have
to stay in this room.
What?
Just tell me right now that I...
that I don't have to stay in this room.
You don't have to stay in this room.
Oh, thank God.
Thank God we're saved.
Look at this.
Who throws out half a pizza?
And look at this couch.
Somebody threw out a whole couch
and it's in great shape.
Yeah, you put a little Febreze on that,
scrub it out a little bit,
it'll look great in your apartment.
You know what?
I know we have a dangerous job
to do here, but
I'm taking this.
I'm taking this couch.
All right, you ready?
All right, one... two... three.
- Easy, easy, easy.
- Okay.
- Stop, stop, stop, stop...
- What? What...?
- No, no, no, no... Twist it.
- I am.
No, no, no, no, no, other way.
You're twisting the wrong way.
- What do you want me to do?
- Just look down, all right.
Just look at me, look what I'm doing.
- You see the way I'm twisting it?
- Yeah.
- Turn it that way from your end.
- Okay.
No, no, no, no, no.
Put it down. Put it down. Just drop it.
All right. All right.
All right, let's...
Just hang on and figure this out.
Han, there are storm troopers
all over the place.
Shouldn't we be getting out of here?
All right, okay, all right, okay.
I got it, I know... okay, okay...
Here's what we're gonna do.
We're gonna take the cushions off,
unscrew the legs,
take the mattress out and this
whole thing is gonna be a lot simpler.
It's easier than we're making it.
Hey, did you hear something?
Probably just another drill.
You know that last drill we had?
I was about to finally
bone my girlfriend,
and then we heard
that there was this drill
and she told me there was no way.
So, Obi-Wan...
we meet again.
What part of "stay 50 yards away
at all times" don't you understand?
Uh-oh.
Your powers are weak, old man.
Obi-Wan!
Boy, you got here just in time.
No...!
All right, go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
All right, twist it counter-clockwise.
I am twisting it.
You're twisting it the other way.
I mean counter-clockwise
from where I'm standing
so... so th... so then you...
so clockwise.
You twist it clockwise.
Okay... okay, go.
You know what? Put it down,
put it down for a second.
- My fingers are killing me.
- Han, they're shooting at us!
You know what? Lift it up tall ways.
Aw, for cr...
oh, it's wedged. It's wedged.
You know what? It's not going anywhere.
Let's just take off,
we'll deal with it later.
You get in the cockpit and I'll just...
I'll hang on to this thing as we go.
Easy.
I can't believe he's gone.
I know, Luke, but it's true.
He's gone.
I mean, you saw him get beheaded.
Nobody lives through that...
Not for long, anyway.
I mean, sometimes the brain
is still active for a few minutes
after the beheading, but...
to be honest, I can't imagine
a worse kind of hell.
And unfortunately,
hell is probably where he'll end up,
because the Christians don't look
too kindly on the whole Force thing.
Come on, kid,
we're not out of the woods yet.
Here they come!
- Hey, Han!
- What?!
- Why do they call them "Tie Fighters"?
- - No idea!
They're coming too fast!
Oh, boy. Nickel for every time
that's happened.
Just keep shooting, Luke!
That's how we do it
in my neighborhood, bitch!
I got him! I got him!
Great, kid! Don't get penis-y!
I just want to tell you both...
Good luck.
We're all counting on you.
Mom?
Yeah. Yeah we won.
Yeah, we won the battle.
Yeah, I'm calling like you asked.
Okay.
Okay, but...
okay, but I gotta go...
I got other stuff to do.
O-Okay
Okay, okay, but I gotta go.
Okay.
Okay, yes.
Yes.
Yes, yes, Mom.
I-I love you too, Mom.
Okay, all right, good-bye.
P-choo. P-choo.
Gotcha.
Thanks to the information in this
R-2 unit provided by Princess Leia,
we should be able to mount a
successful offensive on the Death Star.
But first,
please take a moment to watch
this instructional video.
Nothing but net.
Hi,
I'm Magic Johnson with a few tips
on blowing up the Death Star.
First off, never forget your objective.
There gonna be so many folks
coming at you to slow you down,
you might feel like you got
a bull's-eye on your head.
No, but they will be trying to kill you.
Also, don't forget you have teammates
out there watching your back.
Unless you been messing around
with their wife or girlfriend.
No, but they will be there to help you.
Lastly,
you wanna make sure you step back and
take cover after you sink that bucket,
'cause that sky gonna light up
like the Fourth of July.
No, but there will be a large explosion.
Well, kid, I guess this is good-bye.
So, you got your reward
and you're leaving. Is that it?
When you say it that way,
I sound like a douche,
but, yeah, that's what I'm doing.
What'd you get for a reward anyway?
Uh, let's see,
I got 10% off a Netflix membership,
uh...
some nice Cracker Barrel Cheddar,
assorted lotions, and a little plastic
champagne bottle full of jelly beans...
and a little bear.
See? Little bear?
"Hey, Luke. We had fun
on the Death Star."
Well, take care of yourself, Han.
I guess that's what you're best at.
Oh, look, a light saber cheese knife.
Yuck.
All wings. Check in.
- Red three standing by.
- Red six standing by.
- Red five standing by.
- Red Buttons standing by.
- Redd Foxx standin' by!
- Big Red standing by.
- Red October standing by.
- Helen Reddy standing by.
Simply Red standing by.
I'm going in. Cover me, Porkins!
Uh, having a little trouble here.
Careful, Redd Foxx,
there's one right on your tail!
Ahh! I'm comin', Elizabeth!
Use the Force, Luke.
- Obi-Wan?
- Yeah, it's me.
Use the Force.
Force that thing in there.
Just like I showed you
with those puppets.
but don't tell anybody
'cause you'll get in trouble.
Clark, I don't like the look
of this neighborhood.
Come on, Ellen,
it's important for the kids
to witness the plight of the rebellion.
Kids, you noticing all this plight?
Roll 'em up!
The Force is strong with this one.
**** you, you son of a bitch!
What am I, R2-Pac?!
The Death Star is getting closer.
And Leia's getting larger!
I have you now, young Skywalker!
And with today's gas prices,
not a minute too soon.
What the deuce?!
Look at this.
Look how much more comfortable
we are now shooting stuff.
Luke, the Force will be with you always.
And so will I.
Always.
'Course, when you get older
and get some crow's feet,
I might lose interest.
The end.
Well, Dad,
thanks for keeping us entertained.
That was a great story.
Yeah, but
didn't Robot Chicken already
do this three months ago?
Well, I wouldn't worry about it, Chris.
I don't think people are even aware
of that show's existence.
Well, I don't know, Dad. I think
a decent number of people watch it.
Oh really? Define "decent."
I think it's the highest-rated show
on Cartoon Network
and the Star Wars episode
doubled that audience.
Well, yeah, but double ten people
is like 20 people,
so, I mean, what kind of numbers
are we talking about here, you know?
Don't be glib about this stuff, Dad.
It's a legitimate show
and they beat you to the punch.
Uh... I don't know about that, Chris.
I mean, to me, a legitimate show
is on ABC, CBS, NBC...
You know, one of the real networks.
I don't know about that, Dad.
And besides, what's up
with that 15-minute runtime?
What is that? It's like 15 minutes
of guys playing with Star Wars dolls?
- Oh, yay, yay, tune me into that.
- Oh, so you do know the show.
I read part of a review online.
I am not a fan.
You know, Dad, you're a real jerk!
Synchronisation : Kemar
Transcript : Raceman
www.forom.com