WWW.MY-SUBS.COM
♪ It seems today that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those good
old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man
who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a... Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
- Synced & corrected by MementMori -
-- www.MY-SUBS.com --
Good afternoon, I'm Tom Tucker.
Coming up, we interview a man
who went a whole Hawaiian vacation
without giving a "hang
loose" sign in a picture,
and also didn't do the "lei" joke.
You won't believe this incredible story.
Oh, wait, he's a Japanese
man? Doesn't speak English.
So... so he just didn't know.
Happy birthday, Brian.
We bought you a cake with the groceries,
so it got smashed with a
jug of Tide in the car.
- Open your presents.
- Yeah.
You got one from Rami
Malek, star of Mr. Robot!
Wow, he gave me the dark
circles around his eyes.
Aw, cool! Did he also include
his dead-soul monotone?
No, I don't... Oh, oh, wait, hang on.
I didn't see it at first
because it was under some tissue paper.
- Now open mine.
- Minions 3?
Yeah. In this one, Gru has been
replaced by Harvey Weinstein.
Oh, you like working for bad guys?
I'll show you a bad guy.
Now you touch it.
You know what to touch.
B-Banana.
Well, thanks, everyone.
What's wrong? You seem a little down.
Nothing, it's just that...
I don't know, my-my birthday is just...
it's kind of a reminder that I'm
now one year closer to death,
with nothing to show for my time here.
Can I get a Minion cake
for my next birthday?
- We'll see, Peter.
- Like, a real one.
Like-like, not you makin' it.
Someday I'll be gone, and it'll
be like I was never here at all.
Aw, he is depressed.
Sad little guy.
Let's not project people
emotions onto animals.
I just want my story to live
on, even after I'm gone.
You know, I always did want
to write my autobiography.
Yeah, it's hard to work
when you get distracted
- whenever someone says, "What's that?"
- What's what?!
You know what? Maybe I
can lend a hand, Brian.
I'll help you write your biography.
Really? You-you'd do that?
Yes. After all, I helped
Cleveland with his wardrobe.
Hey, Cleveland, you know I love you,
but those jeans, they ain't for you.
I knew it. I think I
just needed to hear it.
Thank you, Peter's baby.
- Uh-uh.
- Copy that.
We now return to Allison Janney in
Hello, Sexy.
And, uh, to your left,
you'll see a joke about Allison Janney
being very, very tall.
Uh, she has an Oscar,
and we have a great deal
of respect for her.
- You know, I had a terrific...
- Uhp.
- No, sorry. You go.
- Okay.
I found a lump on my
scrotum this morning.
You done? Yeah?
I had a terrific
sandwich, uh, yesterday.
Boy, they are doing a lot
with mayo these days.
I have no doctor.
_
You know that UPS lady with
the super-bruised legs?
Well, one time...
What... Uh, what's going on?
Quagmire, are you okay?
Where's he going?
- Looks like Quagmire...
- I think he...
Boy, you and me today, huh?
He's, like, hypnotized. Do we wake him?
That could be perilous.
_
I was happy to see that
new massage parlor.
But deep down, I was disappointed that
we took a shot at Allison Janney,
just because she can dunk a basketball.
I mean, she has an Oscar,
and we have a great deal
of respect for her.
All right, Brian, time to get
to work on your biography.
Let's start with an interview.
Who would you say is your hero?
Well, I guess maybe Martin Luther King.
Okay, maybe someone you see every day.
Uh, well, I guess Peter is...
No, no, no. Li-Like somebody younger.
Li-Like younger than you, even.
Like that... Like that kind of hero.
Well, I guess Meg and Chris.
Let's take Meg and Chris as a given.
Anyone else you maybe look up to?
- I guess Lois...
- We did say younger, did we not?
Well, uh, I guess that leaves... you.
Oh, boy, embarrassing.
That backfired, didn't it?
So, I should put me, then?
Yes, fine.
Now, another important part
of any book: the dedication.
It's not uncommon for an
author to dedicate his book
to his hero, who you have listed as...
Oh, no, this is...
Oh, this is embarrassing.
_
We already did this. I
got some free time.
_
- Hey, guys, sorry I'm late.
- It's about time.
Thanks to you, we got leap-frogged
by Seamus' foursome.
Ha. Golf club hands.
Hey, could one of you
spot me the greens fees?
I blew all my money at
the massage parlor.
Sheesh, you're sure spending a
lot of money at that place.
How much you pay one of them masseuses?
Eh, 200 bucks.
200 bucks?! That's what I
paid for Reading Railroad!
What kinda medical benefits
do those masseuses get?
I think they see the Chinese
vet down the street.
Well, that's all the information I need
to make a binding vocational choice.
Guys, I'm gonna become a
professional massage therapist.
- What?!
- Are you serious, Peter?
You bet. I could always
use some extra cash.
Plus, I've handled bigger
challenges before.
You know, I was once
in the Blue Man Group.
Peter, what's wrong with your paint?
Remember when I asked
for a five-minute break?
Hey, Stewie, which title do
you like for the biography,
Barking Up the Right Tree...
Did you catch that?
Or, Are You There, Dog? It's Me, Brian?
Oh, about that, I was
meaning to tell you,
your biography is finished.
Already? Wow. Print me up a copy!
Done, Brian. Look behind you.
Whoa, ass ahoy.
- Classic.
- Stewie, this isn't a book.
Brian, it's 2019. We're
living in a post-book,
Post Raisin Bran society.
So enjoy your new robot,
and enjoy a bowl of Post Raisin Bran.
Post Raisin Bran: like
Kellogg's, but worse!
Stewie, what about my biography?
This robot is a living record
of you and your history.
It knows you and your mannerisms,
and it will exist long
after you're gone.
Brian, in every sense of the term,
Robot Brian is your biography.
This is how you'll be
remembered, forever.
Whoa, ass ahoy.
He says that a lot.
He's also got an
interchangeable memory bank,
an expandable encyclopedia
database, and, as a bonus,
the new U2 album.
Oh. I don't want the new U2 album.
You don't get a choice.
So this is a robot version of me?
Not just a robot "version,"
Brian, it's like another you,
uploaded with your genetic
code, your cognitive patterns,
and your entire life story.
"Oh, no, Stewie's time machine broke,
and now we are stuck
in the history past."
Well, that is one of my catchphrases.
I don't talk that robotically, though.
That'll go away. He will evolve
as he gathers more and more data.
"Fire hydrants, images."
"Fire hydrants, news."
"Fire hydrants, near me."
- Now what's he doing?
- Oh, he's also been uploaded
with your Internet search history.
"Yahoo Answers: Is Anton
Yelchin's jeep for sale?"
Ooh, shame on you, Brian.
It's legitimate memorabilia!
"Applebee's, Brittany, Quahog."
"Brittany, Applebee's waitress, blonde."
"Quahog, Applebee's, Brittany, who is."
"Blonde waitress, Brittany,
Quahog, Applebee's."
"Brittany Babbit, home address."
Oh, good, you found it.
Peter? What are you doing here?
I work here now.
You what? Why would they hire you?
I don't know that they did.
Nobody ever picks me, though.
Just Bruce. And his towel
keeps falling off,
and he keeps saying, "Oops."
I dunno, the towels here
are very fally-offy.
Dammit. Good-bye, Peter.
- Where you goin'?
- Home.
I can't come here anymore,
you've made it weird.
You have one that looks
like snowboarder Chloe Kim?
She turned 18, so I can
say that out loud now.
Robot Brian, it's so
great that you're here.
I need a partner for a project
I've been working on.
But, sir, Dogbook was our idea.
It was stolen by Bark Zuckerbark.
And who are you again?
We're the Barklevoss twins.
And... scene.
So, what do you think?
I think it's great. I have no notes.
It's called The Barkial Network.
How come you didn't call it Barkbook?
I thought you said you
didn't have any notes.
I got you dropped from jury duty.
Oh, great. What line did you use?
"I have read about this exact case... "
- That's good.
- "... on hotsy-totsy Nazi dot com."
That's not good.
- Hey, can robots do cocaine?
- What?
Nothing, I was just, you know.
Can they get cocaine?
Hello, The Girls Aren't the
Girls in the Ad Massage.
Oh, yes, the girls are
absolutely the girls in the ad.
Freeze! Police!
- What's going on?
- You're all under arrest.
- Arrest? For what?
- This place is a brothel.
- What does that mean?
- Your coworkers are engaged
in the world's oldest profession.
Lead singer of The Pretenders?
No, Peter. All these
women are prostitutes.
Cuff them, cop with a wife
who's taller than him.
Uh, my name's Gary.
I'm sorry, I'm bad with names,
but I'm good at remembering
gigantic wives.
So, what was Brittany Babbit like?
Oh, you know, at Applebee's,
she's all like,
"Hi, may I take your order?"
and at her bedroom window,
she's all like, "Ah, get out of here.
How'd you find my apartment?"
Tale of two Brittanys, huh?
Yeah, I mean, if you don't want
me showing up at your house,
don't put a smiley face on my receipt.
Uh, Your Honor, the defense rests.
See, you get it.
Have you read my book yet?
I'm downloading it right now.
It's beautiful.
- Mm...
Yeah, this is, this is fine.
This isn't, this isn't weird.
I'm a robot you. Mm.
Post Raisin Bran.
Proud sponsor of whatever
the hell's going on here.
- Good morning, Brian.
- Hey.
So, anything unusual happen
with Robot Brian last night?
Anything you'd like to share?
N-No. W-Why, why do you ask?
Well, as it happens, your robot
has a rear panel sensor.
Every time it's triggered, I get
a text, like a Google Alert.
I... This is ridiculous.
I don't even know what
you're talking about.
Mm-hmm. You know he backs up his
hard drive every night, right?
Though I guess you were also backing up
his hard drive last night, eh?
Wiping that history?
Ah, what else? What
other computer terms...
What, the... oh, getting some RAM?
A few megabytes?
Logging in and logging out... wow,
there's a lot of computer
things that sound dirty.
Okay, I admit it. I'm not made of stone.
I fell for me.
I know it seems strange, but
I'm gonna give it a chance.
And don't worry, we're not gonna
be one of those cutesy couples.
- Morning, RB.
- "RB?"
Yeah, it stands for "Real Brian".
Morning, RB. "Robot Brian."
Well, much like every other "RBs,"
you are making me sick.
Hey, did you get the license
plate of that handsome guy
who ran me over last night?
Ha, ha, clever.
So is there anything
we need to talk about?
I don't know. Is there anything
- I guess not.
- Well, I guess not, too.
- Thanks, RB.
- Back at you, RB.
We just click together.
Like all the pieces in
Chris's first model set.
Okay, lay out the pieces,
find the cockpit,
open the glue, take a sniff...
... and this will be my life now.
Joe, you got to help me.
My picture's in the
paper and everything.
_
Well, everybody knew
that Bob Iger thing,
but you got to help me, Joe.
No way. You should've thought
of that before you committed
a victimless crime between
consenting adults
in a commercial arrangement
which also created jobs
and contributed tax
dollars to the community.
Now if you'll excuse me,
I'm gonna go watch Bob Iger
drain threes at the local gym.
We've got to think of something
to make Joe drop the charges.
I don't know, he seemed
pretty insistent.
Trust me, Joe can be
pretty easily influenced.
- ♪ I get knocked down... ♪
- Oh, no!
- ♪ But I get up again ♪
- Yeah!
- ♪ You're never gonna keep me down ♪
- Good!
- ♪ I get knocked down ♪
- Oh, no!
- ♪ But I get up again ♪
- Yeah!
♪ You're never gonna keep me... ♪
Ah...
Sounds like that water's
pretty refreshing, huh?
- Excuse me?
- No, nothing, you just made a weird noise
after you took that sip of water.
RB, that's the sound you make
when you take a sip of water.
What? No way, that's so annoying.
I'd-I'd kill myself if
I sounded like that.
Brian, don't forget, I'm you.
Everything I do, I
literally got from you.
Well, not that.
I think I know how to
take a sip of water
without sounding like a
rock concert drum solo.
Go ahead. Show me.
Hmm? Mm-mm.
Mm-mm-mm-mm.
Ah...
Joe's police rounds bring
him down this street.
So the plan is, we trick
him into coming in
and getting an erotic massage.
Then we blackmail him into
dropping Peter's charges.
Right. And if someone makes
a joke about my weight,
I laugh good-naturedly and then
go home and eat my feelings.
O-Okay. That-that's part of the
plan you keep on the inside.
Yeah. Next to the pizza
you had for breakfast.
Here comes Joe. Places.
♪ La, la, la, la, unsuspecting song... ♪
Huh. "Miracle Leg Massage.
Walk Again, Joe."
I don't know. What's the
name of this place, anyway?
"Flip Joke Massage Parlor."
Well, tempted as I may be,
there is no way I'm going
in there for a massage.
Ma'am, I assume you're
giving me a great message,
but that's where it stops.
I'll be a monkey's uncle before
I accept a sexual favor.
And that's the story of how
your mother... my sister...
got into college.
Oh, Barnaby Bananas.
You're certainly my smartest nephew,
but Harvard is only for humans.
No monkey will ever graduate from there.
Barnaby Bananas.
I tell you, Janine, I sure feel
dumb for what I said earlier.
Congratulations, Janine. Also, Joe,
we got pictures of you getting
a sexual favor a while back,
so now you got to drop the charges.
This'll never stick, Peter.
I know a top-notch
Harvard-trained lawyer.
An M.A. in urban planning?
That's no help. All
right, Peter, you win.
- Really?
- Yup, I'm gonna drop all the charges.
And now maybe you could
drop a few LBs, huh?
- What?!
- What?
I do not laugh like that.
Again, Brian, I'm you.
I can't do it unless
you've already done it.
You can't do it unless
I've already done it?
What is this, Bark to the Future?
Oh, my God, I do do that.
Hey, Brian, I think I put
in a good day of writing.
Check out what I did.
- This is a blank screen.
- Exactly.
I spent all day working on the margins.
- The margins?
- Oh, yeah,
you got to get the margins right.
They frame the page.
They're like the corral, and
the words are my wild horses.
It's my job to break those word horses
and ride them off into the green
pastures of prose and poetry.
Stop! It's just so pretentious.
Well, they're your words.
No way. I would never say that.
Words are my wild horses.
It's my job to break those word horses
and ride them off into the green
pastures of prose and poetry.
Sir, all I said was your
Discover card was declined.
Turn it off, turn it off!
God, I'm such a jerk.
I hate you!
Which means... I hate me.
What did you just say?
I said I hate me. I hate myself.
You've made me realize I hate myself.
What the...
Well done, Brian, well done.
Stewie? What are you doing?
What the hell happened to RB?
- RB served his purpose.
- Which was what?
To show you that the last thing
you need is a detailed account
- of who you are and what you do.
- Excuse me?
Brian, you wanted to write
your autobiography.
And I needed to show you that no one
wants to read your
autobiography, not even you.
- Because...
- Because your best is middling,
your worst is intolerable,
and when you die,
the most you'll want written about you
is "He Was a Good Boy"
on your tombstone.
And even that will be a complete lie.
_
I couldn't do it. I couldn't lie.
We now return to The
Talking Talking Dead,
the show that talks about the show
that talks about The Walking Dead.
Okay, so what do we think about
what they thought about stuff?
It was awesome. Oh, my
God, it was so great
how they thought that
other show was so great.
Yeah, totally. And that
one part of the show
where the guy was talking about
that one part of the other show
and how he didn't see that coming?
I did not see that coming.
This is just too much to process.
I need an aftershow
after this aftershow,
just to know what I just saw about
what I just saw about what I just saw.
- Well done, Chris.
- Thank you.
And Brian, you certainly
had yourself an adventure.
I sure did.
Hey, whatever happened
to Robot Brian anyway?
He moved down to the marina.
I hear he's doing pretty well.
It's been like this all morning.
I'm actually starting to get
a little worried, you know?
It's not a bionic robot.
It can break.
What's that swoosh?
He's got a mouth sensor, too.
And remember, Brian, he wouldn't
do anything you wouldn't do.
He's you.
It's rather musical, isn't it?
Sounds like the "Carol of the Bells."
Uhp, I'm getting a call.
Oh, no, it's Allison Janney.
Decline, decline.
I tell you, Lois, being a
masseuse is a tough job.
But it all just goes
to show that basically
every licensed massage therapist
in this country is a prostitute.
Oh, yeah. You can pretty
much do whatever you want
with any masseuse ever, because
they're all prostitutes.
And it's not just the masseuses.
If you're ever seeing, like,
a physical therapist,
or doing yoga with a private instructor?
Just go for it.
There's, like, an 80%
chance you'll get there.
But Peter, there's, there's
one thing I still don't get.
Why did you take the massage
job in the first place?
For you, Lois. I did it
to earn enough money
to buy a comb for your beautiful hair.
Oh, Peter, didn't you know?
I sold my beautiful hair to buy
you a bottle of massage oil.
Great. So now I'm an unemployed
masseuse with a bald wife.
Merry [BLEEP] Christmas.
- Synced & corrected by MementMori -
-- www.MY-SUBS.com --