Translated by the community of WWW.MY-SUBS.COM
♪ It seems today that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those good
old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man
who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a... Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
Sync and corrections by btsix
www.MY-SUBS.com
Hey, Meg. What are you up to?
Not much. Just finished
an angel food cake.
Might go out to the trash, see
if there's any possums to kiss.
I was just out there.
Oh, come on, it's your senior year.
Somebody must be having
a party or something.
Well, there's one.
But... I wasn't invited.
Well, so what? Go crash it.
Nah. Not my style.
And what do you care? Do you
want the TV or something?
What? No, no. I want... I
want to see you have fun.
Come on, you should go, you
know? Let loose a little.
You know what? You're right.
Maybe I will give it a shot.
Yeah. How awkward could it be?
Can't be worse than waving at someone
who doesn't wave back at you.
- No, not you.
- Oh. Sorry.
In fact, everyone but you.
Hi, everyone but him!
Hi!
Lou, I like you a lot, but I-I
think that's the last tape
of you having sex with your
girlfriend I want to see.
Suit yourself.
All right, I got to get
over to my mom's wake.
Oh, right, yeah. Crap.
Ugh. Sorry again.
- Oof. Cancer.
- Car accident.
No, I know, I just, I'm...
saying it feels like
everyone's getting cancer.
You know, Bowie.
Time to get creepay...
Huh. Kid family.
What a scumbag.
Aw...
Because I'm working all day!
Oh, yeah? Well, here's what I
think of your stupid work!
Don't you do that!
Fiona, don't you...
Is that Principal Shepherd?
Wow, that looks like a
rocky relationship.
"Rocky relationship."
Ha-ha!
Oh, come on, Brian.
Don't comment or like it.
It's a hard lesson, but
one he has to learn.
All right, ladies, time to mingle.
Hey. You guys talking
Big Bang over here?
Big Bang Theory?
No? Any Bangers over here?
No?
Well, I've tried everything.
We just don't have anything
in common with these guys.
Maybe... we don't need
anything in common with them.
Meg, come on, don't go crazy.
Damn, that's hot!
That was just lucky.
Oh, yeah?
Wow! Meg's so good at
casually tossing bottles
over her shoulder so they land upright!
And that's very popular right now,
because we've run out
of things on Earth.
Meg, that was amazing!
What can I say? I'm full of surprises.
Like the end of The Usual Suspects.
He was gay the whole time!
Okay, they're obviously home.
You'd have to be dumb to
try to rob that place.
Oh, yes!
I hate the guy, but he's good.
Oh, my God.
What the... what the hell
is going on over there?
Did he...
Hello.
Hey, Stewie, it's me. You got a second?
Brian? Hang on.
Hey, keep it down, you screwballs.
Here, let me just go
somewhere a little quieter.
Oh, yeah, right. I'm the screwball.
You and friends say "screwball" a lot.
That's what happens when you
run with a screwy crowd.
- What's up with you?
- Stewie, I think...
I think Principal
Shepherd killed his wife.
What? What are you talking about?
I think I saw him getting
rid of her body.
And carrying a bag with
something heavy in it.
And... and there was red
liquid dripping from it.
Okay, I've got to see this for myself.
Don't do anything. I'm coming over.
Hey, listen, you-you don't think...
you don't think you could
snag a couple of rolls
of toilet paper, could you?
- Stewie?
- I'm here. I just wanted you
to have to sit with those
words for a minute.
Kids, dinner's ready!
"Dinner's ready."
Shut up.
Little of the old schnappster
ought to get me right.
'Ey... Chrissay!
Well, that's delightfully informal, Meg.
How the heck are ya?
So, what are you kids doing in school?
I got in trouble for saying
something "insensitive"
to trans kids.
- What'd you say?
- Well, a few them started
this a cappella group, and
they're all kind of chubby.
So I said, "You guys should call
yourselves the Trans Fats."
Meg, you'll sit next to me this evening.
But, Dad...
I'm sorry, Chris. You've
fallen out of favor.
Perhaps forever.
Oh, Stewie, thank God you're here.
There's a seagull in your hallway.
Listen, what are we gonna do
about this Principal Shepherd thing?
Look, all you know is that the
guy was carrying a wet bag.
It doesn't mean he killed his wife.
You're building this whole theory...
What is that noise?
It's a news alert.
"Fiona Shepherd, wife of James
Woods High School principal
John Shepherd, has been
reported missing."
Oh, my God, maybe he did do it.
You know, there are some
bad people in this world.
Hey, you don't got to tell me that.
I learned that in Fight Club.
All right, Stewie, what's the
first rule of Fight Club?
G-string underwear.
No. It's "don't talk about Fight Club."
Oh. Well, I really blew it.
Hey-o! What's up in this piece?
You're getting home late.
Yeah. We were hanging out
in the woods, and...
this one girl pushed another girl over
while she was peeing.
They fought, and then the cops came.
Meg, this is important.
Did she fall in the pee?
I can smell your breath.
You've been drinking, haven't you?
No! Geez, Mom, get off my back.
Peter, I think she's doing booze.
What should we do?
Lois, she's just being a teenager.
We don't know she's, like, for
sure, definitely been drinking.
I found this in her room.
My little girl's a drunk!
Oh, my God, where did we go wrong?
Meg, we need to talk.
What, Mom? But I know
what you're gonna say,
and I know how you're gonna say it.
- Oh, really?
- Yep.
I don't want you drinkin'
or your life's gonna
go down the crappah.
That's not bad.
I-I mean, I sound nothing like that,
but it's a fun character. Heh.
But this is serious.
Alcoholism runs in our family.
Hey, I'm just glad something
runs in this family.
I don't mean to...
I-I don't mean to laugh,
okay? But that was funny.
Mom, I'm just having fun.
I'm finally known as something
other than "the chubby girl
who put the lunch lady in a headlock."
And besides, Dad's the one
who pushed me into going to that party.
Oh, he did, did he?
Son of a bitch. What was that?
I don't know. Someone must've
messed something up.
Listen, you need to talk
to Meg about her drinking.
What? Why me?
Because you're the one who told her
to start going to these parties.
Okay, fine.
I guess it's just something
I got to deal with.
Like the flush of a high-powered toilet.
So, you plan on going
back at that banana, huh?
So the bastard killed his wife,
and then reported her missing.
I-I got to... I got to call the cops.
- Quahog Police.
- Joe, Joe, it's Brian.
Listen, I have to tell you something.
I-I'm pretty sure
Principal Shepherd killed his wife.
That's a serious accusation.
Do you have any proof?
I have something better than proof,
rank suspicion born out of
boredom and loneliness.
Sorry, that's just not
enough for us to go on.
You must be pretty tired from
thinking about all this.
- You ever get bags under your eyes?
- What?
I've been using this eye cream,
it's done wonders for me.
It's made by a company
called Rodan and Fields.
Have you heard of them, Brian?
- Yeah, I-I think, uh...
- Oh, they make terrific stuff.
In fact, I was such a fan,
I became a sales consultant
for the company.
Listen, Joe, I got to run.
I'm hosting a little
get-together tomorrow night,
If you want to stop by.
There's gonna be pizza
and soft drinks, then a man's
gonna talk about the whole line.
Can I go ahead and
confirm your attendance?
Well, that was no help.
What if I go over there and
try to find some evidence
- that he did it?
- All right, fine.
But you have to be careful.
Don't worry, he won't have any idea.
I'll be more discreet
than a guy standing by
himself in the ocean.
- Hey, are you peeing?
- No.
- Are you pooping?
- I'm just trying to enjoy the day.
Why don't you go bother that guy?
Summer's blown by, huh?
So, your mom says you've been drinking.
Yeah, like, a little bit, but...
but it's nothing you
have to worry about.
Look, I-I was young, too, you know.
I-I remember going to parties,
walking up with a six pack.
You're so excited to get there,
you start jogging a little.
Your friends are all there, and
they're so happy to see you,
they're practically cheering your name.
And then "Mony Mony" comes
on at just the right time.
And everyone's dancing,
and-and Laura Hallston's jugs
are just slamming into you.
You don't have a care in the world,
and if all of it came to an end
right then and there, so be it.
Well, you're my daughter,
and I don't want any of that for you.
Hey, you want to see where I was
sitting when you were born?
Yeah, I still think about Laura a lot.
You were already drinking
tonight, weren't you?
A little.
Well, I can't talk to a
drunk person if I'm sober.
Hey, Jerome, can I get a beer, please?
But now I'm starting to sober up,
so I'm gonna need one to
keep an even playing field.
All right, but it stays between us.
And what if they card you?
Don't worry. I got it covered.
Wow. That's really good.
Right?! Jerome, make it two!
All right, he's gone.
Now, if I give the word, you've
got to get out of there, okay?
Got it.
Oh, my God!
What? What is it?
He sleeps in a bunk bed!
Are you kidding me?! Who is this guy?!
Wait a second. Is that...?
Bri, I'm gonna put you down for a sec.
Stewie, no! Don't.
Stewie, get out of there!
Stewie! Stewie!
Got to get his attention.
Man, just short.
Oh, God.
Domino's.
Oh, good.
Medium pie, ten wings.
Is the blue cheese dressing in there?
Thanks a lot. Have a good one.
Mmm.
He got out! Ha, ha! Yes, Stewie!
Oh, crap.
Oh, my, that was close.
Stewie, he saw you! He saw
you leaving his apartment!
Oh. Well... so what?
He doesn't know what we're doing.
What? What is it?
Well, that's...
that's not good.
Dad? Dad, wake up!
- Huh? What happened?
- I don't know!
We must have stolen
this boat last night.
I-I have no idea where the hell we are!
Oh, no, my cell phone's dead!
I got a little bit of juice left,
so we can either A, call someone,
maybe they answer, maybe they can help,
or B, we can definitely switch faces.
Look at you! Look at me!
That's what this is!
Oh, we're gonna die.
Dad, what are we gonna do?
You think it's too early to tie
our shirts around our heads
to show we're going insane?
I mean it, Dad. This is serious.
I did pants instead.
Ugh! I don't feel so hot.
What is wrong with me?
Have you taken a break since
you started drinking?
Not until right now.
Do you feel like lying on the
couch, rubbing your eyes,
while listening to Lou
Reed's "Perfect Day"?
Yes!
Then I'll tell you what's wrong
with you. You got a hangover.
What can you do for a hangover?
Well, Meg, so I don't have to think
about my throbbing headache,
I try to think of something
else, like a riddle.
Like, how would you
describe Chris O'Donnell?
Huh. He's not tall or short.
And he's not fat or thin.
Well, he's not handsome or ugly.
And he's not young or old.
He's not loud or quiet.
Uh, he's not memorable,
but-but I know who he is.
Thanks, Dad!
I feel so much better.
But you know who doesn't?
Chris O'Donnell.
Bye, dildo.
Oh, no. Hard shoes on linoleum.
That's a principal!
Brian, a lot of people
live in this building,
and you can't tell it's a
principal just from a walk.
Excuse me? May I have
your attention, please?
Okay, that's probably a principal.
Hey. How are you today?
What can I do for you?
What do you want from me?
Listen, it's... it's-it's
not what you think.
Then what is it?
Well... I'm, um... I'm
actually doing a documentary
about some of the finest principals
in the country, and...
Ow! Continue.
"Finest principals in
the country" and...
Brian!
Stewie! Help me!
How did I get here?
Well, to answer that, you'd
have to go back a little while.
We're not doing that!
We found this in a Dumpster
behind Principal Shepherd's building.
That's it. That's-that's the bag!
I guarantee his wife's in there.
Ha! What's the matter,
rook? Too heavy for you?
I've actually been a cop for years.
I have tummy cancer.
Oh. Weird way to say that.
What the hell? Bu-But I saw...
Yeah, well, what is all this?
Principal Shepherd,
I think you've got
some explaining to do.
Look, I tried to tell you,
I didn't kill my wife.
She just texted me today
that she's moved out
and she's banging my cousin,
Pat Sajak's accountant, by the way.
It's a weird time to name drop.
And the food, well,
I've been stealing it
from the high school to make ends meet.
My life's "kinda brute,"
as the kids say.
Sounds like you've had a rough day.
No wonder you've got those
bags under your eyes.
Have you ever heard of a company
called Rodan and Fields?
Ugh. Are all hangovers this bad?
Yup, that's the deal you
make with the gods of fun.
Every 72 hours, you lose a day.
Dad, you're so sunburnt.
I can't move because it hurts too bad.
Ugh. This is awful.
We don't even know if
anyone's looking for us.
Look, don't worry. We're gonna be okay.
This is why you shouldn't drink.
Booze is nothing but trouble,
and you don't need it.
You got a good brain in your head.
Thanks, Dad, and if this is what
drinking makes you feel like,
you don't have to worry about it.
I am done with booze.
Aw, I'm glad to hear that.
And I'm sorry I pushed it on you.
I just... I just wanted to watch TV.
I don't want to see you
waste opportunities
'cause you were out partying.
That's what I did.
You just worry about being you.
Don't worry, Dad.
I'll never be anything like you.
That's my girl.
Dad, look!
Oh, my God. Meg, we're saved!
Thank God you found us.
We're so glad you picked us up...
- Chris O'Donnell?
- That's right.
And I hope you like turbulence, dildos.
The actual Chris O'Donnell
is not a Coast Guard helicopter pilot.
We assume he's probably too short.
Oh, my God. Brian, are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Annie, are you okay?
So, Annie, are you okay?
Are you okay, Annie?
What happened to her?
She was hit by, uh...
She was struck by a smooth criminal.
That was fun, Mom.
We don't get to do a lot of
that kind of stuff together.
Listen, Brian, we want
you to come home again.
Oh, so the Twitter pariah
is finally welcome home?
No, but the school board hero dog is.
It was all over the papers.
You saved the school $206 from
all the food they recovered
from Principal Shepherd's fridge.
So... you really want me to come home?
They're still gonna serve that food?
Of course we do.
Hey, where's everyone else?
Oh, my God. Peter, what happened?
What happened? A fair question.
And to answer it, we
have to go back a ways.
- Stop doing that thing!
- Aw.
Brian, I got to say, it's great
to have you home again, buddy.
Well, it's great to be here.
Living on my own was fun,
but I couldn't stop thinking
about all the stuff
I was missing being away from you guys.
Did you ever finish that banana, Brian?
And, Meg, I hope you learned
your lesson about drinking.
Yeah, I think I'd rather
live my life as a loser
than feel bad once in a while.
Well, I hope you know
that you're our loser.
Thanks, Mom.
If my life were better here,
would I stop searching
for it... up there?
Sync and corrections by btsix
www.MY-SUBS.com