Translated By The Community Of WWW.MY-SUBS.COM
Family Guy - Episode S06E10
Peter's Two Dads
Synchronisation : Kemar
Transcript : Raceman
Um, Mom, Dad, um,
I decided I want a big party
this year with all my friends.
And maybe a band. Is that cool?
- Yeah, sure...
- Yeah, sure. Why not?
Oh, thanks, guys! You're the best!
What's she talking about?
A party for what?
I don't know. She have her period
or something? She getting married?
No. If she was getting married,
we probably would've seen
a guy around, right?
- Sound reasoning.
- You guys,
it's Meg's birthday next week.
Oh, my God, it is!
Peter, we got to put together a party!
Ah, man, I hate kids' birthday parties.
This is gonna be worse than that time
I was stuck behind Robert Loggia
at the airport.
- May I have your name, please?
- Robert Loggia.
- Can you spell that for me?
- Certainly. That's Robert Loggia.
"R" as in Robert Loggia,
"O" as in "Oh, my God,
it's Robert Loggia,"
"B" as in "By God, that's Robert Loggia,"
"E" as in everybody loves Robert Loggia,
"R" as in Robert Loggia,
"T" as in "Tim, look over there,
it's Robert Loggia,"
space,
"L" as in "Look, it's Robert Loggia..."
- Here you are, Brian.
- What's this?
It's an invitation to Meg's party.
I'm the party planner.
You have to RSVP.
You can do it right now if you want.
All right, fine,
I'll come to Meg's party.
No, you have to call the RSVP line.
- You got to be kidding me.
- I'm waiting.
Ring, ring.
Aren't you gonna pick it up?
No, I'm not gonna pick it up
on the first few rings. I'm busy.
Maybe I'm in the other room.
Ring, ring.
- Ring... Oh, come on!
- Hello!
- Stewie?
- No, this is Stewie's housekeeper,
Mrs. Pennyapple. I'll see if he's in.
Stewie! Stewie!
- Yes, Mrs. Pennyapple?
- You've got a telephone call.
- Who is it?
- He didn't say.
- Well, find out, would you?
- Who is this?
- It's Brian.
- It's Brian!
Oh, Brian. Probably RSVPing
about Megan's party.
- Hello, Brian.
- Hi, Stewie.
- What can I do for you?
- I'm coming to Meg's party.
Oh, splendid. Just give your
information to Mrs. Pennyapple.
Hello, it's Mrs. Pennyapple again.
Shall I put you down for two, Brendan?
- Brian.
- Ryan?
- Brian!
- Mitchell?
- What?
- Good-bye.
Hey, Lois, I'm ordering a birthday cake,
and the guy wants to know how old
Meg is. I didn't know what to tell him.
- You're asking me?
- Yeah. How old is Meg?
- I don't know.
- Well, my God, Lois,
I thought you were the one
keeping track of that.
No, no. I have no idea.
Don't you remember me faking
my way through her last birthday?
You are hmm-hmm.
Going on hmm-hmm.
Fellas will fall in line...
Should we...
Should we just ask her how old she is?
That, uh...
that'd be kind of awkward, huh?
Hey, maybe we should just cut off
her leg and count the rings.
Yeah. Or maybe try carbon dating.
I don't know what that is.
You know, we're gonna have
to talk to her
and kind of steer the conversation
in a way that gets her to spill it.
Come in.
- Hi, sweetie.
- Hey, Meg.
So, Meg, your birthday's coming up, huh?
You excited about turning...
Uh, Meg,
I got 16 candles for your birthday cake.
- How does that sound?
- That's not right.
So... less...?
More...?
Too many...?
- Not enough?
- You stupid son of a bitch!
You didn't even know how old I am!
Meg, that kind of language is not
appropriate for a girl your age.
- Or is it?
- I'm gonna be 17, you jerks!
She's the jerk.
All right, come on in, everybody.
Have a seat anywhere.
Meg's gonna open her
presents in a little bit.
Oh, Francis,
I'm glad you could make it.
Here! This for Megan!
- Oh. What is it?
- It's a cookie
- from lunch period at the home!
- Well, I'm sure she'll love this.
I want to see her eat it!
So the man asks the bartender
to recommend a good drink.
The bartender says, "A Grasshopper."
So the guy orders a Grasshopper.
Then he's walking home
and along the way,
he notices a grasshopper on the ground.
So he says to the grasshopper : "Hey,
you know there's a drink
named after you?"
The grasshopper says :
"You mean there's a drink named Irving?"
So which one of you wants
to lose your virginity?
Mom, this party sucks!
I mean, balloons? Pin the tail on
the donkey? I'm not five years old.
Meg, your father worked very
hard to put this party together.
He says he's got a big surprise for you.
Hey, kids, I'm Peepants,
the inebriated hobo clown.
I'm an adorable tramp who wears found
clothing and eats out of your garbage can.
A clown?! Dad, I'm 17!
Meg, guess what Peepants
got you for your birthday.
- A scarf.
- I don't want a scarf, Dad.
Well, then how about...
a dozen scarves?!
Peter, I don't think you're actually
supposed to swallow those.
- Here you go, Meg.
- I don't want them!
Take them!
Are my long john stied
to the end of those?
- No.
- Oh, God.
Mom, can I just open my presents now?
- All right, Meg.
- Thank you.
- What the...?
- Let's see what else we've got here.
The first season of
Sister, Sister on DVD?
You're welcome.
Stewie, what are you doing?!
You can't open Meg's gifts!
These are mine, you hear me?
Mine!
Oh, God, not the "mine" phase.
I've been dreading this day.
I'm entitled to these things, Lois.
Especially after I got shafted
by that Asian Santa at the mall.
What you want?!
What you want for Christmas?!
I was thinking maybe
one of those old-timey...
Too late! Take too long!
Sad Christmas!
- What you want?!
- Fire truck!
- What color?!
- Red!
Next!
Peter, have you been drinking?
- Well, a little. It is a party.
- Take off that stupid costume!
You look like a damn fool.
Ah, Dad, you won't say that when
you see my grand unicycle finale.
Everyone, I'll be right back.
In the meantime, I leave you with
the musical stylings of Chris Griffin.
I don't know what we're afraid of
Nothing would change if we made love
So I'll be your friend
And I'll be your lover...
All right, this is gonna blow you guys...
- Grandpa!
- Oh, my God!
- Is he breathing?
- Somebody call an ambulance!
Uh, Lois, maybe you better
call two ambulances.
How is he, Doctor?
Mrs. Griffin, his internal injuries
were much too severe.
I'd estimate he'll be dead
within the hour.
Dad, I'm so sorry I broke all your ribs
and busted your spleen
and punctured your lung.
I don't if you can hear me right now, but
I hope you know...
I love you, Dad.
Peter...
come closer.
There's something...
I need to say to you.
I'm here, Dad. What is it?
Peter...
you're a fat, stinking drunk.
Oh, my God, he's dead. He can't be dead.
There's got to be something I can do.
Maybe I'll bury him in the pet cemetery.
Okay, I'll bury him in
a regular cemetery.
- I can't believe Grandpa's dead.
- Well, he did kind of treat us like crap,
- but, yes, it is a tragedy.
- It is a tragedy.
- Excuse us.
- Yeah, we'll be right back.
- We're all gonna miss him.
- Tragic.
You know what the worst part is?
All I wanted was for my dad
to tell me he loved me.
But instead, he called me a fat,
stinking drunk.
Those were his last words.
Well, I hate to side
with your father, Peter,
but you do kind of drink a lot, and,
you know, sometimes
it affects the people you love.
Oh, my God. Lois, you're right.
Booze made me fall down all those stairs.
Booze killed my father.
Well, from this day forward,
I, Peter Griffin,
will never drink again.
- Peter, what are you doing?
- Crack.
- What the fuck?!
- Hey, at least I'm not drinking, Brian.
This isn't exactly a good substitute.
Where'd you get crack?
- From blacks.
- What?
Right behind Black's Hardware Store.
There's a white guy selling it.
Doing crack is not the way
to stop drinking.
You need to get to the heart of why you
feel the need to drink in the first place.
Look, here, this is the number of
a hypnotherapist I want you to see.
- All right, Brian.
- Good.
Peter, just thought I'd check on you.
Oh, my God!
Gov'ment came and took my baby!
This is mine, and this is mine,
and that's mine, and this is mine.
Oh, what's this?
"Hot Monogamy,
the board game for failing marriages."
"Dare card : Have her do a strip tease
and see how long
it takes you to get a bonner."
What's a "bonner"?
Stewie, what are you doing
with my jewelry box?
- You give that back to Mommy.
- No! Go to hell!
Stewie, I have had just about enough
of this new selfish attitude of yours.
- Now, give that back to Mommy!
- Very well, then.
- If I can't have it, nobody can!
- That is enough!
- You... you struck me!
- Oh, my God.
Stewie, honey, I am so sorry.
Are you okay, sweetie?
Oh, honey, I'm sorry.
Mommy would never hurt you.
- Let me give you a hug.
- No!
I haven't been this scared since
Mother Teresa OD'd in my car.
She is messed up, man!
Shut up! Just shut up!
Let me fucking think!
- Push her out.
- We can't leave her alone.
Push the bitch out!
Okay, now let's go back in
your mind to your childhood,
- to some of your deepest memories.
- Yeah, I'm getting something.
- Happy Father's Day, Dad.
- I'm not your father!
Oh, my God!
Francis Griffin wasn't my real father!
I wonder what else I've repressed.
Oh, my God!
I could've had a V8.
It was horrible, Rupert.
It was like a nightmare.
Lois came at me like a wild animal.
I had no way to defend myself.
Mother, I'm sorry I went
against your wishes.
I'm sorry I misbehaved, mother!
I'm sorry I misbehaved!
I love you, Mommy Dearest!
Oh, it was awful, Rupert.
I felt terrified and
brutalized and humiliated and... and...
and alive.
My God, I...
I haven't felt that alive in years.
Rupert, you know, I think perhaps
I may be one of those people who...
- gets a jolly out of being hit.
- Oh, Stewie, there you are.
Mommy is so sorry she hit you.
I promise I will never lay
a hand on you again.
Well, let's not make any rash decisions.
I mean, I did provoke you.
Come on, Lois, hit me! Beat the
crap out of me! Step on my cubes.
Oh, hi, Peter. Are you here
to bring back the TV set?
No, I sold it for crack. But listen,
Mom, I've got to ask you something.
Who's my real father?
I knew this day would come.
All right, Peter, here it is.
About 40 years ago,
I was vactioning in Ireland,
and I met a young rogue
named Mickey McFinnegan.
Peter, Mickey is your real father.
Oh my God! I gotta find him!
To Ireland!
- Sweetheart, when will you be back?
- I don't know, Lois.
All I know is somewhere
in the great land of Ireland,
is a big fat bastard who looks like me.
Call me as soon as you can, Peter. And
I really hope you find your real father.
- We're going to miss you, Dad.
- Come back soon, Daddy. I love you.
That'll do, pig. That'll do.
There she is, Rupert.
If I can just get her to
hit me one more time,
it'll give me the rush
I've been looking for!
What's next? What's next?
Oh, God, I've been so bloody naughty,
and I need to be taught a lesson
and you're the one to do it.
Oh! Thank you!
Thank you!
Yeah, all that stuff.
Let's make that happen.
- Hi, sweetie. You want some juice?
- Ooh, that'll be lovely.
- Oh, Stewie!
- Yeah?
- Look at the mess you made.
- I've made a terrible mess, haven't I?
Yes, I made you take time out
of your day to clean my mess
- and I should be punished for it. Go!
- Well, I guess it's not that big a deal.
- Accidents happen.
- I don't know.
Don't you think you should
spank me or slice my nostril?
- It's all right, Stewie. Now go play.
- All right.
Look! I've drawn heavy weight pugilist
David Tua on the wall.
- Punish me!
- Sweetie, you've really gotta stop...
huh, looks like David Tua...
You really got to stop misbehaving.
You're getting on Mommy's nerves.
Well, you know what'll ease your stress?
Slap me across the face like a bitch!
It's all right. I'll get some windex.
Come on! Discipline me!
Make me wear panties, rub dirt in my
eye, violating me with a wine bottle.
My God, I really do
have problems, don't I?
Welcome to Ireland.
We'll be landing in five minutes.
This is quite a country, Brian.
You know, Ireland has more
drunks per capita than people.
That's a negative stereotype.
I don't think the Irish drink
as much as people say they do.
Uh, excuse me?
Is this McSwiggen Village?
Ah, did ***** who say a word *****, hmm?
Is that a yes or a no?
Aye, tis McSwiggen Village. Where the
hills are green, the streams are clear,
and the sweaters are so thick,
even the boniest-fingered nun
could poke you in the chest
and it wouldn't bother you none.
Don't be so bold with your
dark hair and your proud ways!
I can't feel a thing!
You heard of a man
named Mickey McFinnegan?
Have I heard of him?
Of course I've heard of him!
- He's the town drunk.
- Town drunk?!
Oh, my God, you mean he's
the disgrace of the whole town?
You lads aren't from around here, are ya?
Top of the morning, ladies!
Let me cut you an Irish rose.
I don't know exactly
where the county Cork is
but I know where it should be!
Around here, the town drunk
is a person of great honor.
Excuse me, sir? My name is Peter.
Pleased to meet you, lad.
My name's Mickey.
Listen, uh, this maybe hard
for you to believe but...
- You're my father.
- Oh, am I now?
Yeah, I came all the way
from America to find you.
I suppose it's money you're wanted.
I owe you some allowance and so forth.
Oh, no, I don't want money. I just
want to get to know you and be friends.
So I can finally have a real dad
who loves and respects me.
You can't be me son.
You and me are nothing alike.
Just ask me sheep, O'Brian.
Who's leg do you have to hump
to get a pint of Guiness around here?
Boy it's amazing, isn't it?
You get two fathers
and neither one of them
wants anything to do with you.
There's got to be some way I can make
him see that I'm worthy of being his son.
About the only way I can ever impress
him is if I was a fat stinkin' drunk.
Peter! You are a fat stinking drunk.
- What?
- You're a fat stinking drunk!
Yes, from was he told us.
That's right on the money.
- Challenge him, you must.
- And I'm Hayden Christensen.
Wait a minute, Brian, that's it!
I'm a fat stinkin' drunk
because my father is a fat stinkin'
drunk. I gotta prove it to him.
I have gotta drink him
so far under the table,
he'll have no choice but to respect me.
Get me a beer, Brian.
I am going to prepare
for this as thoroughly as
Ben Affleck prepares for a role.
Wow, I got to be Henry VIII
in twenty minutes!
Allo? Allo? Alloo? Alloo?
Got it!
Mickey McFinnegan,
I challenge you to a drinking contest.
And what makes you think you can
hold your own with the *likes* of me?
Because I'm your son. And I'm tough.
I mean it half way through
Failure to Launch.
I just never managed
to get my life together.
Isn't that hilarious?
You're cute.
Done!
As we say in Ireland,
Let's drink until the alcohol in our
system destroy ours livers and kills us.
- I've got twenty on the fat one.
- Which one's the fat one?
- What happened?
- Peter, you won!
My God, nobody's ever beat me
at the game of drink.
Now do you believe that you're my dad?
Nobody but a McFinnegan could
handle that much of the creature.
You're the broth of me own
stubby shillelagh, all right.
- Welcome to me family, Peter.
- You hear that, Brian?
I'm a McFinnegan now!
I can forget all about Francis.
You know, there's something
you should always remember, Peter.
Francis may not have been your father,
but he raised you as if you
were his own. And if that isn't love,
- I don't know what is.
- Wow, I guess you're right.
But there is one thing, Mickey.
You knocked up my mom and
never called her again.
- Yeah, so what?
- So what?
So let's dance!
He doesn't smell like Irish Spring
And he never taught me anything
But still I slap my chest and
sing of my drunken Irish dad
His face looks like a railroad map
And he never shuts his freakin' trap
But all the ladies catch the clap
from your drunken Irish dad
Ask a Hennesy, Tennesy, Morrison,
Shaughnessy, Riordan and Rooney,
they'll tell you the same
McNutley, Mulrooney and
Cotter and Clooney
All feel the same mixture
of pride and the shame
Finnegan, Hannigan, Kelly and Flannigan
Look to the ground when
their dad passes by
Cafferty, Rafferty, Joyce and O'Lafferty
Fight for his honor and then start to cry...
We Irish lads are all infirm
And our moods infect us like a germ
'Cause we're all the spawn
of a pickled sperm...
And we don't tan well, either.
From our drunken Irish dad!