Translated By The Community Of WWW.MY-SUBS.COM
Family Guy
"Deep Throats"
Synchronisation by Kemar
Transcript by Raceman
Tuesday on Scarecrow and Mrs. King...
My God, what did those
drug dealers do to you?
Oh, they took my chest
out and threw it over there.
Then they pulled my legs out
and threw them over there.
Brian, you're still watching TV?
God, you've been sitting
there since I left.
I spent all morning watching
a VH1 special on Gwen Stefani.
I don't know what
a "Hollaback Girl" is,
all I know is I want her dead.
Hey, can you hand me the remote?
You know, you've been laying
around the house a lot lately.
Why don't you get a part-time
job like Peter used to have?
Ding, fries are done. Ding, fries are done.
I gotta run, I gotta run,
I gotta run, I gotta run.
I work at Burger King making
flame-broiled Whoppers,
I wear paper hats. Would you
like an apple pie with that?
Would you like an apple pie with that?
Mom, guess what?!
I just found out I got that
internship at Mayor West's office.
Wow, congratulations, Meg.
Yeah, it was a really tough
interview, but I totally nailed it.
All right, Meg, we're going to
start with a little word association.
I'll say a word and you say
whatever comes into your head.
- Okay.
- Mosquito.
Bite.
- Bite.
- Mosquito.
Ah, yes. Good one.
- Uh, mosquito.
- Bite.
- Mosquito.
- Bite
Very good.
You are a worthy opponent, indeed.
Oh, honey, I'm so proud of you.
You see, Brian, Meg has a job.
Hey, Meg, if you're working for the
mayor, you know what that means?
Even you're doing better than Brian.
Hey, everybody, Brian's the new Meg.
Brian's the new Meg!
- Yeah, you're the new me.
- Shut up, Meg.
Let's go, kids.
Time for school.
Lois, I don't want to
ruin your morning, but...
I flushed a diaper and
it's a mess up there.
Brian, what is this?
You're driving a cab?
Well, Lois, I realized you were right.
I mean, it's time I went out
and got a job,
for God's sakes, I'm seven years old.
Seven? That's not bad.
You know, Todd was 15 when he died.
The dog we had before you.
Hey, Peter, did you call me?
Yeah, I thought we'd
go to the park, Todd.
Oh, you're not taking
me to the vet, are you?
No, no, just a nice day at the park.
I'm a little worried that you're
going to have me put down.
I know there's been some concern
about my sphincter's low shutter speed.
No, no, we're just
going to the park, Todd.
Oh, okay, well,
I'll enjoy the ride, then.
Around the park one
more time, Bitterman.
Peter, I'm not your chauffeur.
Not for long with that
attitude, Bitterman.
Ah, this is living, Bitterman.
This set of wheels is even better than
those talking cars on that commercial.
Hey, how you doing there?
Listen, uh...
I couldn't help but notice you
across the parking lot and, uh...
you know, you're very
attractive and, uh...
You want to go behind
the Applebee's and do it?
Huh? You want to just go have some
dirty, stupid, insane parking lot sex?
Chuck, it's me, Morty.
Yeah, 'cause we could...
What?!
Yeah, they had me painted.
Oh, my God, I'm so embarrassed.
- Hey, how do you think I feel?
- No, no, that, too, but...
- It's not all about you, you know.
- Morty...
- Oh, my God, what are you doing?
- Think I was like a birthday present...
- for the kid or something like that.
- Oh, my god. Look at you.
- You're, you're hot.
- I know.
You know what I would've done to you back
there? Why didn't you say something earlier?
I said all that stuff. God!
Let's not rule anything out.
- Hey, look, there's Lois.
- Yeah. Hey, honk the horn.
Ah, hi, Peter.
- Ram her.
- What?
I said ram her!
What the hell?!
- Now shoot her tires out.
- What?
You got a gun?
Well, yeah. Every cabbie
carries a gun...
Give me the gun.
What the hell is wrong with you, Peter?!
You could've killed me!
Yeah, but I got you good, Lois.
Admit it. Just say it, I got you.
Oh, all right, you got me.
I told you.
Oh, no, what happened here?
Oh, we got into a little
accident. It's all right.
Oh, no.
Well, I guess accidents happen
when you least expect them.
That how come they
call them accidents.
Oh, look, you got the community
events corkboard wedged in your grill.
There, that's better.
Don't y'all forget to sign up for the
Quahog community talent show.
Talent show?
Oh, Peter, that could be fun.
- Do you think we have a chance at winning?
- Absolutely. I love being around the stage.
Except for that time we went
to see Phantom of the Opera.
Music is the gift I give to you...
Let's see the gross half of your face!
Come on!
Let's see the gross half of your
face so I can get out of here.
- That nose better be piggy.
- Shut up.
You shut up.
There it is.
Oh, your old guitar.
I haven't seen that thing in ages.
Well, Lois, I thought you and me
could do a song for the talent show.
It could be just like the old
days when we used to play.
You remember, Lois?
Remember our band: Handful of Peter?
Hi there, I'm Peter.
And this is Lois.
We want to talk to you about a
friend of ours. He's not here tonight.
Although, you know,
he's kind of here, Lois.
- You know you're right, he kind of is.
- Yeah, because he's in our hearts.
Uh, this is a song about that man
and his world that was taken from him.
Noble Indian chief
Bring us back your ways
You Indians were so awesome
in oh, so many ways
They all loved each other
Regardless of the tribe
One Comanche needs a cup of sugar
- And the Blackfoot would oblige...
- Oblige...
The only cause of death
Was drifting off to sleep
And they left this piece of wisdom
That we hope you all will keep
And they said...
They're gone now.
How could this have happened?
- How?
Oh, I haven't thought
about that in years.
You know, it would be fun
to write some new songs.
You know what else is fun?
Watching Mr. Belvedere
without people talking so loud.
- So I was thinking we could...
- Streaks on the china!
Never mattered before!
Who cared?
When you drop-kicked your jacket!
When you came through the door!
No one glared!
Hello?
Hey, Lois, what's up?
Milk?
Yeah, I'll pick some up
at the end of my shift.
Oh, got to go.
First fare of the night.
I should really pick up that
milk now before I forget.
You son of a bitch!
Hey, Brian, you see that magazine
cover right there? See who's on it?
Yeah, that's Jessica Alba.
Yeah, you want to know a secret, buddy?
- What?
- I would do her.
- Really?
- Oh, yeah.
I just wanted you to know
a little bit about who I am.
Thanks for the milk, Carl.
What the hell?
$400?!
My God, this is a bigger rip-off than
Peter's Sounds of the Rainforest CD.
This will help us fall asleep, Lois.
All right, let's get rid
of all these trees.
Once they're gone, this'll be a
great place to raise cheap beef.
Up yours, Sting!
Yeah, yeah! Hey, what's that
song he does that I hate?
Uh, "Desert Rose. "
Yeah, yeah, that song sucks.
Meg, I'm going to lunch
now and I'm having pizza.
So if you see the Noid running around,
tell him if he ruins
my pizza's freshness,
I'll snap his neck.
Hey, Meg, I need to see the mayor
about this $400 parking ticket.
Brian, you can't just barge in here.
You have to make an appointment.
But this is flat-out extortion.
No, it's not.
Adam can charge whatever
he wants for a parking ticket.
You know, Meg, that guy's
been playing fast and loose
with his position for years now,
and I've had it. He's a corrupt bastard.
- That is not true.
- Yes, it is.
Somebody's got to stand up and
prove to this town that he's a crook.
And it looks like it has to be me.
- What was all the commotion?
- Oh, nothing, it was just...
Perhaps it was the Noid
who should've avoided me.
Oh, you know what, Brian?
It took me two hours to
spell "hat" with these things.
I finally got the "T" right-side-up,
and then you come in here...
You're a bastard.
Where are you going?
I'm going to expose Mayor West
as the corrupt politician that he is.
I'm on my way to meet a source
who won't talk to me over the phone.
Ooh, scandal in Quahog.
Count me in.
Thank you for coming, Deep Throat.
You'll understand if I don't
come out from the shadows.
My identity will be safest
if you never see my face.
Uh, okay.
Mayor West hasn't slept
at home for three nights.
Kermit the Frog?
Somebody talked! No one is safe!
I'm getting out of here!
What's his appeal?
They should make a tube
that sends you right to work
That would save a lot of gas
But I guess there'd be a lot of tubes.
Well, that wasn't very good.
We're never gonna win that talent show.
Hey, now, Peter, you gotta remember
that when we used to write the old songs,
we had a lot of "inspiration," huh?
You know, I think Brian may have some
inspiration in a cigar box under his bed.
Eh, I don't know, Lois.
I don't think this is gonna work.
Come on, we can't
give up on our goals.
What if Jesus had done that?
Why is the ironing board still out?
That's, that's my
favorite picture of Brian,
over there on that wall.
He wants to have sex with me so bad.
He's not,
he's not gonna get to.
All right. There he goes. Let's move.
I say, what are we looking for?
I dunno, some proof of
Mayor West's corruption.
What are you doing here, Brian?
Still trying to smear my boss?
No, no, no, I actually
came to my senses,
and realized I was out of line.
Uh, I'm just here to apologize.
Oh, and, uh...
you're so pretty.
You're always pretty.
Oh, you guys are so sweet.
Oh, well, it's my pleasure.
Hey, can you guys hold on a sec?
I gotta get this to Helen in Accounting.
Okay, bye.
Aha. The mayor's date book.
This should tell us what we wanna know.
All right, let's get outta here.
Oh, God, I feel more delirious
than my cousin, Stewie Cruise.
I'm in love with Katie Holmes!
I'm not gay!
Go see my new movie!
I'm in love with Katie Holmes!
I'm not gay!
All we need is one incriminating entry
in this date book, and that's our ticket to...
Hey, Brian. What's up?
Hi, uh, Lois...
Peter.
Brian, did you know
this couch was here?
It's so comfortable.
Hey, Lois...
look how short Stewie is.
He's so short.
Oh, my God. He is short.
Well, uh, you two are
busy being nude. So, uh...
we'll just, uh, head out and, uh...
let you be nude.
Who were those guys?
I don't know.
Room for one more?
Well, this is the last
entry in the date book.
"Super secret meeting at motel.
Inform no one. "
I think we got him now.
You know, you really shouldn't
lie on that bedspread.
I saw this report on TV about
how filthy hotel rooms are.
In a moment, we will
use the special lights
to see just how filthy this seemingly
clean hotel room really is.
Well? What do you see?
Oh, Jem, you are truly outrageous.
Truly, truly, truly outrageous.
I see a grown man enjoying cartoons.
Well, that's it, then.
The only thing this guy is
guilty of is being a whack-job.
Wait, wait, wait.
Somebody's coming in.
Oh, it's just some fat hooker.
Oh, my God, it's Meg!
- What?
- Meg and Adam West.
Oh, oh, sorry, sorry.
God, this is incredible.
The mayor is dating a teenage intern,
and it's Meg.
What a story.
This is the perfect scandal
to take him down.
All we need is taped evidence.
Well, I've got the
disguises right here.
I thought you were supposed
to get the suit and the top hat.
Eh, I liked this one better.
Anything to wear a dress, huh?
Gosh, you're swell, Meg.
I really have a great
time when I'm with you.
Oh, Mayor West,
I feel exactly the same way.
Oh, please, please.
Call me Mayor Chapstick.
Well, we should probably go.
Here they come. Kiss me.
Come on, we gotta follow them.
Stewie?
Everything all right?
Uh, yeah. Uh...
Hey, listen. Freakin' shot in the dark.
You wanna do something sometime?
Great practice, Lois.
We are totally ready
for that talent show.
Oh, my God, Peter,
I am so wasted.
All I want to do is make cookies.
Oh, my God, I have a great idea.
Let's make cookies!
We don't have to, Lois.
Look...
there's a magical land of
desserts right behind you.
Stop.
Oh, Brian. You scared me.
Another late night, huh?
Yeah, Mayor West keeps me pretty busy.
Yeah, I noticed.
Where did you get that?
Meg, what the hell have
you gotten yourself into?
You realize he probably
does this with every new intern.
That's not true.
Adam and I are in love.
Oh, don't be ridiculous.
Listen.
I'm warning you
because I care about you.
I am going to the
press with this story,
and when it hits,
it'll be bigger than
Uncle Sam's nipples.
Jeez! What the hell...?
Uh, they're called nipples, guys.
- They're freakin' huge.
- You know what?
Maybe we can just all
relax and enjoy the sauna.
Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles
Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles...
I have to tell you something, Adam.
You're an alien. I know.
No, no.
My dog is gonna expose
our relationship to the press.
Well, so what?
You and I know that we
haven't done anything wrong.
I told you that I'd wait for
you until you're 18 or 21.
Or maybe 25, when you
can legally rent a car.
They don't care.
They're gonna make you
look like a monster.
I see.
Well, Meg, I'm a public figure.
I'm used to the tabloids' doodie.
It's you I'm worried about.
You're just a sweet young lady
with her whole life ahead of her.
This story could ruin your future,
and I can't let that happen.
I'll take the fall, no matter what.
Good-bye, Meg.
I'll always value your friendship.
I love you, Mayor Chapstick.
Brian? What are you doing here?
I, uh...
just wanted to give you this.
I don't think I'll be
needing it anymore.
I got so caught up in taking
down Mayor West, that I
just lost sight of right and wrong.
Thank you, Brian.
Well, can I give you a lift home?
My cab's right outside.
Good evening. I'm Diane Simmons,
and I'd like to welcome you
to Quahog's Fifth Annual Talent Show.
Let's have a round of
applause for our first performer.
There's no moustache
like my father's moustache
That's the biggest moustache in town.
Play me off, Johnny.
Ah, what else be funny tonight?
Uh... Star Jones got married.
That was in the news.
Uh, married a black fella,
which is quite a surprise
because I'd call her quite a catch,
and black guys, by and large, they're
not so helpful on a fishing vessel.
Now, Portuguese, absolutely, absolutely.
I even had a couple of Japanese
guys who worked out great.
Thank you very much.
You guys have been terrific.
And now our final
performance of the night.
Let's hear it for: Handful of Peter.
In God's eyes
Everybody's hot
This world has beauty
All through her
Picture the fattest
Chick you know
God
Would totally do her
He'd do her all the way
Even call her the next day
To see how work was going
I can't believe we
lost the talent show.
What'd we do wrong?
Well, Dad, I think I can
shed a little light on that.
You guys were so baked,
you didn't sound anywhere near
as good as you thought you did.
I was in the audience.
And here we thought
the weed was inspiring us.
Well, that's a popular misconception,
Mom and Dad, but the fact is,
the chief ingredient
in marijuana is THC,
a mild form of acid,
prolonged usage of which can cause
adverse effects to your sexual potency,
short-term memory loss and can
also severely damage your brain tissue
central nervous system
and basic motor skills.
To put it simply, Mom and Dad,
there's a reason
that they call it "dope. "
Trying to watch Mr. Belvedere.
So my advice to the
two of you would be...
According to our new arrival!
Life is more than mere survival!
And we just might live the good life yet!
Synchronisation by Kemar
Transcript by Raceman