Translated By The Community Of WWW.MY-SUBS.COM
Family Guy - Les Griffin
"Peterotica"
Synchronisation by Kemar
Transcript by Raceman
Guys, this is the best
dirty bookstore in town.
Family-owned, great hours,
and lots of parking in the rear.
Get it?
Wow, you usually expect
these places to be dirty.
Nah, it's pretty clean. Carol Burnett
works part-time as a janitor.
You know, when she tugged
her ear at the end of that show,
she was really saying
good-night to her mom.
I wonder what she tugged
to say good night to her dad?
Whatcha staring at, Joe?
These dolls all look really
surprised for some reason.
I... wonder what they're
all so surprised about.
What?!
You never seen a
handicapped man before?!
They're polyurethane
sex toys, Joe.
They're not capable
of judgment.
And even if they were,
who cares? They're whores.
Wow, an old-time penny show.
"The Naughty Flapper Girl. "
Oh, hot! She's voting!
Yeah, you break all the rules, huh?
Yeah, that's right,
vote for Taft, you dirty girl.
Hey, Quagmire, what's through that door?
Oh, that's the exit. 'Course, in this
place, every exit's also an entrance.
Make 'em laugh
Don't you know all the
world loves to laugh
I always try and find
the hottest chick in the place
I crack her on the noggin
with a lamp or a vase
And then when she's unconscious
I do stuff to her face
Make 'em laugh, make 'em laugh,
make 'em laugh!
Meg, I need you to baby-sit
Stewie tomorrow afternoon.
Mom! You know I go to
the mall on Saturdays.
I mean, I do have a life.
Hey, what time is it?
We're gonna miss the movie!
Yeah! Let's go, everyone.
Wow, Peter, that's a book, isn't it?
That's the first time I've
seen you reading something
that didn't later turn out
to just be a sandwich.
Eh, it's an erotic book.
I bought it at that sex shop.
I got to tell you, I've read 4 chapters
of this, and it's not sexy at all.
"Much Ado About Humping. "
Well, sounds sexy.
Peter, would you put that away!
I don't like you reading
smut at the table.
Yeah, if only this were smut, Lois.
"He rubbed her shoulder sensually. "
What the hell is that? That's not sexy.
You can't do somebody in the shoulder.
Why don't you and
that book get the room?
D- Did you hear what I said, Brian?
- I said, why don't you and that...
- That book get a room, yeah.
Okay, I just wanted
to make sure you heard.
Hey, guys, tell me if
this letter sounds all right.
"Dear Reek Publishing,"
"I was highly disappointed
by your erotic novel. "
"Here's what I would've wrote:"
"It was past midnight when the
blonde, smokin'- hot lab assistant"
"who looked a little like Heather
Locklear, only with bigger jugs,"
"was grabbed and thrown
on to the lab table. "
"He ripped off her lab coat, and she
grabbed his metallic extension. "
"Oh, did I mention he was a robot?"
"Cause that's kind of important. "
"Yeah, a robot. "
"Awesome. "
Whoa! That is hot!
I got to get a copy of that.
Yeah, you got some serious
talent there, Peter.
Really?
I'm no school administrator,
but there's an extension program
going on in my trousers.
"And then Captain
Leroy Hot Dog' Zanzibar"
"and Gina from my work got in the
backseat of his really cool spaceship. "
"Gina was finally wearing that
tank top I got her and nothing else. "
"Zanzibar knew he couldn't control
his space horniness any longer,"
"and then they totally did it. "
"And if I'd have been there,
I would've been, like,"
"Ah, sweet. "
Eh? What do you think?
You certainly do paint a picture, Peter.
I felt like I was right
there on planet Niptune.
You're not the only one. Everyone
down at the bar wanted a copy.
Wow! Maybe you should
think about publishing it.
Hey, if you ask daddy, he might even
give you some money to do it yourself.
That's a great idea, Lois!
I'll talk to him tomorrow.
If this works out, I could
make more money
than when I had that
rat farm in the basement.
Armando, do you have the rent?
We are trying, Senor
Griffin, but the land,
she gives us nothing.
There is no sunlight.
It's been two months, Armando.
You're putting me in a
real awkward position here.
Oh, please, Senor Griffin,
just one more week.
I will pay you double.
Perhaps we can work out
another arrangement.
Oh, please, senor, not my beloved!
Armando, Armando...
it is for the children.
Dios mio.
He takes the beam.
The spectators hold their breath
as Stewie Griffin
is America's last hope...
to take home the gold.
Oh, oh, did you see that, Mitch?
I sure did, Cathy that was impressive.
Here comes the dismount.
Hey, Stewie, I just took a nap.
You want an eye booger?
Oh, damn you, Chris!
Look what you've done!
I'm training for the Olympics,
and I need absolute concentration!
Look at him.
Look how fat he is.
Oh, my God, that was
even cooler than playing
with the speech function
on my Macintosh.
So, computer, what are you
thinking about right now?
Stewie is cool.
- What do you want, homo?
- Listen, uh, Mr. Pewterschmidt,
you're a businessman,
I'm a businessman,
and I've got a proposal that
I guarantee you can't refuse.
See, I wrote this erotica
book, and I was hoping
you could loan me
$7 billion to publish it.
How about I loan you five dollars?
It's at the bottom of this jar
of barbed wire and salt.
Why do you keep these things together?
All right, who wants to
buy some Peterotica?
- Ten bucks a pop.
- I'll take one.
- Me, too!
- Hey, give me one of those.
I look forward to having a raging semi!
Wow, Peter, you're going
into the publishing business?
Yep. Mr. Pewterschmidt gave me
five dollars for these Xeroxes,
and I haven't looked back.
I'm such a huge fan of Peterotica.
There you go.
Thanks for reading.
Hi. Would you be offended
if I told you your prose
suggests a male-working class
version of Emily Bronte?
No.
Would you be offended if I said I'd
like to use your ass as a bongo drum?
Yes.
Well, then we are on
two different wavelengths.
Peter Griffin. Thanks for reading.
Welcome to Peterotica on tape.
I'm Betty White reading
"The Hot Chick Who Was Italian,"
"or Maybe Some Kind of Spanish,"
by Peter Griffin.
Chapter One.
"Oh, God, you should've
seen this one hot chick. "
"She was totally Italian. "
"Or maybe some kind of Spanish. "
Oh, yeah!
Getting hot in here.
I'd better take my shirt off.
Wow! You know, from the other
side, that's kind of annoying.
Happy birthday, darling.
Oh, honey, a fur coat!
Thank you.
Well, it's not real fur. It's actually
made from bald eagle,
and it's weather-treated with a mixture
of whale skin oil and children's tears.
Yes?
Mr. Pewterschmidt, I'm Scott
Greenberg, attorney at law.
My client was injured
listening to this audio book.
We're suing you for
every penny you've got.
What? Why?
You're liable as publisher.
I'm here to cease your assets.
Griffin!
Well, Mr. Greenberg i'd like to see
you try to cease my assets after
battling the Rancor.
Didn't realize Greenberg
was a Jedi name.
- Hey, Mr. Pewterschmidt.
- Hello, Peter.
- What's up?
- Good... Oh, damn it.
- I mean, not much.
- What you got there?
- This? It's a gun.
- Oh yeah?
- Yeah, i'm going to kill you.
- Daddy, what are you doing?
Your fat bastard husband ruined me!
I lost my home, my money,
and, perhaps just as serious,
my wife left me!
- Mom left you?
- Yeah. She ran off with Ted Turner.
God only knows what they're doing.
Should we give Elmo a bath?
- Yeah!
- Should we give Telly a bath?
- Should we give Ernie a bath?
No! Ernie doesn't like the monster!
Look, you can stay with us
if you want, you filthy hobo.
You shouldn't be embarrased about
mooching off your kids at age 70.
Go to hell, fat head!
Have I use that one?
No, I haven't.
Yeah, fat head.
Daddy, don't talk to Peter like that.
All you've done his hole
life is treat him like crap.
Now he's offering to help you.
The least you can do is be grateful.
Mmm... all right.
That is settled. You stay with us.
I promise, you'll love it here.
Even more than Julia
Roberts loves herself.
Hi, i'm Julia Roberts.
You know, a lot of people
died in the tsunami.
But don't worry.
I didn't.
And i'll be here to
entertain you and love
my life for many, many years to come.
Me...
Meeeee...!
- Daddy you're not dressed.
- Huh?
Oh, yeah. Couldn't figure that one out.
You've still a guy for that.
Mom, I can't believe you
came out of that belly.
What is that?
Daddy, did you, um...
use the bathroom
this morning?
- Yeah.
- And did you remember to...
clean up after wets.
Um, no. I was hoping you'd...
Oh, daddy! No, no!
OK. Brian?
Oh, God, no. No, no, no, no.
I'll do it.
Daddy, I never thought you'd
be so lost without your money.
You right, Lois. Who the hell am
I kidding? I can't live like this.
I should never have come here.
Oh, I hate to see daddy like this.
Maybe there's something you
can do to help cheer him up.
Don't worry, Lois,
I know just what to do.
I am going to teach your father
how to be a regular guy.
You think you can do that?
Sure, I've steered our family
through bigger problems.
Like when we were cartoon
sketches on the Tracy Ullman Show.
Well, that's the end of Puss.
He was the best cat anyone ever had.
Hey, Lois, what do you say we
go downtown and buy a dog?
Hey, wait a minute.
You already have a dog.
- So long, Puss.
- We'll miss you.
It's gonna be quite a different
place with him gone, that's for true.
All right, Cathy, it looks
like Stewie Griffin
is preparing to begin the floor routine.
That's right, Mitch, and as we
watch Griffin doing this,
I want to remind everyone
that this is absolutely not gay.
Boy, that was really gay.
No, no. Didn't you just hear the
announcers? They said it's not gay.
Ha, ha. Stewie one, you zero.
What are we doing here?
Listen, I know you're upset
about losing your money,
so I wanted to show you it's not
so bad living like a regular guy.
- So, these people live here?
- No, this is a bus.
People ride it to get
places that they need to go.
You look familiar.
I was your gardener for 12 years.
You look different without
my lawn under you.
I don't take the lawn
with me when I go.
Well, I was right to
trust you with it, then.
Now, this is called waiting
in line at the movies.
It's what us regular people do.
Trust me, it makes it
that much more special
when we finally get inside
and see Renee Zellweger
doing her whole scrunch-face routine.
Oh, no, these ants are
ruining our picnic.
You meant this picnic
is ruining our ants.
So don't try to deny it, pretty baby
You've been down so long
you can hardly see...
You know, Peter, what you
showed me today was just awful.
What are you talking about?
I really don't see what's so great
about being a regular person.
The bus smells like crap,
the movie theater is sticky,
and Renee Zellweger should only
be the cute friend at best.
You know, I never thought
about it till now, but...
maybe being a regular
person does suck.
My God, is this what my
whole life is destined to be?
Not unless you do something about it.
Yeah, but what?
Carter,
hand me my thinking grenades.
- Where'd you get these?
- Shh. Carter,
I'm thinking.
Oh, my God, he's dead!
That might work.
What's happening?!
I got it.
Carter, somehow you and me
are going to find a way to get rich.
Now you're talking my language.
All right, then, let's do it.
Hi. I'm Betty White.
I just got a subpoena
regarding an erotic novel,
and I'm looking for the
son of a bitch responsible.
All right, Peter, how are we going to
do this? How are we going to get rich?
Well, I say we start out
small, Carter. Here's my plan.
I'll distract Lois while you
steal money from her purse.
Lois, look at me!
Look at me! Look at me!
Ka-kaw! I've got her wallet.
Ka-kaw!
- Daddy, what are you doing?
- Look at the unicycle!
Well, she's got ten dollars in here.
And it cost me $900 for the
six weeks of unicycle lessons.
So, we're a little in the red right now.
But you've got to spend money to
make money, champ. Moving on.
All right, now we play it cool.
Hey, Meg, uh, we're trying
to make some money and, um...
would you like to buy some pot
from your granddaddy and me?
Um...
- Wow, sure.
- Oh, fantastic.
- What the hell was that for?
- Now we have to pot and the money.
You sure this is going to work, Peter?
All I know is, there's a
lot of money to be made
in these stupid teen dramas
they keep putting on TV.
And we're going to get our share.
I don't want to wait
for my lunch to get colder
Why can't I eat it now?
I don't want to wait
for da-da-da new Toyota
I want the car that's got a lot of gas
Come on, Joey, I want to be with you.
Dawson, I'm just not ready
to give up my virginity.
Come on.
No.
I promised myself that I'd save
it for the man that I marry.
Come on, that's stupid.
I'm, I'm just not
comfortable, you know?
I don't...
This is like the '90s, man.
I mean, it's like, everybody's...
Come on, you saw me on that boat.
I was wearing a blazer.
- Uh? Come on.
- No! I just... I...
I don't want to, all right?
I don't want to right now.
I told you, I'm not comfortable.
I think you could respect that,
you know.
I do res...
I totally respect you.
Makes me want you more, you know.
Come on, man, let's just...
Let's just go nuts.
- No. I said I don't...
- Come on!
No! No! Peter, stop!
Just stop, all right?
Turn off the camera.
- God, I'm sorry, Mr. Pewterschmidt.
- I don't want to do this anymore,
all right? You know
what? You went too far.
- What?
- You went too far.
This is character.
That's how... I mean...
- He's that kind of...
- No, forget it, forget it.
You know what? It's just
weird, man. It's just weird.
You're weird.
All right, just get off it.
Let's just do something
else to make money.
And we will be back.
Stand back, Brian.
I'm preparing for my vault.
You can't vault inside the living
room. You're going to get hurt.
Yeah, I'll get hurt right
on to a Wheaties box.
I don't see that happening.
Yeah, who cares what
you say. You're a dog.
You can't see colors.
Which means you can't see
the colors of the American flag.
Commie.
I think I'm okay.
Oh, God!
Somebody!
Do I take it out or do I leave it in?
- Got it. We'll rob a train.
- Love it.
All aboard.
All right, everybody, this is a...
Hey, where the hell is everybody?
Oh, we haven't had a paying customer in
months. Nobody rides the train anymore.
Oh, well, for God's sake.
Are you robbers?
Yeah.
Well, you could take my wallet.
My MasterCard's in there.
Although, to be honest,
I'll probably just cancel it
before you can use it, so...
Give me that hole punch!
Is this your hole punch
or the train company's?
Well, that's, you know,
I got to pay for that.
That comes out of my paycheck...
if you take it.
Oh, really?
Well, I can't in all good
conscience take that, then.
Oh, good...
- Thank you... I guess.
- Yeah.
- I'm a working man myself.
- No, it's tough out there.
- You can't, you know...
- It's tough, it is.
All right, well, uh, can you stop
this thing, so we can get off?
Uh, no.
I mean, I'd love to,
but it stops at the
pre-designated stops.
I don't have control over that.
- The engineer does that.
- Well, uh...
Well, how much are tickets?
Well, for this, this is
a first-class cabin,
it's 25 bucks.
And we're the robbers.
- OK, um, how much is coach?
- Uh, $12 for coach.
Well, he's a senior.
You know what, that's fine.
Just give me two coach tickets.
All right, thank you.
Oh, wow, when did Mama Mia!
come to the Oakdale?
Oh, yeah, what, uh,
just a week ago, I think.
Oh, well, we should go.
Do you want to go see Mama Mia!?
Peter, could I speak to
you over by the door?
Good as new.
Oh, come on!
I give up. We're going to be
lower-middle class Americans forever.
A fate worse than death.
Seriously, we may as well just be dead.
You know what, Peter, that's not true.
In the time we've spent
together, I've learned something.
When you're rich, you don't
own your possessions,
your possessions own you.
- Oh, Carter, darling.
- Babs, sweetheart!
Honey, we're rich again.
I divorced Ted Turner
and took half his money.
- We own half of CNN.
- He-hey!
- And TNT.
- Neat.
All right, buddy, we did it, we're rich.
We? Go to hell, you fat peasant!
- Aw, crap.
- Peter, listen to me.
Money doesn't matter.
Ten years ago Daddy offered to give
us $10 million, and I turned it down.
- What?!
- Yes. And I'll always turn it down,
because money just
complicates everything.
We don't need money
because we have each other.
Happiness isn't about buying expensive
things, it's about being together.
It's not about taking expensive trips,
it's about holding each other
during a thunderstorm.
And we have that kind
of happiness, Peter.
Real happiness, because
we have each other.
Yeah.