Translated By The Community Of WWW.MY-SUBS.COM
Family Guy
The Tan Aquatic with Steve Zissou
Peter, are you sure you're allowed
to bring a baby onto the golf course?
Well, Lois asked me to watch
Stewie for the afternoon.
It's all right, I don't think
the club will mind.
- It's Cleveland I'm worried about.
- Peter, is this really necessary?
- I can't hardly see anything.
- Hey, look, it's President Nixon.
No, wait, it's a black guy.
No, it's Nixon.
Oh, boy, that was close.
Will you please hurry up?
It's 100 degrees out here.
You're a worse parent
than Britney Spears.
I know, I know.
Oh, the gift basket was not
worth the trip, not by a long shot.
Oh, I got to get that.
I'll talk to you later.
- Hey, uh, Joe...
- Don't say it, Peter.
- I was just wondering...
- Peter, I swear to God...
What's your handicap?
Every hole... that's a joke
that just doesn't get old!
Damn it! Come on! Come on!
Come on, Glen! Come on,
get your head in the damn game!
Hey, do you think it's time
to talk to Quagmire
about his anger issues with this game?
A white man shouldn't play sports
in the first place.
Hey, hey, that's a stroke!
I just tapped my ball, Quagmire. Relax.
Oh, relax? Oh, okay.
Look, I just tapped my ball.
Just tapped it again.
Tap, tap, tap.
Where is it? Oh! It's in the hole.
Eagle.
Yay, Quagmire.
Hey, Quagmire, you know it's
not fun when you're like this.
You want fun? Go home and buy a monkey.
- What does that even mean?
- I don't know.
Boy, we've got a beautiful day for this.
Hi, Mr. Herbert. Here's your paper.
Sorry, Chris, but I'm afraid I'm going
to have to cancel my subscription.
Cancel? But you love this paper.
Listen, I think you're a real nice guy,
but I've just decided
to go with another paper.
Hello, there, Kyle. You look nice today.
I see you're wearing your big shorts
with the baggy leg holes that flutter
- so carelessly in the breeze.
- Here's your paper.
What are you doing here?
Beat it, nerd.
Thank you.
Would you like to come inside
for a cupcake and a glass of wine?
Shut up, old man.
What's going on in my pants?
Looks like we got six
more weeks of winter.
We now return to
Cutting in Line in Front of Italians.
Hey, Copernicus, why don't you navigate
yourself to the back of the line
with your feet and
stand there with your shirt?
Hey, Peter, how was your golf game?
Well, Lois, you tied my golf shoes
a little tight before I left the house.
Had to deal with that all day.
Thank you very much.
Oh, my God, look at Stewie!
Peter, you took him out
without any sunscreen?
Maybe.
You know the sun is dangerous
for a baby's skin.
Peter, this is more irresponsible
than when you fed your
mogwai after midnight.
Peter, didn't the little Chinese man
tell you not to feed him after midnight?
Come on, Lois, he's so cute.
And he's hungry. What could happen?
Hello, I'm Fran Drescher.
Kill it! Kill it!
What the deuce are you all staring at?
Is there something wrong with me?
Wow, look at me.
I'm a young Eartha Kitt.
"President Johnson, bring our boys
home from Southeast Asia.
It's an unwinnable war..."
Dad, I was wondering
if I could borrow $17.
Chris, what do you need money for?
Isn't that why you have a paper route?
No, this new kid named Kyle
keeps stealing all my customers.
Oh, that's terrible. You're a
wonderful paperboy, Chris,
and you need to remind
your customers of that.
She's right, you got to
stand up for yourself.
Like my great-grandfather, Turn-Of
The-Century-Take-On-All-Comers Griffin.
All right, put 'em up, put 'em up.
Are you having a bully day?
I'm having a bully day.
Is everyone having a bully day?
- Bully.
- Yes, Bully.
Oh, thank God we live in this time.
- Stewie, what are you doing?
- Just getting my bronze on, baby.
Hey, what do you think
of my recumbent tan pose?
Legs probably spread a little wider
than they ought to be, but
who gives a damn? This is
just tan Stewie being tan Stewie.
Check me out, Brian.
Hey, Mr. Herbert, I want you back.
Please, will you be
my paper customer again?
Oh, uh, hey, Chris.
Oh, is that my phone?
- Oh, better go get that.
- Well, if it isn't King Lardass.
- Don't call me names, Kyle.
- Hi, Kyle.
Well, listen, it was wrong of you
to steal my customer away from me.
- And I want him back.
- Oh, yeah?
- Look, Griffin got his ass kicked.
- What a loser.
I have that shirt at home.
You... you pushed me.
Boys, boys, we can settle this like
reasonable and sexy teenagers.
Whoever can swallow
the most Tylenol PM wins.
- Oh, my God, Chris, what happened?!
- Kyle beat me up.
- You let that little punk beat you up?
- Peter, you should be more sympathetic.
Remember, you had a bully, too,
when you were his age.
Yeah, you're right. Randy Fulcher
used to pants me every chance he got.
My book report is on The Giving Tree.
Nerd!
Randy!
- Nerd!
- Randy!
Peter, I think one of us should go over
and have a talk with Kyle's parents.
I'll do it, Lois. Right after
a healthy breakfast of juice,
toast and store brand imitation frosted
flakes featuring Terry the Tiger.
They'rrrre... food.
Hey, ladies, you mind if I park here?
I'll only be a few minutes.
- Stewie, what is that on your lip?
- I drew a pencil mustache.
I like it 'cause it's just above my lip.
The kind of mustache that says, "Yeah,
I've been nude on camera. What of it?"
Come here, I'll take care
of that, sweetie.
Ew, ew, it's got spit all over it.
Now I know what it feels like to
have dinner with Martin Landau.
What people forget about Polanski is
Polanski wasn't a perfectionist.
And pedophile or not, he,
he was a perfectly professional person.
And punctual.
Yeah, maybe we could talk
about something else?
You know my wife and I are very
involved in Planned Parenthood.
Which provides possibilities for
people who are underprivileged.
Maybe chew your food a little, champ.
Who are all these people?
Oh, just a few friends over to
enjoy this gorgeous weather,
and maybe take a dip in the pool.
Hey, Devon, Devon, come here.
Brian, this is Devon.
Devon just finished directing a movie.
Yeah, it, uh, stars a little actress
named Joan Van Ark.
Maybe you've heard of her.
- Right. Possibly.
- You're talking out of your ass.
It doesn't matter, Brian, I'm tan.
Hey, Brian, Brian, Brian,
look at my tan walk.
- Devon, do you have a cigarette?
- Sure.
And here's a copy of my last movie.
It's essentially Brokeback Mountain
from the point of view of the horses.
Hey, the sun's been up for an hour.
Shouldn't we get riding?
- Uh, are they still sleeping?
- I don't know. I'll check.
- Hey, there. Are you Kyle's parents?
- Yes. Can we help you?
Yeah, I'm Peter Griffin.
Listen, apparently your son got
into a little scrape with my kid.
- Oh, dear, they're not getting along?
- Like an old guy and a midget.
Sir, will you please stop staring at me?
Where's the rest of ya?
So, listen, Chris is pretty upset
about what happened.
Would you mind if I had
a word with your son?
Not at all. He's up in his room.
Hey, there. Kyle?
- Hey, I'm Chris Griffin's father.
That's not very nice.
I don't sound like that at all.
You're making me sound
like Michael Stipe.
Listen, I just want you to know what
you did the other day was wrong.
- What you did the other day was wrong.
- You're not making this easy, Kyle.
You're not making this easy, Kyle.
My name's Peter Griffin.
I'm a big, fat, dumb butt-face.
- Shut up, Kyle.
- I'm Peter Griffin.
- I'm a dorky, fat, numbnuts.
- Kyle, I said shut up.
You're a poop-nose.
- Hey, Peter.
- Hey, what's going on?
- Is something wrong?
- No, no.
Everything's cool right now.
Might be some problems later, but we'll
cross that bridge when we come to it.
Hello.
Peter did what?!
- Well, I'd best be getting to work.
- It's nighttime.
Boy, you said it.
All right, take it easy.
Peter, you get down from
that tree this instant!
No! You're gonna yell at me!
You're damn right I'm gonna yell at you.
You beat up a 13-year-old boy!
He called me names!
You're 43, and you just assaulted
our neighbor's child!
This is a very serious situation.
Well, maybe you should have
just had an abortion, Lois!
Would that make you happy
if I was never born?!
What?
I'm going to prison, aren't I?
- What are you doing?
- Got to keep the tan up.
It's not a skin color,
it's a lifestyle, Brian.
See, you wouldn't know that
because you're white as a ghost.
You're haunting this house
with your whiteness, Brian.
Hey, wake me up in 15, will ya, babe?
Fine.
Key Largo, Montego
Baby, why don't we go down to Kokomo?
But not too fast 'cause
Stewie takes it slow...
Oh, crap! Stewie!
Uh, hey, buddy. I was just coming
to tell ya it's time to get out.
I've been in there for six and
a half hours, you son of a bitch!
- Don't touch me!
- Well, how, how...?
- Can, can you get up?
- I'll try.
I can't do it! I can't do it!
Get the lotion! Put the lotion on me!
- Brian!
- Oh, uh, hi, Mr. Furley.
Never mind! I'll come back later!
Now be polite, Peter.
Kyle's mother agreed not to
press charges if you apologize.
- Hello, Lois.
- Hello, Claire.
We just came by
because there's something
Peter would like to say to Kyle.
- Go on.
- Slorry.
- Say it right, Peter.
- Ow! Ow! Sorry!
Thank you, Peter.
Now what do you say, Kyle?
- Apology accepted.
- Good.
Now why don't you patch things up with
Mr. Griffin by showing him your Legos?
You got Legos? Aw, sweet!
- Lois only buys me Mega Bloks.
- They're the same thing, Peter.
You know what, Lois?
They are not the same thing.
And the sooner you get that
through your thick skull,
the sooner we can get
this marriage back on track.
Hey, listen, uh,
sorry about beating you up.
I felt pretty bad about it.
Hey, this look like a spaceship to you?
Sorta.
Well, I never was very good
at building things.
Like that time I built that
handmade electric razor.
By gluing many razor blades
to this ordinary desk fan,
I'll save time in my morning routine.
Lois, I done it again.
You don't have to apologize.
I would have done the same thing.
I mean, bullying makes
you feel pretty cool.
Yeah, guess it was kinda cool.
You know, I always used to be
the nerd getting bullied, but
doing it to someone else
was pretty sweet.
And the more you do it,
the sweeter it gets.
Cook much?
Peter, what the hell is wrong with you?!
What's wrong with me? You're the
one punching yourself in the face.
Hey, Lois, how come you keep
punching yourself in the face?
- Knock it off!
- You're gonna hurt yourself.
- Ha! You're getting her good!
- Hey, Stewie, nice sunburn.
God, you horse's ass!
Hey, Brian, you want some Stewie jerky?
- Oh, God, that is disgusting.
- I'm finally starting to peel.
I'm telling you, Brian,
my tanning days are over.
I'm just glad I stopped before I
did any real damage to my skin.
I wouldn't be so sure.
I don't remember you having
that mole before.
What the devil?
Where did that come from?
- Brian, what is that?
- I don't know.
Of course, your sunburn was
pretty bad. I suppose it could be...
the "C" word.
What the hell does that
have to do with anything?
No, cancer.
I-I thought you meant...
It's not important...
Oh, no!
Cancer!
Well, the mole looks benign,
but we won't know for sure
whether it's cancerous until the
tests come back in a few days.
A few days?!
- I could be dead by then!
- Relax, Stewie.
He said it looks benign.
We'll just have to wait and see.
Jim Henson had a wait-and-see attitude
and look what happened to him.
Now we've got wrong-sounding Muppets!
- Hey, Swedish chef.
- Oh, hey, Kermit, what's going on?
I'm hungry.
Oh, that's no problem. I could cook
you something. You want some spaghetti?
That's, like, my specialty and junk.
Dad, what's wrong with you?!
Why are you acting like such a bully?
'Cause there are two kinds of
people in this world, Chris.
There are bullies and there are nerds.
And there are hot Asian chicks.
They'll do what you want. Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah. You better believe it, buddy.
They will do what you want
because they know,
they know what you want.
Oh, oh, oh, don't be afraid.
Don't be afraid. I won't hurt you.
I won't hurt you.
Me big American man.
My point being that I'm a bully,
not a nerd.
Now, where was I? Oh, yeah.
Dad, get away from me!
Oh, in the kitchen, Meg?
Brian, I may only have one week to live
and I've got to make the most of it.
Now, I've made a list of things
I want to do before I die
and you've got to help me
since this is all your fault.
"Visit Chicago Museum of Art."
Okay, we can do that.
Next on your list, you want
to learn to ballroom dance.
All right, if you're gonna make
me do this, at least let me lead.
- Fine, you lead.
- All right, then.
I love you.
- What? What'd you say?
- Uh, olive juice.
- Olive juice?
- Olive juice you, too.
Hey, you nerds wanna see a puppet show?
- Peter, put me down!
- I told you, not until you sing.
High on a hill was a lonely goat herd...
Lay-hee-oh-da-lay-hee-oh
da-lay-hee-hoo!
Dad, what are you doing to Mr. Swanson?
Peter, put him down right now!
- Beat it, Lois.
- Peter, stop it!
- Joe is your friend.
- Shut up, ya nerd!
Peter, look at yourself.
You are no different than that
bully who used to pick on you.
Are you kidding?
I'm nothing like Randy Fulcher.
Oh, no? Does that look familiar?
Oh, my God, you're right, Lois.
I shouldn't be bullying
the people I care about.
I should be bullying Randy Fulcher!
He's the jerk in all this.
Like Dick Cheney when he was
a Wal-Mart greeter.
Go fuck yourself.
- Well, that's it for the list.
- Not quite, Brian.
There's one more thing
I need you to do before I die.
- Write down my final thoughts.
- Oh, come on!
I don't have much time!
Oh, squiggly line in my eye fluid,
I see you there lurking on
the periphery of my vision,
but when I try to look at you,
you scurry away.
Are you shy, squiggly line?
Why only when I ignore you do
you return to the center of my eye?
Oh, squiggly line, it's all right.
You are forgiven.
Hello. Oh, hi, Dr. Hartman.
All right, I'll tell him. Thanks. Bye.
You don't have cancer.
You're gonna be fine.
Really?! Oh, thank God! Oh, thank God!
Wait, wait. Look, there's no reason
we can't finish the memoir anyway.
Let's see what you've got so far.
Oh, you are just the
worst type of person.
Dad, what are we doing here?
Chris, I'm gonna show you
how to stand up to a bully.
Hey, Fulcher!
Griffin?
- The feeling's mutual.
- What are you doing here?
I'm here to kick your ass, Fulcher.
I'm gonna beat ya, and then
my son Chris is gonna beat ya.
It's gonna be an old-fashioned
father-son beat-off.
Wait a minute, Dad. You can't hit him!
- Yeah, I have MS.
- Oh, you hear that, Chris?
This guy's got a monkey scrotum
and he's bragging about it.
Now you really got me mad.
No, Dad!
Sorry I had to do that, Dad.
But you wanted me to
learn to stand up to a bully.
Well, I'm standing up to you.
Stop bullying people, Dad!
My God, Chris, you're right.
Look at me. Look what I've become.
I thought it'd feel good
to be a bully, but
all I did was make people feel
as bad as Randy made me feel.
- I'm just a big jackass.
- It's all right, Dad. I forgive you.
As long as you promise never
to bully anyone again.
I promise, Chris.
I mean, you know,
unless I get really stinkin' drunk,
in which case all you got to do
is outrun your sister.
Oh, I like that. That's nice.
That's a warm family moment.
I agree. We can all learn
something from that.
Wocka, wocka...
Who wants to hear a funny-ass joke?