Translated By The Community Of WWW.MY-SUBS.COM
Hi, it's me, Peter, your TV cartoon pal.
Y'know, Lois has bitchin' lately
that I watch too much
TV and don't read enough books.
So I went to the library
and picked up three books
by the greatest author
of the last thousand years.
Stephen King.
And tonight I'd like
to share them with you.
We begin with a little
tale called "Stand by Me"
about 4 young boys who
went looking for a dead body
and instead found ..... themselves.
... and also a dead body.
The year was 1955
and the voice in my head
was that of Richard Dreyfuss.
I never had friends like
the ones I had when I was 12.
There was me, Petey Lachance
Anyone else fed up with
this over-saturation of media?
Three channels, and still nothin' on.
Then there was Joey Duchamp
The voice in his head was Roy Scheider.
How are you, Richard?
Fine, Roy, how are you?
Good, good.
We should grab a
drink sometime and catch up.
Maybe reminisce about "Jaws".
Great, you should
give me a call sometime.
My number's 555 ...
Wait, wait. What?
555?
Er ... yeah.
You know what, Richard?
If you don't want
to have drinks, just say so.
You don't have to be a dick about it.
Oh, please!
Make the voices stop!
And then there was Quag Chambers.
He was the leader of our gang.
He had sex when he was five
and committed his
first rape when he was ten.
Rape, of course,
being legal in the 50's.
Ha ha. Beat those cards, fellows!
Ha ha ha.
Giggity, giggity, 50's, giggity
Hey, you guys ...
Finally, there was Cleve Brown
my pudgy black friend.
I can still see him now
all pudgy and black.
Cleve, please, we're
busy lookin' at Playboy.
Look at the way these
women starve themselves.
This one can't be more that 180 pounds.
This is way better than Playboy.
Do you guys wanna see a dead body?
Cleve, it's 1955.
Please re-enter the clubhouse in a
more stereotypically animated fashion.
Lord a'mighty! I done seen me
a dead body down by the lake!
Sho' nuff, I thought I'd go deef and dumb
when I saw me that dead body!
Cleve, calm down!
You're not making any sense!
Anything was possible
as we set out that day
except contracting AIDS
because AIDS had not yet
been invented by the government
in an effort to eradicate
the homosexual community.
Have Gun, Will Travel,
reads the card of a man
A knight without
armour in a savage land
OK, I got another one.
- Show me that smile again
- Ooh, show me that smile
Don't waste another
minute on your cryin' ...
We decided to cut through
old man Pressman's junkyard.
Even though legend had it,
that any kid caught scaling the fence
ran the risk of being
attacked by the old man's dog.
who would charge to the cry of "Chopper,
sick balls"
I got a bad felling about this.
Hey!
What are you kids doin'?
Oh no, it's him!
That's right!
Old man Pressman.
I own the junkyard.
I'm cranky 'cos all my stuff is junk.
Why can't I have nice things?
Chopper, sic 'em!
Sic 'em, boy!
Now, he said "sic 'em, boy",
but what I heard was
"Chopper, talk to
disfigured World War 2 veterans
who aren't as
bitter as they should be."
Glad I could do my part.
I think you may have done too much.
Hey, how about this brand
new thing called rock'n'roll?
Even though it was just invented,
we already remember it fondly.
Here's Little Richard
with "Piano Riff Woooo"
My arse!
Man, this trip is dangerous.
Couldn't we have just taken a bus?
..... black guy.
Uh, guys, anyone know
when the next train is scheduled?
Don't worry. If a train comes
I'll warn you in slow motion.
T-r-a-i-n!
Aaaaaaahhhh!!!
Aaaaahhh! Aaaaahhh! My legs!
A-n-o-t-h-e-r     t-r-a-i-n!
Aaaaaaahhhh!!!
Aaaaaaahhhh!!! Aaaaaaahhhh!!!
What an odd, clustered train schedule!
Hey, sorry you paralyzed, Joey.
Ah, it's alright.
Thanks for goin' all the way back
to the junkyard to
get me this wheelchair.
Boy, was old man Pressman angry.
O-o-o-o-o-h-h-h-h-h!!!
Well, there it is.
None of us could breathe.
The twisted and mangled body
we had come to see
was far more disgusting
than any of us could
ever have imagined.
He's nasty.
Out of my way, you little pipsqueaks!
I'm taking credit for finding this body.
It was the meanest guy in town.
Ace, and his whole gang.
Beast-man, Mer-man, and for
some reason, Norm from "Cheers."
Hey, gang.
What, are we beatin' somebody up?
Now, get lost!
We'll take it from here.
Kiss my grits,
you cheap dime store hood.
This ain't over, Lachance.
I mean, you have a
gun right now, but tomorrow
I'll get a gun and come
to your house and kill you.
Oh .... yeah, I guess
you could do that, huh?
I mean, we live in the same town.
And I just can't be on
my guard for the rest of my life.
Boy, that is a major hole in this story.
OK, take the body.
We never forgot
that wonderful summer,
and eventually, we all
went our seperate ways.
Joey learned to live
without the use of his legs,
and even went on to create
a wheelchair type rugby game
called
"Don't-feel-sorry-for-us-ball"
Cleve grew up and went
on to marry Rebecca Romjin.
Actually, I'm not
even joking about that.
The fat kid from "Stand by Me"
is now married to Rebecca Romjin.
Can you believe that?
I swear to God!
Look it up on the internet!
Doesn't that piss you off?
Quag grew up to become
a famous Hollywood actor.
Unfortunately, about a week ago,
he took an overdose of
designer drugs at the Viper Room.
He died on the kerb outside.
And now, we're left
with a hair lipped reminder
of what might have been.
Hi. Welcome
back from commercials.
Joaquin Phoenix, if
you're still watching,
you are a good sport and a trooper.
And you passed our test,
and you can be our friend.
And now for a segment
we like a little less than
the first and the last ...
Here's "Misery."
Marcia, I've done it!
I've finished the book
and Snuggly Jeff is dead
and the readers
are just gonna love it.
Paul, I still wish I
could talk you out of this.
Snuggly Jeff is the most
succesful children's book series ever.
Yeah, but I wanna get
into writing more serious stuff.
Y'know, something where
the reader doesn't have a load in
his pants while he's lookin' at it.
Well, we'll talk about
it when you get back.
This just in ...
The Weather Service has
reported a big snow storm on its way.
Oh, my God!
Stephen King!
Aaaaahhhh!!!
Hey, this'd make a neat story!
Done!
I'm your number one fan.
O-o-o-o-o-h-h-h ...
Who ... wh-who are you?
I'm Stewie Wilkes.
I saved your life.
You were in a terrible car accident
and you broke both your legs.
I taste lipstick!
Am I wearing lipstick?
Not any more.
Um, Paul, quick question,
and feel free to say no,
but I couldn't help but notice
the new Snuggly Jeff manuscript
in your bag, and, I was
wondering if I could read it
then kill you if I hate it?
Well, I guess that'd be OK.
Oh, thankyou, thankyou, thankyou!
Can I read it while I touch
your ear and suck my thumb?
Uh, I guess.
Oh, goody, goody!
Stewie?
I just finished the
book, you dirty birdy!
How could you?
He can't be dead!
Snuggly Jeff cannot be dead!
Aaaaaarrrr!!
Look, Stewie, I've gone as
far as I can with Snuggly Jeff,
and I .. I wanna
write something more serious
Well, you are gonna write
Snuggly Jeff back to life, Mr. Man.
Look, Stewie, first of all,
you're insane.
And second of all, I have
to be inspired before I write.
Well, how 'bout a little TV?
We now return to Magnum B.M.
Magnum, I've found a fingerprint
smudge at the crime scene.
Do you have poo on your hands?
A little.
No, no, no!
This won't do, Paul.
You can't just have Snuggly Jeff
magically brought back to life
by a child's wish.
It's insulting to the reader!
What do you mean?
Well, it's just bad story telling.
Let's see ... How
can I explain this to you?
Did you ever see the movie Contact?
Yeah.
So, like, they spent a trillion dollars
building this mile high space machine
and Jake Busey blows it up.
So, now they're all like:
"Oh, no. We can't
use the space machine"
But then this other guy's like:
"Hey, it just so happens,
"I built another identical
trillion dollar space machine
at my own expense,
on the other side of the world"
And we're supposed to believe
no-one noticed that?
Well, I stood up in the theatre and I said:
"No! You can't go into space
because the machine
already got blown up
by Jake Cock-a-Doody Busey!"
Start over!
Fine. But you're
gonna have to go into town
and get me some more paper.
I'm all out.
Uh, I don't know, Paul
Let me see if I can
get the Big Wheels started.
Rurrr, rurr, rurr, rurr.
Oh, I don't know, Paul. It's not starting.
Oh, I'm afraid I'm gonna flood it.
Rurrr, rurr, rurr, rurr.. Vrooooom!
Vrooooom! Vrooooom!
OK. I got it now.
I'll see you in a bit.
Heh heh. He's too big for that car.
Mr. Sheldon?
Oh, my God! I'm saved!
Let's get outta here
before Stewie gets back!
Ah! My legs!
Now I'm gonna have to spend
the rest of my life in a wheelchair!
No you're not.
Well, that's it, Stewie.
The book is done.
Can I go now?
Oh, no, Paul. I'm not stupid.
If I let you go, you'll
just run straight to the police
and tell them I kidnapped
you and held you hostage
and fondled you
while you were asleep.
No, I ...wait ...What?
You'll tell them that
while you were sleeping
I did things to you
that you don't remember.
You .. fondled me
while I was asleep?
Yeah.
I don't think I like that.
Well, it's done.
Everybody still awake?
Alright. Big finish.
Now, you remember
that Stephen King story
when the guy went
up to the empty hotel
and there were those creepy twins
and a guy was
runnin' around with that axe
and a kid talked to his finger?
Ah ha, can't you see Stewie doin' that?
Well, here's
"The Shawshank Redemption"
The first time I
laid eyes on Andy Dufresne
I didn't think much of him.
He was a fat drink of water,
the kind of drink of
water that y'know your friend
got from the bathroom
and not from the kitchen.
5 packs of cigarettes says the
fat one breaks first tonight.
You're on. I'll take the
Don Martin looking one.
A month went by before
Andy said 2 words to somebody.
As it turned out,
that somebody was me.
Vagina, boob.
Later, Andy came back
with more than 2 words.
I understand you're a man
who knows how to get things.
I've been known to procure
various and sundry items.
I .. I .. I don't
understand what you just said.
I need stuff.
Can you get it?
What do you need?
I need a rock hammer.
What's it for?
I carve Star Wars
figurines outta stone
but it's also for not
tunneling my way outta here.
Wow. Can you carve me a set of
women's private parts out of stone?
Sure.
Or you could just
have sex with Helen Hunt.
- Ah ha ha ha ha ha!
- Ha ha ha ha haa!
Ah, we've only had one conversation
but I can tell we're
gonna be life long friends.
And since you're
black and I'm white
that makes it more
especial for the audience.
Inspection!
You Andy Dufresne?
A little bit. You?
Ah ha ha ha ha!
I'm just tweakin' your bum.
What can I do for you?
I understand you
make Star Wars figurines.
Oh, Grievous! Wicked!
Well, anyway, I'm
a pretty corrupt guy
so I figured I could sell your
figurines and pocket the cash.
What d'ya say?
I don't know ...
Oh, come on!
I'll even cripple that guy
who rapes you in the shower.
But I like that guy.
Too late!
Ah, my legs!
Two things never happened again
after that.
Boggs never walked again,
and Andy's farts
never made a sound again.
Thanks to the Star
Wars figurines Andy carved,
he landed a cushy job
cleanin' the warden's office.
OK, you clean up the warden's office
while I go pop out a pine cone.
Plays "Hollaback Girl"
by Gwen Stefani
To this day, I have no idea what
that woman was singin' about.
Like, literally, no idea.
I don't know what a hollaback girl is.
But I have to imagine
it's a foul disease ridden thing
that wears too much makeup
to cover up the fact
that it's a 47 year old fish dog.
Andy, I think you know why
I've called you in here today.
A prison is an
environment which requires
the highest level of discipline ...
and that little stunt you pulled today
.. that little stunt you pulled today
made a lot of
people look very foolish.
Look, warden ..
we got it rough in here
I just thought we
could use a little music.
Music is expressly
forbidden inside prison walls!
My God! How can you be so obtuse?
What did you call me?
Obtuse. You're bein' obtuse.
Two months in the hole!
Or am I being obtuse?
Nope, now you're bein' acute.
That time in the
hole changed ol' Andy.
I'm gettin' outta here tonight, Red.
I'm gonna take the
poop pipe to the crap swamp.
Wow. Where you
headed once you get out?
Zihuatanejo.
Sounds fancy.
Eh, actually, it's
a filthy Mexican village.
Listen, Red
when you get outta here,
I want you to do somethin' for me.
Up in a hayfield in Buxton,
Maine, under an old oak tree,
there's a rock that has
no earthly business bein' there.
Under that rock is a box with
somethin' I want you to have.
Course, now that I think about
it, I've been in her 25 years
All these landmarks are based
on possibly outdated observations.
That whole area could
be a Wal-Mart by now.
If it is, pick yourself
up some nice cheap pants
and good life to you.
Inspection!
Dufresne? Dufresne!
Dufresne, you better get
your arse out here before
here before you make
me cut this sentence shor ....
Where is he?
Where the hell is Dufresne?
I don't know, Sir.
I want him found ... now.
Not after breakfast
Not after C.S.I.
Now!
God, I'm so angry
I could just throw a rock
at that poster of David Cassidy.
What the warden and
his boys didn't realise was
that Andy Dufresne had
escaped from Shawshank Prison
the night before.
Andy crawled to freedom
through 500 yards of foulness
I can't even imagine.
Andy Dufresne,
the man who crawled
through a river of poop
and came out clean on the other side.
Why he chose enchilada night,
I will never know.
Do you believe,
in your best judgement,
that you have been rehabilitated?
Rehabilitated?
It's just a stupid made up word
so boys like you
can sit behind a desk,
wear a fancy suit,
and feel important.
You're a jerk! And I had
sex with your mother last night!
And I swear to God,
you let me out of here,
first thing I'm
gonna do is kill again.
When I got outta Shawshank,
there was only one thing on my mind.
A promise I made to
a friend that I had to keep.
Walk along the stone wall
until you reach the tree,
and that's where
you'll find the rock.
Dear Red,
If you've come this far,
maybe you're
willing to go a little further.
You remember the name
of the town in Mexico, right?
Crap!
What? Oh! Oh, is that him?
Is that..? No, no, beach dog.
Oh! Oh! Is that Red?
Is it? No, no. Not him either.
Where the hell is that jagoff?
There's like 1200 bucks in that box.
Oh, my God,
if he ran off with that ...
Oh, I am gonna be so pissed!
And what am I gonna do?
Go to the authorities?
I just broke out of prison.
Now, what? I gotta spend the
rest of my life here by myself?
Well, at least I won't have to be
self conscious about my farting.
Well, that's our show.
Thank you, Stephen King.
We'll see you in court.
Now stay tuned for whatever FOX
is limpin' to the barn with.
Subtitles by Keef
www.tvsubtitles.net