Translated By The Community Of WWW.MY-SUBS.COM
We interrupt this program
with a special report.
Quahog is seeing its worst
flu epidemic in years,
due in part to a severe
shortage of flu shots.
Let's go live to Asian flu
correspondent Tricia Takanawa, Tricia?
Diane, I'm...
Thank you, Tricia. We now return
you to Robin, Boy Wonder.
Hey, don't worry. I'm here.
Robin? They sent you?
Yeah. Everyone else was busy so,
uh, they sent me.
What the hell are you going to do?
You don't have any superpowers.
Uh, I... got a cell phone.
Oh, no bars.
All right, who's next for a flu shot?
Oh, that's me, I'm, uh, I'm Peter Griffin.
Mr. Griffin, these flu shots
are in short supply.
We need to save them for the elderly.
- Like these folks here.
- Oh. Okay.
Well, I guess I'll be heading out
then and... Whoa!
Oh, look at that.
Oh, well, since it's already in there,
you might as well,
push down on the ol' plunger there.
You're a monster.
You know what was a monster?
Frampton Comes Alive, 1976.
Is there anyone you knew who didn't
have that record? I don't think so.
Bam!
All right, have a good winter.
Very well, Mr. Griffin,
you got your flu shot.
Now, if you'll just sign here...
- Hmm, well, this is odd.
- What?
Well, you're 42 years old and it says
here you've never had a prostate exam.
No, but I've had other exams.
Like that one in college.
Damn it, this is too hard!
Here's what I think of your test,
Mr. Teacher.
You just stood up to me.
Congratulations.
That was the test.
Heaven helps the man
who fights his fear.
Okay, heart sounds good.
All right, Mr. Griffin, I'm just going
to need you to drop your pants
and we'll check your prostate.
Uh, what?
Drop your pants, turn around,
and lean forward.
Um, okay.
So, how's this work,
you just feel my pulse or...
What the hell was that?
Mr. Griffin, that's a prostate exam.
Shut up!
You had your finger in my ass!
That's how a prostate exam is performed.
- Now, if you'll just let me...
- Get away from me!
Ugh. Get a tan.
Peter, my God, you look terrible.
What happened?
I was raped.
What?
Dr. Hartman violated me.
He took my innocence.
Wh-What?
Peter, that's a prostate exam.
It's an important part of a
physical for men your age.
You sound just like him!
idiot.
Hey, Peter, buddy.
How 'bout some TV, huh?
We now return to:
Freddy got fingered.
Oh, God.
- Oh, God.
- ... Yellow Pages.
Let your fingers do the walking.
Are we still going to the baseball game?
Get that away from me, Chris.
Stop it, Meg.
Peter...
I'm trying to be supportive
but after all, it was just a prostate exam.
You weren't there, Lois.
You weren't there.
Who's that?
Who are you?
Where's Peter?
Where is he?
You're a whore.
Wear your whore makeup, you whore.
- Is somebody in there?
- Ocupado.
Filthy whore.
You're somebody's father, you filthy whore.
- Hi, sweetie.
- Ugh, look at her staring.
What are you looking at, huh?
God, I should take her out right here
with these, man.
Oh, hey, Lois. Oh, you like staring?
Oh, why don't I give you a closer look?
Yeah, you want some of this,
Maury Po-bitch?
Oh, oh, what's that, oh,
you come back for more, huh?
I'd freakin' drop her ass.
Oh, an unfamiliar dog.
Why don't you go away?
I don't want to be your friend.
Rupert!
Oh, dear God, somebody help!
R upert!
Give me that bear!
Oh, honey, I'm afraid
Rupert had a little injury.
Oh, Rupert, please live.
Please, I'll never be short with you again.
W- We'll go away. W-We'll go to Hawaii.
Would you like that?
I always envisioned how it would be.
I never knew there could be
such a thing as a perfect day.
Don't frolic too much, Rupert.
Save some energy for the hula contest.
Stewie, I have a surprise for you.
Good as new.
Rupert, it's really him.
I don't believe it.
You-you did this for me?
And to help you feel better,
I made your favorite dinner.
Cut green beans...
Atkins-friendly potato sticks arranged
according to size from largest to smallest,
and a Scooby-Doo yogurt with
Shaggy's eyes scratched out.
Oh, it's perfect down to the last detail.
Lois, I was wrong about you.
You're...
you're my everything.
Mommy loves you, sweetheart.
Stewie loves Lois.
Brian loves Olympia Dukakis.
Oh, yeah, I do.
Peter, what's the matter with you today?
You're not yourself.
Guys, I went to Dr. Hartman
yesterday and...
he did things to my fanny.
- Peter, it's okay.
- It's not okay.
- You don't know what it's like.
- You're wrong.
I, too, have felt the cold finger of injustice
on my insidey parts.
He did it to you, too?
I have something to say.
Dr. Hartman violated me, as well.
I only went in there
for a physical-slash-guinea pig sremoval,
but I turned out to be the guinea pig,
for a sexual experimentation.
You guys are a bunch of queers.
And so am I!
Oh, God, it was horrible!
I scrubbed and I scrubbed, but damn it,
they don't make water hot enough!
My God, we've all been victims
of Dr. Hartman's "prostate exam. "
Well, gentlemen, the abuse stops here.
I will not turn a brown eye to this.
I am going to sue that bastard
and make him pay out the ass.
No ifs, ands, or buts.
I'm going to be really anal about this.
Sphincter.
Good morning, Lois.
My, Stewie, you're in a good mood today.
Well, why shouldn't I be?
You saved Rupert's life and I love you for it.
So warn the villagers,
here comes the cuddle monster.
Oh, Lois, your breasts are great.
Well, good morning, Mr. Nipple.
Hey, there.
Must be cold in here.
Peter, you're going to sue Dr. Hartman?
You can't do that, all he did was
give you a prostate exam.
Are you saying I asked
for this to happen?
You know, Dad, there's this lawyer at
the mall who says he'll take any case,
- no matter how frivolous.
- Yeah, yeah...
and-and they also have an Orange Julius.
Just-just trying to keep
the conversation going.
Well, whatever happens,
I'm not going to stand for this.
Too many people get away with injustice.
Like the folks you meetin
those Louisiana swamps.
Excuse me,
do you know how to get to town?
Yeah, it's back the way you came.
I love you, Lois.
You know that, right?
Just in case, I'll say it again.
I love you.
Oh, you are just so cute, sweetie.
Look at that little foot.
I'm gonna eat that foot.
Give me that foot, it looks delicious.
Don't-don't eat my foot.
Oh, God.
Oh, it is so hard to find funny women,
and you are hilarious.
Oh, you're like a female Bonnie Hunt.
Sit right there, honey. Mommy'll go get
Rupert so he can eat with you.
Oh, God. Thoughtful.
- Lois, I made coffee if you want some.
- Oh, thank you, Brian. That'd be nice.
Uh, hey, Brian.
Uh, listen, I've got a favor to ask.
Could you, uh, could you
not talk to Lois anymore?
What?
You know, it's just I'm tired of you
hitting on her. That's all, it's-it's not cool.
I was just making coffee.
I didn't hit on her.
Besides, Lois is my friend.
I'll do whatever the hell I want.
I'm asking you nicely, Brian.
Stop hitting on her.
- That's ridiculous.
- I see the way you look at her.
Sorry, I fell asleep watching
Sabado Gigante last night.
Chiste grande.
Lois, you know what
we should do right now?
We should play restaurant
with my Play-Doh.
I'll make you a hamburger.
Perhaps I'll make it blue.
Oh, can you imagine such a world?
Uh, Stewie, I love you,
but you're wearing Mommy out.
- Now it's time for bed.
- Hey, Lois, I have a secret for you.
You're awesome.
Our top story: a local woman
loses her sex drive
after a $125 dinner at Alfredo's.
But first in medical news, Dr. Elmer Hartman,
beloved family doctor to all of Quahog,
is the target of a molestation lawsuit.
The trial is set to begin tomorrow.
We now return you to
Native American What's Happening!
Hey, Rerun, you see Dwayne?
Not today.
Oh, here he come.
How, how, how.
Peter, I don't know
how much more I can take.
Stewie used to be so independent,
but now he just clings to me night and day.
I'm exhausted.
Oh, look at me, I'm Lois.
The sun revolves around me.
I'm the one who's got
to go to court tomorrow.
Peter, isn't there anything I can do
to talk you out of this lawsuit?
Hey, I was violated sexually
and that man is going to pay.
And I suppose it wouldn't matter
if I told you for the 50th time
that it's a legitimate medical
procedure to test for cancer.
Lois.
Mom.
Mommy.
Mama.
Ma.
Mum.
Mummy.
M um-ma.
Mum-ma.
- Mum-ma.
- What?!
Hi.
Is it not true that you went
to see Dr. Hartman
for a simple prostate exam?
No, I went for a flu shot.
At first, I thought he was nice
and that he was kind of handsome.
I trusted him
and then, he told me to bend over.
And then, I just felt like something was wrong.
I tried to get him to stop,
but he kept saying,
"Relax, I'm a doctor. "
- This is ridiculous, that never happened.
- Sit down, you rapist!
Oh, I'm sorry. I'm supposed to wait
until I've heard everything.
Go ahead, Mr. Griffin.
And that's when things got bad.
He made me feel so dirty.
Relax...
I'm a doctor.
Your Honor, I can't believe
you're even listening to this.
For God's sake, you're a patient of mine.
I gave you a prostate exam last year,
don't you remember?
Come to think of it,
I remember it as a pretty standard exam.
Are you sure, Judge?
Are you sure it wasn't all evil and grainy
and black and white? Think about it.
Relax.
I be a doctor.
Guilty, guilty, guilty, guilty!
Dr. Hartman, your medical license
is hereby revoked.
That's outrageous!
God, I've looked forward to this moment
more than the second coming of Jesus.
Okay, everybody, uh,
I know you were expecting something else,
but as science will tell you,
people were a lot shorter 2,000 years ago.
So let's try to be adult about this.
Uh, no snickering and... Hey!
That's exactly what I'm talking about.
Okay, so if we can all be mature...
give me the gum,
we can all get through this a lot faster.
I have so much fun
when we hang out, Lois,
and I love your hair.
We should make up a name
for your hair color.
We could call it, like, like,
strawberry sunset
or ginger maiden,
o- o-or-or one of those hair color names
that's a random noun, like
like temptress.
Oh, at some point,
you have to let me braid it!
Lois, what are you doing?
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, what's happening to me?
I'm like that Texas woman
who gave her son brain damage
by holding him underwater.
I'm just like Barbara Bush!
Brian, what kind of a mother
has homicidal thoughts
about her own baby?
I'm a horrible person.
Lois, you're just exhausted.
Somehow, you've got to break Stewie
of this new over dependence on you.
Well, it's worth a try.
Lois, I've got a surprise for you.
You and I are going to see Eddie Money!
Two tickets, won'em on the radio.
We're gonna have a ball.
God, he's like a totally different person,
like Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Sulu.
Oh, no, I never should have
drank those chemicals.
Hello.
Peter, congratulations on taking down
that monster Dr. Hartman.
Yeah, what'd you do with
your pain and suffering money?
I got collagen.
Hey, Lois, want to make out?
Yeah, what do you think
of new sexy lips Peter?
Yeah.
This is your life from now on.
Enjoy it, lucky wife.
I tell you, boys, this is a victory
not just for my anus but for anuses...
Oh, hang on, I got to go pee.
That's a lot better. So, anyway, this is a...
Oh, I got to take a leak.
There we go.
Oh, pee time.
Peter, you're urinating unusually frequently.
Yeah, what gives?
If it's gale-force peeing you be doing,
it could mean you've got
barnacles on your prostate.
Best have sick bay check below your decks.
Wait a minute. Are you telling me
I need a prostate exam?
Aye, and soon,
before your rudder jams with flotsam
and you're dropping anchor
without an order from the captain.
How are you liking
all these nautical puns?
- Cute. - Not bad.
- Somewhat entertaining.
My God, I'd better see a doctor.
But no doctor in town
will see you after that lawsuit.
Well, then, I'll just find
a doctor out of town.
Listen, uh, I know
I'm not a regular patient,
but I think I have some
trouble with my prostate.
- So can you help me out, Dr. McCoy?
- What, so you can sue me, too?
- Oh, come on, it'll only take a sec.
- Forget it. I'm a doctor, not a patsy.
Hello.
Lois, what are you doing?
I want to sleep in your bed.
Good night, honey.
I love you.
This is for your own good.
Lois, wh-wh-where are you going?
Lois... Lois.
Lois, answer me!
Damn you, I will not be ignored!
Get back in here!
Get back in here and love me!
Lois!
Maybe I should go in. He's so upset.
He's just being melodramatic. You've got
to ignore it if you really want to help him.
- Are you flexing?
- What, me?
Ha, no.
Wha... why-why would I be flexing?
I mean, I have, uh,
sort of been hitting the gym,
so uh, if-if you wanted
to see how it's going...
What am I going to do, Seamus?
Dr. Hartman is my only hope,
and there's no way he's going to see me.
Well, you best come up
with something, Peter.
Otherwise, this will happen
to your prostate.
You just, uh, carry a picture
of a diseased prostate around with you?
Never know when it's going
to come up in conversation
and then, who's the
one who's prepared?
I've also got a map of Middle Earth,
a cat doing a pull-up,
and the guys from Primus.
These poster jokes
doing anything for you?
- Eh, hit and miss.
- We should hang out more.
I need her love.
I need her love, and she's ignoring me.
Well, let's see her try to ignore this.
Lois, help!
I ate this whole jar of pills that
look like candy and now I feel sick.
- You look like a jackass.
- Can't hear you, Brian. I'm dead.
All right.
What did you do?
Oh, that is so not cool.
Mommy, I'm dying!
I'm dying!
I said I'm dying!
Hey!
I'm dyin'up here.
What is this? A Tommy Lee pool party?
Come on, Lois, get with the...
Oh, my God.
Stewie, are you all right?
Oh, my sweet baby.
And to think I ignored your cries
for attention. I'm so sorry, honey.
Never again, Stewie. I'm going to give
you all the love you could ever want.
Forget it, you neglectful,
swag-bellied measle.
You had your chance and you blew it.
Well, now you're too late.
I hope they charge you with
child abuse for my broken arm.
I'll testify against you
just like I did against Michael Jackson.
Stewie, did Mr. Jackson behave
inappropriately toward you?
Well, yes, but the worst part
was he never called back.
No, but in all seriousness, yeah,
he was actually pretty aggressive.
- Uh, package for Dr. Hartman?
- All right, where's the package?
Here it is.
Uh, so why don't you go ahead and
open it up and reach on in there?
It's probably cookies or something.
Wait a minute, there's
something strange about this.
I wasn't expecting any package.
Who are you?
Griffin!
You got to help me, Dr. Hartman.
I think there may actually be
something wrong with my prostate.
Well, don't look at me.
I lost my license, thanks to you.
Look, I-I know what I did was wrong, but
you're the only one I can turn to.
So, I'm asking you...
as a man with no more options...
will you take a look in my ass?
Despite everything that's happened,
I suppose I can't ignore
my Hippocratic oath.
All right, drop your pants.
Oh, well, this is nothing. Just a little
swelling. Probably a minor infection.
Looks like there's some blockage.
What the devil is that?
Hello.
Dr. Hartman,
your license is hereby reinstated.
Oh, I'm so glad you two
worked things out.
And to think I actually thought
you raped me.
Well, I was going to,
but you ran out of the room.
What?
Family Guy was recorded on tape
before a live audience.