WWW.MY-SUBS.COM
It seems today that all you see
Is violence in movies and sex on TV
But where are those
good old-fashioned values
On which we used to rely?
Lucky there's a family guy
Lucky there's a man who
positively can do
All the things that make us
Laugh and cry
He's... a... Fam... ily... Guy!
- Synced and corrected by AlexandreMT -
- www.MY-SUBS.com
Ugh. I can't believe
you dragged me to The Flow.
- This is gonna suck.
- Oh, knock it off.
It's not gonna be that bad.
Besides, I couldn't leave you at home.
Last time I did that,
the kids walked in on you
looking at Internet corn.
Oh, God, what I wouldn't do to that.
What? N-No! No, it's not even mine!
I just clicked on it!
And c-come on,
it's not like it's gay corn.
It's gay corn.
It was baby corn.
Hi, ladies, and welcome to The Flow!
We'll be starting the taping
in just a few minutes,
but I wanted to come out here personally
and say hi to my fans.
Let's get everyone up, up, up
and dancing like maniacs.
First down.
Let's welcome our first guest,
my colleague at Channel 5
and now a best-selling author,
Tricia Takanawa.
So, Tricia, tell us about your book.
I understand it's been
number one on Amazon
for many weeks, long time.
It's called Throw It Away:
The Life-Improving Art of De-cluttering.
People nowadays own too much stuff.
I am encouraging them to throw it away.
Genius! So just throw everything out?
Not quite.
If it kindles joy, you keep it.
But if no joy, you throw it away.
Can I look at your phone?
No. Use your activity book.
I already did
all the fun ones at church.
It's very simple.
I came up with it after hiking
to the top of Mount Asia
and meditating on Epiphany Bridge.
Ah! Peter, these are Asian techniques,
and they're new to me.
I have to buy this book,
read two chapters,
then leave it on my nightstand
for a year.
That fart was the lady next to me.
Whatever. I'm getting that book, Peter.
And it's for reading,
not for killing spiders.
Oh, don't worry, Lois.
I got a better method
for doing that now.
I'm really excited
you're humanely relocating me
to outside your house.
Oh, yeah. Me and the fellas
thought it was time.
♪
Oh, no...
Kids! Peter! Get down here!
Everyone, I just read
Tricia Takanawa's book,
and it was really inspiring.
She says that when you
de-clutter your house,
you de-clutter your mind and
clear a path to true happiness.
How about a clear path to dinner, bitch.
So I want everyone to go through
every single item you own,
and if it doesn't kindle joy,
throw it away.
See?
This sweater, it's okay,
but it doesn't kindle joy.
I'm throwing it out.
Now, get to it.
Wow, she's really all in on this.
Well, she's searching for something
to fill her empty life.
You remember when
she thought the solution
was putting a lemon slice
in a plain glass of water
for a "very simple kind of pleasure"?
Ah. Perfection.
And just the thing
to wash down six Xanax
from four different prescriptions.
Mmm.
Tomorrow, this will seem
like a new idea again.
Oh, my voodoo doll of Mom.
Yeah, totally throw.
It never worked, anyway.
Ow! What the hell was that?!
Oh. Keep.
Box of cords that go to
computers from the 1980s.
Keep.
$70,000 in Camel Cash.
I should've pulled the trigger
on that umbrella. Keep.
Woody and Buzz,
who definitely are not alive,
so I can turn my back... on them!
Well, I guess they passed the test.
They're really... not alive!
Peter, what are you doing up there?
Oh, nothing, Lois.
I was just making sure
I kept my Woody and Bu...
I knew it.
Peter, there's nothing
in your throwaway pile.
I know. I'm keeping everything.
- Everything kindles joy!
- That can't be true.
Even this old tin can on a string?
I mean, what are you
even doing with this?
You're a grown man!
Why would you possibly need this?
If anything is garbage, this is garbage.
Sounds like things aren't going well
- at the Griffins.
- This is why no girls allowed.
I hate to do this, guys,
but Peter's been compromised.
Oh, look, my box of ribbons I've
saved from various presents.
Oh, I'm not throwing that out.
That's a good ribbon.
This is a good ribbon, too.
These are all very usable ribbons.
Hey, little guy.
How's the sorting going?
I'm not getting rid of my ribbons!
I just wanted to know
if I could borrow a ribbon.
If you love Game of Thrones on HBO,
you'll love Cinemax's Boob Dragons.
Series pass. Record all. Priority one.
Peter, that's, like, your 50th bag.
What could possibly be in there?
- Oh. Have you not heard?
- Brian, no!
Well, everybody's... 'bout the bird
Bird, bird, bird
Bird is the... bird, bird...
Wait a minute, didn't we destroy that?
I glued it.
"Surfin' Bird," uh, uh, uh,
finds a way.
I love it!
Perfect!
Ah-ha-ha!
So, Lois, what's your next
"bored housewife seeking
purpose in life" project
after de-cluttering?
Vegan baking? Handmade soaps on Etsy?
Whoa. You drunk already, bro?
What's your next fake writing project,
a rap opera about Grover Cleveland?
No, Lois, that would be ridiculous.
Mine is a '70s funk musical
about William Howard Taft.
Who's the big fat president
Whose suits look like
a flannel circus tent?
Taft
Right on
Who's that presidential chub
Got stuck in the White House tub?
William Howard Taft
They say this cat Taft
Is a fat mother...
Shut your mouth
I'm just talkin' 'bout Taft
And we can dig it.
Ah.
Ah, so good to be home.
Since when do you surf?!
Oh, I don't. I just
rolled around in the sand
and brought home
this bucket of alive crabs.
When the clutter is gone,
the path to happiness is clear.
Lois, you could just pee in
these like a space suit, right?
Peter... you don't kindle joy.
- What?
- I'm sorry,
but I'm looking at you,
and I'm just not feeling joy.
What... what are you saying?
Peter...
I don't think I can have you
in the house right now.
You're throwing me away?
Yes.
I'm so sorry, Peter.
I just feel like
if you don't kindle joy...
And that's what the book said...
You can't kick me out of my own house.
The house that I pay for?
That I semi-pay for
with help from your parents?
That your parents pay for entirely,
but I get to put the
mortgage coupon in the mailbox?
That your parents pay for entirely
using autodraft from their account
while I put a pretend mortgage
coupon that clearly says
"Not legal tender" into the mailbox?
That your parents pay for entirely
using autodraft from their account
while I put a pretend
mortgage coupon that says
"Not legal tender" into
Stewie's Sesame Street mailbox?
That your parents pay for entirely
using autodraft from their account
while Chris puts a pretend
mortgage coupon that says
"Not legal tender" into
Stewie's Sesame Street mailbox
while I hold the plastic door
open for him?
That your parents pay for entirely...
- Peter, we get it.
- Okay.
What's happening again?
I'm asking you to leave the house.
The house that I pay for?
Thanks for letting me
crash here, Quagmire.
No problem, Peter.
I'm sure Lois'll cool down
in a few days, and you'll be back home.
Yeah, she'll be fine. And you
won't even know I'm here.
I mean, I need to keep up
with my workouts.
And I can't sleep unless I have
Dunkirk on at full volume.
But, yeah, this'll be great.
Hi, kids. Do you need those hats?
- I mean...
- It's the foundation of my look,
but we can discuss it.
I feel like they're clutter.
I feel like you don't need them.
L-Let's just see
what you look like without...
Whoa! You kids are Legos?
Sorry you had to find out this way, Mom.
Oh. Hi, Brian. You're carrying clutter,
I'll just throw it out.
Ha! A clean house means a clean soul,
and a clean soul is a happy one.
That was a whole pizza.
And I didn't even start eating it yet.
You're surprised about a pizza?
She threw out a whole guy.
Yeah, Lois might be starting to lose it.
Even her cutaways are getting
a little too minimalist.
Have you noticed?
Donald Trump's hair is unusual.
Oh, hey, don't use the toilet.
I'm making wine.
Peter, you got to get out.
The truth is I should have
asked you to leave
after the other night.
- Hello?
- Quagmire?
Yeah?
I can't sleep.
So?
What do you want me to do?
Will you read me a story?
Peter, I-I'm-I'm in the middle
of something here.
- Like, maybe a Clifford?
- Peter, get out of here!
- Clifford?
- No! Not now!
Quagmire, Clifford now?
Ugh! Just read him the story.
"Clifford was just too big
for the bathtub."
- Isn't he big, Peter?
- Clifford big!
"So they decided
to hose him in the yard instead,
but Clifford couldn't fit
through the door."
See that, Peter?
Finally. All right, ladies,
I guess we can...
Wouldn't you know it.
Oh, my God,
they took the whole roof off.
Everybody thinks they can kick me out?
Well, who gets the last laugh now?
I get to sleep with all my stuff
in a storage unit
on the highway access road.
Okay, can't go to bed till you make one.
All right, just got to make one.
I'm going to sleep.
Something bad's gonna happen
if you don't do it.
Meg! Chris!
What the (BLEEP) is this?
- I've never seen it before.
- I don't know.
Stewie, she's got your time machine.
Well, don't drag that
down the stairs or else...
Thank God, everything's back to normal.
Pe-tew. Gross.
I tell you to clean your rooms,
and the first thing you do
is put all your science projects
in Stewie's closet?
- Mom, we didn't...
- Stop arguing and get rid of it.
And give me those glasses.
They're cluttering up your face.
- I need them to see.
- They're not bringing me joy!
You realize there are four of us
and one of her.
- If we rushed her all at once...
- That's not gonna work.
She's clearly developed
the strength of the insane.
- What did you say, Chris?
- Uh, nothing. I'm sorry!
Chris, I will not have
your comic strip anger
cluttering up my house.
It's negative, and it ruins my joy.
- Get it out of here!
- Now you've done it.
You've made me 1930s work whistle angry!
Shut up, Meg!
- What? I didn't say anything.
- You just did.
Your voice... it's cluttering up
my space. Get out.
- But...
- Get out of my house!
You know, Lois, one could argue
that your bra is clutter.
Nice try, dirtbag. Leave.
Figured it was gonna happen, anyway.
Might as well go out on my terms.
♪
I cluttered my pants.
It did not kindle joy.
Well, that does it.
I got rid of all the clutter.
I made order out of chaos,
And it's beautiful.
Ah, there's even an echo in here now.
I'm so happy!
I'm very unhappy!
My house is at peace, so I am at peace.
You're all alone and sad.
Simplicity is good for the soul.
Your soul is as empty as this house,
this house, this house.
But I did what the book said.
I did it all.
Why didn't it work?
Why am I still not happy?
What have I done?
Looks like there's only
one thing left to get rid of.
The mirror.
- Look. Towels!
- They don't even match.
Who cares? They're still thirsty.
She's not here. Come on.
Wow. Everything's gone.
What's that?
"Words, letters, letters and words,
mm-hmm, mm-hmm, more words and letters."
Chris, can't you read?
No, I know the letters
when they're on their own,
but, you know,
when they team up like this,
I'm just, uh... I'm sort of outmatched.
"It was my fault, not yours.
"I'm so sorry, and I love you all.
"Goodbye.
"P.S. Please throw this note out.
It is clutter."
Oh, my God. Where could she be?
You don't think
she killed herself, do you?
We're gonna need professional help.
I got to call Joe.
Hello?
Joe, are you in my kitchen?
No.
- What are you doing?
- Nothing.
Hey, Bon.
Did they have the French bread pizza?
Not a good time, Bon.
Well, she's dead. It's a suicide note.
It doesn't actually say
she's gonna end it.
Maybe she just took off somewhere.
I'll call Cleveland.
Maybe he saw something.
Hello?
Are you stealing my copper plumbing?
- No.
- What are you doing?
Nothing.
Hey, Donna.
Did you check the counter for Keurigs?
Not a good time, Don.
Dad, how can you be so sure
Mom is at Mount Asia?
We cut a whole scene
where we figured it out.
You got to just trust me.
Boy, feels like Rocky, huh?
- Huh?
- Okay!
Look! We're almost there!
♪
I don't even care
that I left my phone in my pocket.
I had too much. But then I had nothing.
But then that wasn't enough.
Lois!
Lois, don't do it!
♪
Wait. Is this really
'cause of all my stuff?
No, Peter, don't come any closer!
Please don't jump! Please!
I love you.
Lois!
Feels like Cliffhanger, huh?
Huh, Chris?
Okay!
- Mom!
- Oh, my God!
Lois, are you okay?
I'm fine!
I'm fine.
Everything's fine!
I was saved by garbage!
I'm garbage.
Everything's garbage,
and garbage is wonderful!
Oh, when Mommy's unstable,
I feel unsafe.
We're so glad you didn't kill yourself.
I wasn't gonna jump, you idiot.
I just came here to think.
You made me lose my balance,
but when I landed in all that garbage,
I realized it saved my life.
Literally, yes, but also
it saves my life every day.
The joy that you find in everything...
The fact that every little thing
you see kindles joy for you...
That's the right attitude, Peter.
And I'm gonna try to have
that attitude from now on.
- I love you.
- I love you, too, Lois.
Now let's go home.
I can't wait to sleep in my own bed.
Oh, just leave it for now.
We'll deal with it later.
Oh, okay. Thanks, Mom.
Yeah, that de-cluttering thing
was nice for a while,
but I definitely went overboard.
I don't know. Somehow, an idea
I got from a two-minute segment
on a morning talk show didn't
bring me the life satisfaction
I thought it would.
On the bright side, our sparse,
white living room looks like
the John Lennon, Yoko Ono
"Imagine" living room.
We can't afford "Imagine," so
just imagine this is "Imagine."
Boop-boop, deedle-Dee, Dee-Dee-Dee
Imagine, imagine
No religion, nothing matters
Everything is bad.