Translated By The Community Of WWW.MY-SUBS.COM
Oh, Peter, you're selling your anvil?
Yeah, I've had a lot of good times
with this thing.
Ooh! A dollar!
- Hey there, Chris.
- Hi, Mr. Herbert.
- Selling your old hand-me-downs?
- Yep.
You got anything you used
to wear in the summertime?
- Just these old shorts.
- Sweet Jesus.
- Give you a dollar for this.
- Sold.
Brian, where's Rupert?
I just left him here to watch my things.
- What?
- Uh, nothing, I haven't seen him.
It's not like him to wander off.
Rupert? Rupert!
Oh, no. What if he's been kidnapped?
- Well, let's just calm down...
- I've got to save him, Brian.
What if he's dead?
I don't think I can handle a funeral.
Of all the souls I have
encountered in my travels,
his was the most...
human.
Orders... hup!
Holy crap.
Evel Knievel gloves!
I bet I could do a wheelie with these!
How much for the gloves?
- Peter, those are yours.
- Ten bucks.
Two. Seven. Four. $5.50. Ten. Sold!
Sucker. I would've gone
to $15, easy. I am so stupid.
Awesome!
Peter, you can't drive the car over that.
You're gonna get hurt.
Lois, I don't come down to Burger King
and tell you how to do your job.
- Peter, I don't work at Burger...
- I don't work at burgaga... I'm busy.
Now if you'll excuse me,
I have some death to defy.
This is just like what happened with
Matthew Broderick, except no one's dead.
- Hey, Joe.
- Good morning, Peter.
- I'm here to revoke your driver's license.
- What?! Why?!
We got reckless driving,
disturbing the peace,
plus the driver of one of
the other cars was a virgin
whose hymen was busted
by the airbag, so rape.
Okay, well, I guess
you can take my license.
'Course it's all the way up here.
Peter, knock if off. Give it to me.
Give me the damn license.
This is in poor taste, Peter.
You're starting to piss me off.
You're starting to piss me off!
Aw, man, this sucks. I got no license.
I can't go anywhere.
Well, this is your own fault, Peter,
and if you want my opinion,
a little time away from the bar
will do you some good.
I'll show her.
I'll just go to another bar.
We now return to Cheers.
- Norm!
- And Peter! Yeah!
How's life in the fast lane, Mr. Peterson?
- Griffin.
- I can't find the on-ramp, Woody.
He was talking to me, Norm.
Quit stealing my punch lines,
you fat drunk.
That show stopped being funny after
Kirstie Alley ate Shelley Long.
Ah, man, now I can't even watch TV.
What the hell am I gonna do all day?
That's all right, that's okay.
I don't need TV.
I'll just make my own sitcom in my head.
And I'll give it
an upbeat '80s sitcom theme.
This time around, I'm staying at home.
And things are gonna get better.
Settlin' in, lovin' my wife.
But then I got that letter.
My Black Son, My Black Son.
Now each day my heart is getting bigger.
Don't even remember sleeping
with that lady, but I did.
My Black Son. He's coming to stay.
My Black Son. He's making each day...
The best that he can.
Also he's a ninja.
Why have you brought me
to the toy store, Brian?
I'm buying you another Rupert.
Hey, this one's cute, huh?
And if we buy it,
they save a real gorilla in the wild.
And if we don't, they kill one.
Wow, these guys are playing hardball.
You can't just take some Korean-made
velveteen primate and call it Rupert.
Now come on, this is all time we could
be using to find Rupert's kidnappers.
Look, I, uh...
I may as well come clean with you.
Rupert wasn't kidnapped.
I accidentally sold him at the yard sale.
You son of a bitch!
Come on, Stewie, I'm really sorry.
It was an accident.
Damn you, Brian.
How could you sell Rupert?
What you've done is more horrible
than sex with Sharon Stone.
Wow, that was great!
One minute I'm filling up at Chevron,
and the next I'm having sex
with Sharon Stone.
Yeah. Now comes the best part.
- Get out of the fridge, Peter.
- There is no Peter, only Zuul.
I said get out of the fridge!
All right, all right! Geez, Lois,
I'm just trying to amuse myself,
since I don't have a damn
driver's license.
Peter, it's getting a little annoying
having you around the house all the time.
So you'll be happy to know
I got you your own personal driver.
My own driver?! Holy crap,
that's awesome! Where is he?
- She's right here, Peter.
- Meg?!
Yeah, Dad. I don't mind driving you
around till you get your license back.
What?!
Lois, this is the best you could do?!
Well, it was either Meg
or a talking monkey smoking a cigar,
but I didn't you'd like that.
I've already accepted another job.
Lois, you picked the opposite
thing that I would like.
It's all right.
I would've driven you bananas.
Oh, oh, and he makes jokes.
Nice going, Lois.
Dad, are you ready?
- What exactly are you trying to do?
- It's very simple, Brian.
I've taken DNA from the dollar bill
you were paid for Rupert.
Now to check that DNA
against the federal database.
Ooh, we have a match!
Stanford Cordray, 89 Spooner Street.
That's only a few blocks away.
Let's go!
Hello? Hello?
It can't be.
This house is deserted.
He moved. He's gone.
Rupert's gone.
Wait a minute, look!
The moving truck.
We're not too late.
- Can I help you, gentlemen?
- Follow that truck.
Didn't you hear me?
I said, "Follow that truck. "
Oh, I heard you.
What I didn't hear was, "Please. "
Please follow the truck.
I always enjoy traveling companions.
Let's play 20 questions.
Am I Bo Bice? Yes, I am.
Well played, worthy adversary.
We're gaining on him!
I'm coming, Rupert!
- I'm sorry, but I can go no further.
- What?! Why not?!
If I enter Connecticut,
I'm entering every state
that Connecticut's ever been with.
Good luck, brave travelers.
No! We were so close!
I say, what a bit of serendipity.
Now we've got that fellow's address.
Let's see...
"Aspen, Colorado. "
Well, you can forget that.
We're not going all the way to Aspen.
What?!
But I can't leave Rupert to perish.
For the rest of my life,
I'll be as lonely
as Pat Robertson and Jerry Falwell
after the rapture.
Damn it, Jerry, why are
we the only ones still here?
I don't know, we hated
all the right things.
- Now there's nothing left to hate.
- I'm gonna hate that rock.
- No, I'm gonna hate that rock.
- Let's both hate that rock.
- I hate you.
- I hate you, too.
Look, Stewie,
don't you think, at some point,
you're gonna have to let Rupert go?
I mean, you are getting a
little old to have a teddy bear.
- Brian, I'm one!
- Still? What?
Look, I'm not going to Colorado.
I'm turning around and going home.
Fine, then, I'll go by myself.
See you from the back of my milk carton.
Want that on your conscience, Brian?
Try explaining this to Lois.
You'll wind up in a Dumpster with a
bunch of slow, unadoptable greyhounds.
Don't joke about that.
That's like the Holocaust to us.
Yeah, well, when greyhounds
start running The New York Times
and the World Bank,
I'll be more inclined to believe you.
Now, are you coming or not?
Fine.
Take to the highway
Won't you lend me your name...
- Who sings that song?
- James Taylor.
Yeah, let's keep it that way.
This sucks. Can you believe
I'm stuck with Meg driving me around?
Dad, it's just you and me in the car.
Don't remind me.
It's bad enough
I got a suspended license,
I gotta ride around town
with Stinky McPoop-Pants.
- I want apple juice.
- Dad, you left your apple juice at home.
I want apple juice!
- You want to watch SpongeBob?
- Yes.
With apple juice.
SpongeBob.
Thanks for the ride, Bandit.
Good luck tapping some of that
hot, hot Sally Field tail.
Knock it off. I don't like it
any more than you do.
Where the hell are we?
Oh, this is history right here, Brian.
Gettysburg. Billy Yanks. The 20th Maine.
So many lives lost.
All in pursuit of the ideal that no man
should be subjugated
because of the color of his skin.
These boys paid the ultimate price here.
For equality. For humanity.
- You're welcome.
- I'm sorry?
I'm just sayin', make it
worth our while, you know?
We wrote a pretty big check
for you folks here, so, um...
You know, whatever. It's fine. It's fine.
Doesn't matter. Just, uh... I...
Just hope you're making the best
of what we gave you here.
I would say that,
given the events that preceded it,
the couple hundred years or so,
maybe we're about even.
Yeah, no, no. We gave more.
Hey, Cleveland,
who would you rather do:
Queen Latifah or Halle Berry,
but she's been dead for six hours?
Aw, man.
That's a tough one.
God, will you guys
just shut up back there?!
Aah! Gross!
Would you stop it? Stop it!
Hey, guys, check this out.
Hey, Meg, don't be such a hothead.
What?!
Hey, Meg, you sure look hot today.
Hey, Meg, I lit your scalp on fire.
Don't worry, I'll put it out.
What the hell is your problem,
you dumb bimbo?!
Oh, oh, God, stop!
Meg, that was awesome.
If we wanna get to Aspen, we're gonna
have to get over those mountains somehow.
Excuse me, uh, how much is it
to rent a helicopter?
It's ten bucks an hour.
But there's a $100,000 deposit.
Oh, God.
Looks like we're walking.
Wait a minute, it says here
you accept cash, check or a jaunty tune.
Well, this rental agreement
was drafted back
when musicals were culturally relevant.
Unfortunately, that's no longer the case.
Well, I can prove to you
that's a whole lot of nonsense.
You may think that song and dance
is dated boring and dry.
<>But you might just learn to
like it if you give it a try.
You could laugh and sing and dance
as gaily as an elf.
But just in case you don't believe me,
ask the man himself.
Mr. Kelly?
Will you show us?
- I'll show you.
- Let's do it.
- Good. One, two, three, four.
- One, two, three, four.
- One, two, three.
- La, la, la, la, la, la.
- You see?
- It's easy.
Look at me! I'm dancing!
Okay, you can have the helicopter.
Brian, be careful 'cause the mountains
are the same color as the sky.
What?
I said, be careful 'cause the mountains
are the same color as the...
- What the hell was that?
- I'm practicing my comedy crash.
Well, keep it down
'cause I'm trying to...
Imagine the dance I'm gonna have
to do to get our security deposit back.
Oh, my God! Brian, look!
It's Aspen. We made it.
Well, looks like you're gonna be
reunited with Rupert after all.
And just in time, too.
I can't keep my teeth from chattering.
Isn't that fun?
I got these at Jack's Joke Shop
in South Attleboro, Massachusetts.
Remember, if it ain't funny,
it ain't worth Jack.
Bitch.
Aw, you should've seen what
our amazing, freakin' daughter
did to that guy, Lois.
She kicked his ass.
- It was like what life did to Dana Plato.
- Meg, how could you do that?!
You should call that man and apologize.
Hey, hey, hey.
Don't you talk to her like that.
Meg's as cool as the
other side of the pillow.
- Billy Dee Williams.
- Hello, Peter.
Welcome to the cool side of the pillow.
You've had a hard day.
Rest that weary head of yours
and drift on off to dreamland.
Works every time.
Well, this is the place.
Looks pretty fancy.
- Can I help you?
- Uh, yes, my name's Brian, um...
Look, to make a long story short,
I accidentally sold you a teddy bear
back in Rhode Island, and...
I kind of need it back.
- Rupert! It's, it's Rupert!
- Stanford, who is it?
It's nothing, dear, I'll handle it.
I'm sorry, but that bear belongs
to Timmy. Now, please leave.
Wait, wait. How about a ski off?
- What...?
- You heard me.
First one down the mountain wins.
If I win, I get Rupert.
Interesting. What do I get if I win?
- My dog.
- Hmm. What can he do?
If you put peanut butter anywhere
on your body, he'll lick it off.
Anywhere.
Well, I did go to Choate.
All right, it's a deal.
She's the kind of girl
who's not too shy.
And I can tell I'm her kind of guy.
She danced close to me
like I hoped she would.
She danced for me
Somethin' tells me
I'm into somethin' good...
You know, Dad, it's been really great
hanging out with you.
I know there's probably a million
things you'd rather be doing.
Are you kidding, Meg?
I've had more fun with you than I did
going to see Lost in Translation
with Cleveland and Quagmire.
- What do you think he whisper to her?
- I'll bet it was just right.
Look, I know sometimes
I give you a hard time.
You know, calling you names,
reading your diary,
farting in your cereal
when you go to get milk
and then laughing: "Ha-ha ha!
She doesn't know she's eating my fart. "
But, you know, Meg,
I'm starting to realize
- I got a really wonderful daughter.
- Thanks, Dad.
Peter, good news. Your suspension is up.
You can have your license back.
You... you mean it? I'm free?
No more getting driven around?
Aw, sweet!
So, I guess this means
you don't need me anymore.
You'll probably go back to
treating me like crap, huh?
Well, maybe just to keep up
appearances in front of the family.
You know, peer pressure and all that.
But from now on, Meg,
you and me are secret best friends.
Who wants a glass of fresh lemonade?
Not me!
What I want is a fresh glass
of better daughter!
Stewie, do you really think
you can beat this guy?
Trust me, Brian, I've got
a few tricks up my sleeve.
Oh, no, if only I had rockets in my skis.
Oh, wait, I totally have rockets
in my skis.
And now I just sit back,
relax and watch my progress.
- Tea, sir?
- Oh, thank you, Crone.
You're so pleasant.
Would you like to check
on the race, sir?
Yes, why not.
Well, that's it, I suppose.
Listen, I'm, I'm really sorry, Stewie.
- I know how much Rupert meant to you.
- I don't know, Brian,
maybe this is a sign that you were right.
Maybe I am getting too old for Rupert.
I guess I've just got to let him go.
That's very grown up of you, Stewie.
Hey, dog, let's go.
My dad won you fair and square.
You're not really gonna
live with them, are you?
No.
You're not really over Rupert are you?
- No.
- That's what I thought.
Oh, Crone.
- How are we gonna get out of here?
- You still got the starting gun?
- Yeah.
- Give it to me.
Get out of the fucking car! Get out
of the fucking car right now, man!
- Oh, Jesus!
- Get out of the fucking car.
Do it! I don't give a fuck!
I'll fucking kill you!
Get out of this fucking car!
- Did we just carjack someone?
- We sure did, Brian.
We sure did.