WWW.MY-SUBS.COM
♪ It seems today that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those good
old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man
who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a... Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
Sync and corrections by btsix
www.MY-SUBS.com
Previously on Family Guy...
Certain of his own wit and intellect,
Brian opened up a Twitter account.
If you ask me, Twitter is the
perfect place for that guy,
because he's a twit.
But an off-color tweet
suddenly made Brian
a pariah to all of Quahog,
forcing the family to
make the difficult choice
of sending him to a crappy apartment
on the other side of town.
Brian, the family has spoken.
You know, you're the only man in America
who looks good in sandals
and cargo shorts.
Good luck, everyone. I'll miss you.
Uhp, something's comin'!
Brian. Brian!
I said you're a week late on your rent.
Well, I can get you the
money. Hang-hang on.
Let me just make a call.
Hello. You've reached...
- The Griffins!
- Chris!
See that? I told you we
should've rehearsed this.
- Lois, can we do it over?
- No, that's eight times.
- Just leave a message.
- I'm sorry.
Hey, guys.
It's me again. Brian.
We haven't talked since I moved out,
so I figured, you know, 10:00,
you're probably on the
couch watching Pawn Stars.
So, uh, pick up.
Pick up?
Uh, da, da, da, da, da, da.
Maybe you went out.
Da, da, da, da, da, da.
Da, da, da...
Ooh-wa, ooh...
Okay. Well, again, it's Brian.
Um, guys, really, really, call me back.
It's Brian. Bye.
So, what do you think?
Is your family gonna give
you money for the rent?
Yeah, I'm thinking no.
Well, you got to do something, Brian.
- You're a week behind.
- Okay, okay.
Look, I'll get a job, okay?
There's got to be something I can do.
It's not like I'm Ringo.
Well, lads, what do you think
of the new album cover?
Great, but it won't look good
when it's shrunk down for a CD.
CD? What's a CD?
A digital compact disc.
Ringo, are you from the future?
Yeah. And I outlive two of you.
- Which two?
- Yeah, come on, Ringo. Tell us.
Okay, but you all have to agree
to do my song about the octopus.
Hey, before you tell us,
I'm gonna go and smoke
a thousand cigarettes.
And I'm gonna move to New York City
and walk in and out of my building.
Okay, everybody, time to go to
Grandma and Grandpa's house.
- They're dead.
- Not your grandparents, Peter.
I'm talking about my parents.
I hate going there.
I'm not allowed to touch
anything in their house.
And, besides, today's Dolph
Lundgren's birthday,
and me and the guys always celebrate it
by watching Rocky IV.
Fine, we're probably
better off without you.
You always find a way to
embarrass us at my parents'.
Please pass the All Fruit.
Pass the Polaner All Fruit.
Would you please pass the jelly?
Hi. We're concerned that many
of you Family Guy fans under 40
didn't get that reference,
so I'm gonna take you through
the actual commercial.
Okay, typical '80s stuffy brunch.
Please pass the All Fruit.
Clearly the matriarch.
She's got the most pearls.
Pass the Polaner All Fruit.
Weird sexual tension there.
Okay, okay, watch. Here's
where it all goes to hell.
Would you please pass the jelly?
See? He called it jelly.
See... All right, now,
what I don't get is,
if they know this guy,
why are they surprised
by the way he talks? Right?
And if they don't know him,
why is he at the table?
Okay, now you have the information
that would've made that funny
had you had it going in.
All right, you ready to watch Rocky IV?
- Let's do it!
- Yeah!
Happy Dolph Lundgren Day!
What the... what the hell?
Try blowing on it.
Crap! It doesn't work!
Well, we got to watch the
movie. It's our tradition.
We could just stream
it on your Apple TV.
Is that what that is? I
thought it was a coaster.
I've been putting cold, wet
things on it for a month.
Turn it on. I'm sure we can
find Rocky IV on there.
I don't know how to turn it on.
It doesn't have any buttons.
Well, maybe it's voice-activated.
Rocky IV! Rocky IV!
Let's just go to the damn store.
Hold on, hold on, let me try
screaming at the PlayStation.
Hey, you guys, why the long faces?
Eh, we were trying to watch Rocky IV
and our DVD didn't work.
And that's just Scottie Pippen.
When I was a baby,
they pulled me out of my moms real slow.
We got a bin of old movies.
Rocky IV might be in there.
Let's see.
Talladega Nights, everywhere.
Ladybugs, classic Rodney.
A Million Ways to Die in
the West, no, thank you.
Here it is! Rocky IV!
Aw, nuts, this one's
written in terrorism.
That's, uh, Cyrillic.
It's a Russian bootleg.
All right, we'll take it.
It's better than nothing.
Hey!
Welcome aboard, Brian. This
is your coworker, Martha.
Pleased to meet you, Brian.
Pleasure's all mine. So, any advice?
Well, there's a script you
can go off of, if you want.
Ah, script. Now you're
talking my language.
Writer.
So, watch out, or you might
end up in one of my scripts.
"Martha, gorgeous, headstrong,
legs as long as spaghetti
noodles, enters."
Why don't you just take your first call?
Suicide hotline.
Hey, I'm a pathetic dog
whose family kicked him out,
and I want to kill myself.
- Stewie?
- Hey, Brian!
How's the new job going?
All right, here comes the fight.
Get ready to eat it, Drago!
And Balboa is down!
Drago wins!
- What the hell?
- Son of a bitch!
Those Ruski bastards changed
the movie so Drago wins!
Yeah! Rocky gets up!
Not only does he not get up,
he's holding a sign that says,
"Workers of the world, unite!"
Well, that-that seems
like a logical idea,
but this aggression will not stand!
I'm writing Vladimir
Putin an angry e-mail.
"Dear Vladimir..."
Ho-ho! That's telling him.
"I hope this e-mail finds you well."
Oh, man, I wish I could see his face.
"I'll get right to the point.
My friends and I were aghast
when we saw what you did
to the end of Rocky IV.
Everyone knows that any American
can beat up any Russian
on any day of the week.
Other than that, all
is well on this end.
Chris continues to hit the
books as best he can,
and his grades have
shown some improvement.
Stewie is growing like a weed.
And Meg has become a woman
in front of our very eyes."
And... send.
I think we lost a little
steam there at the end.
We now return to Captain
America: Civil Union.
All right, Captain America,
we have to get ready
for the big fight with the other heroes.
- Who do we have on our side?
- Well, Hawkeye, we've got you,
Scarlet Witch, the Falcon,
and, of course, Randy.
- Who's Randy?
- You know Randy.
Lives in my guesthouse.
We've been friends since college.
He's... my pal.
He's the guy I went to Paris with.
You are such a coward!
Randy!
Vladimir Putin?!
Da. Where is bathroom?
I George Brett myself on plane.
Gross!
You can Google that
during the commercial.
Oh, my God. President Putin?
What-what are you doing here?
Husband write me impertinent e-mail.
Says any American can
beat up any Russian.
I am here to prove him wrong.
You're gonna beat up my husband?
Unless he American chicken.
Did you just call me chicken?
Yes. Chicken.
Fi-cray! Fi-cray! Fi-cray!
Sound different in Russia.
Nobody calls me... chicken.
Outside, now.
Hi, we're from Publishers
Clearing House.
I have a million-dollar check
for someone named Chicken.
A conflict!
You're going down!
- Kick his ass, Peter!
- Yeah, kick his ass!
Punch his ass, Peter!
Oh, pretty quick, huh?
Well, how about this?
Here comes the haymaker!
You had enough?
He gone.
Peter!
Oh, looks like Putin's phone is buzzing.
Brian?
Oh, hey, Marth... a.
- What are you doing here?
- I'm always here.
Suicide is not a nine-to-five problem.
Yeah, so I was thinking,
maybe we could Netflix and grill.
I think it's "Netflix and chill."
Oh. Good, 'cause I don't have a grill.
Hey, do you have Netflix?
The credit card numbers
I've been guessing
keep getting rejected.
Good night, Brian.
Well, nothing says I
can't date her up here.
Let's see what kind of Facebook
account we got for this Martha.
Uhp, private account.
But... sister.
Similar age. Few parties
they went to together.
Ooh, "Grandpa's Funeral."
Baby look good in black.
That's her mom?
Damn. I can work with this.
You know, this is exactly what
Dr. Fishbein was talking about.
I never go for it.
♪ Martha ♪
♪ You're playing hide and seek ♪
♪ With love ♪
♪ Martha ♪
♪ This is what Dr. Fishbein ♪
♪ Was talking about ♪
♪ Martha ♪
♪ With a little bit of love ♪
♪ And a whole lot of sass... ♪
You know what, Brian, I will...
Oh, my God!
Gross! You scumbag!
♪ Dr. Fishbein predicted it'd
be three years of treatment ♪
♪ And Martha's only six months in... ♪
Come on, Marth... a.
♪ Martha ♪
♪ It's gonna work out. ♪
I'll tell you something,
if he were here right now,
I'd kick his ass.
Just like hundreds of dead journalists,
I'm not afraid of Vladimir Putin.
Hello? Is it me you're looking for?
Yes!
Peter, you not coward I thought.
You put up impressive fight.
Thanks, Vladimir.
You know, as someone who
doesn't read the paper
or listen to the news,
you're not such a bad guy.
Well, thank you.
To show there are no hard feelings,
anyone want to go to strip club
and look at some cat emojis with me?
- Hell yeah.
- I'm up for the strip club.
Great. Who's driving?
You know, you're gonna think I'm
crazy, but it's such a nice day,
I was kind of thinking
of taking my shirt off
and riding a horse there.
Get out.
That's totally my thing!
Ah, the sun feels good
on my drunk chest.
You know what, you're a good guy, Peter.
Friend?
How do you say "friend" in Russian?
There is no Russian word for it.
Well, you're my friend now.
Funny how this worked out.
Who would have thought, huh?
I guess things not
always what they seem.
Yeah. I mean, except for
Ronan Farrow, who is clearly
Woody Allen's son and
absolutely not Frank Sinatra's.
I.. You know, I-I'm glad
you could make it home
for the family dinner, Ronan.
You got it, four eyes.
Wouldn't miss a dinner
with my cuckoo dad for the world.
Hey, Anna May Wong, no
tickie, no shirtie.
I'm just kidding around,
rice bowl. Geez, lighten up.
This room is tighter than
Ava Gardner's caboose.
Us, right?
It's like lookin' in a mirror.
Well, Peter, thank you
for showing me Quahog.
Ah, it was fun.
I'm gonna miss you, Vladimir.
So come with me back to Russia.
I need friend.
Ah, I'm flattered, but my home is here.
And besides, I can't go to Russia.
I'm scared of Brigitte Nielsen.
She is here with you in your country.
She-she's here now? Is she...
O... All ri... Okay, okay, let's go.
Let's go, let's go, let's
go, wheels up, let's go!
Oh, my God, she can smell
the tiny bottles of booze.
We got to go! We got to go now!
Dear Lord, please send me a
six-foot-seven blonde woman
who likes to drink until she blacks out.
I think we got our prayers crossed.
Welcome to Russia, Peter.
Man, Russia has the hottest and
ugliest women in the world.
All tens and ones.
Wow! Whoa.
- Wow! Whoa.
- Whoa.
Aw, I'm a "whoa."
I know what'll cheer you up.
We listen to funny morning zoo on radio.
You're listening to backwards-K-FMB.
I am The Penis, here with Buttocks.
Hello, Buttocks.
Ha. Humor.
Now time for government-approved
prank phone call.
What?
Is your refrigerator running?
Yes.
You are very fortunate.
I've tried everything, Lou.
I told her I was sorry.
I even sent flowers.
She's gonna report me,
and I'm gonna get fired.
Wh-What can I do?
Do what I do when people
don't pay their rent:
plant drugs and call the cops.
I don't know, I-I may be broke,
but that seems like a crappy
thing to do to somebody.
Well, then you're evicted.
Okay, fine.
But where am I gonna get drugs?
Walk me to my car. My
trunk is full of coke.
Brian Griffin?
Your life's about to change.
We're not having a lot of luck today.
So, what do you do for fun around here?
- You got DirecTV?
- We have Time Warner.
- You got HBO?
- We have Starz.
- You got ESPN?
- We have Fox Sports 1.
- Does that come in HD?
- 420P.
You got...
Everything you say, I say
something little bit worse.
- You got Simpsons?
- We have Family Guy.
Ah, I did it to myself.
Well, just shoot her first.
It's not called "suicide-murder,"
it's called "murder-suicide."
Brian, can I talk to you for a second?
- Yeah, sure.
- I wanted to tell you,
I thought a lot about what
happened, and I guess...
In your own weird way...
you were complimenting me.
Um, w... w-what?
I just wanted to let you know
I'm not going to tell anyone
about what happened, and...
maybe we could get that drink tomorrow.
Tell 'em you have no idea
how your hair strands
got in that baggie. Hello, Officer!
- Is this your desk, ma'am?
- Yeah. Why, Officer?
Found it.
- What is that?
- Like you don't know.
Cocaine. Glorious cocaine.
Best thing ever.
You're gonna have to come with us.
And, Jeff, you might want
to call your sponsor.
You did this, didn't you?
I knew you were a little
twerp as soon as I met you.
He did this! He planted that!
Martha, I'm so sorr...
You bastard!
Aah! My leg is broken!
Only thing I can possibly
do is lick it repeatedly.
There we go. That's fixing it.
Please pass the aspic.
I'll have the aspic.
I, too, will have the aspic.
Could you please pass the beef jelly?
Huh? See?
Now aren't you glad we did
all that work earlier?
Peter, come.
Over here is where we rig
every American election.
Eh.
Also, American football.
What?! No!
Is true. Meet my best
friend, Roger Goodell.
NFL Commissioner Roger Goodell?
You're a Russian spy?
I don't know, Peter.
Why don't you tell me?
Today we decide which
New England Patriot
to suspend, eh?
Da. Tom Brady or Tom Brady?
You leave that gorgeous
piece of ass alone.
I was right about you
from the start, Putin.
You can't just do whatever
you want in the world
and get away with it.
It's time someone stood up to you.
And survived.
Ladies and gentlemens,
tonight we are here to see the fight
to determine East/West superiority.
Fighting for Russia,
President Vladimir Putin!
Fighting for America,
Kevin James!
Everybody here thinks I'm Kevin James.
Kevin James! Kevin James!
- Kevin James!
- I can't believe it,
but it sounds like the audience
is starting to cheer for the American!
Kevin James! Kevin James!
Enough!
Lois? What are you doing here?
I'm not really here, Peter.
You've been hit several
times in the head
and sustained severe brain trauma.
She's right. This has gone too far.
There are other ways to
settle our differences.
Say you.
Yes. Say me.
♪ Say you, say me ♪
♪ Say it for always ♪
♪ That's the way it should be ♪
♪ So you think you know the answers... ♪
Vlad and I finished our dance,
then spent the rest
of the night talking.
The next day, he poisoned me on
the limo ride to the airport
with radioactive tea.
♪ Believing who you are ♪
♪ You are a shining star... ♪
I lost half my body
weight, all my hair,
and I have lesions that'll never heal.
That's our president's best friend.
♪ Say you, say me. ♪
Sync and corrections by btsix
www.MY-SUBS.com