WWW.my-subs.co
It seems today that all you see
Is violence in movies and sex on TV
But where are those
good old-fashioned values
On which we used to rely?
Lucky there's a family guy
Lucky there's a man who
positively can do
All the things that make us
Laugh and cry
He's... a... Fam... ily... Guy!
- Synced and corrected by AlexandreMT -
- www.MY-SUBS.com -
- Hey, where's Quagmire?
- Actually, I haven't seen him all week.
Methinks he found a new lady friend.
Don't say "methinks" ever again, Joe.
- Hey, there he is.
- Hey, guys.
What-What's all this?
Oh, this little oogie-woogie
is my new friend, Albertine.
Who thinks she's French.
She loves to smoke
and feels it's not truly a meal
unless you serve bread.
Isn't that right, Albertine?
You got to serve bread?
I don't believe
she's ever said any of that.
So where have you been
lo these many days?
Joe!
Well, you know how there's
hardly any cat cafés in town?
Well, I decided to open a cat café.
- What's a cat café?
- It's like a coffee shop,
except one where lots of cats
live and roam.
Hmm, methinks the cat café
sounds like a great idea.
That's it, Joe!
I challenge you to a duel!
Pistols at midnight.
Peter, did you bring a flamethrower?
No.
I also didn't bring one of them
laser guns from Ghostbusters.
Joe, look! Look!
I got Mayor West!
Good. We'll keep him
till we get a new mayor.
Principal Shepherd, we were
so surprised to get your call.
Wh-What's going on?
Mrs. Griffin, Meg and Chris
were caught cheating.
- What?
- Yes.
They had the Lost Boys of the Sudan
standing in for them in gym class.
Nice block, Griffin.
Nice shot, other Griffin.
This is terrible.
Uh, what do you think about this, Peter?
Bad. Very bad.
Here it is, guys! What do you think?
I'm realizing I may have a cat allergy.
I think it's great, Glenn.
And people really seem to be
enjoying themselves.
Boy, if I could clean myself
with my tongue,
I'd never leave the house.
Right?
And it's like, if I had nine lives,
maybe I'd finally find a man.
You's joining me.
- Peter, we have to talk.
- What fireworks?
After what happened today
with Meg and Chris at school,
I sent an e-mail to my sister,
and five minutes later,
Google Ads suggested
a Christian family camp.
Yeah, the world's better
now that corporations read
our most private communications
and then sell back at us
the very things
they've eavesdropped about.
Even before this, I'd worried about
our church attendance dropping off.
Now with the kids showing
a complete lack of morals,
well, we may all need to go
to Christian family camp.
Lois, you know I love you like a
brother, but I'm not doing that.
I'd only get in an awkward,
campfire-crackle argument
with a counselor.
Jesus has love for everyone.
Uh, actually, what Jesus has
is the might of Western civilization.
Jesus has guns, germs and steel.
Sorry, the wood is very wet.
Uh, actually, the wood is very dry.
Wet wood hisses, dry wood crackles
during uncomfortable silence.
I like cutaways where I get to be smart.
What the... what the hell is that?
Hey! Shut up!
Don't look at me! I'm dominant!
Brian? What are you doing here?
What am I doing here? What is all this?
I happen to own this place.
It's a cat café.
Now get out of here.
You're making all my cats angry.
That's why they're hissing.
Actually, frightened cats hiss.
Angry cats moan.
You can't open this place here.
It's right next to my favorite bar.
Go to hell, Brian.
You don't own this block.
I'm not going anywhere.
Fine. But I am about to become
your worst nightmare.
No way. I've already had
my worst nightmare.
I've told you about
my worst nightmare, right?
- No, I-I don't think so.
- Oh, boy, get comfortable.
Well, first,
I'm driving through a forest,
but it's actually inside,
which is weird, right?
- Okay.
- And there's all these people
in the van who normally wouldn't
know each other in real life:
my second grade teacher, my mom,
Joe, but it wasn't quite Joe.
All the kids are
yelling at me in German,
and I understood them,
but I don't speak German.
Then SNL is starting,
and I'm clearly in the cast,
and I haven't been
to any of the rehearsals,
and all the cue cards are blank,
and that show is all cue cards.
And just as that's sinking in,
I realize I'm also the musical guest.
I mean, I can't pull that off.
Who do I think I am? Silverchair?
- And the weird thing is...
- Wait a minute.
Listening to other people's nightmares
is my worst nightmare!
Oh. Oh, thank God.
I got to shut down that cat place.
Okay, Peter, the kids and I
are off to church camp.
Meg, Chris, the vans are here.
Wait a minute.
- You got any booze in that bag, mister?
- No, sir.
Well, then, how you gonna
make any friends at camp?
Here you go.
Now chug all this next to
a lake, you little rascal.
Shut down the cat café!
It's a nuisance
and a threat to public health!
Oh, for God's sake.
City ordinance 321 states,
"Food or drink shall not
be prepared or consumed within
20 feet of fecal matter."
- Damn it, Brian.
- Also, Persian cats?
Let's call them what they are:
Iranian cats.
This entire operation
needs to be shut down.
And as long as
Brian's got your attention,
is it taking anyone else longer to wipe?
More wipes these days?
I'm taking shorter poops
but with longer wipes,
and there's always this one little line.
I swear to God, it's like
there's a crayon down there.
Wait, excuse me for a minute.
Son of a gun, it was a crayon.
Thanks for letting me
talk that out, everybody.
Wikipedia states that
"Toxoplasmosis is a parasitic
disease spread by exposure
to infected cat feces."
Damn it, Brian, get out of here.
You're scaring away my customers.
They also ring you up
on one of those tablets
they flip around at you and then glare
while you pick from
three inflated tip percentages.
You can also choose "no tip."
But that option is, by design,
much less prominent.
You're a jerk.
But fine, if it's a fight
you want, you got one.
I will squash you like a bug.
Well, that's enough of that show.
But, Dad, we want to see
what happens at Christian camp.
All right. But they're on thin ice.
Welcome to Sunrise Woods Bible Camp.
I'm the camp director Vera.
Nice to meet you. We're the Griffins.
Why are all these trees
bunched together?
Th-Those are woods, Chris.
I only like rooms.
What a lovely setting.
Yes, the fresh air really helps
clear your mind
of thoughts of Tom Selleck.
Oh. How frighteningly specific.
Ugh, Mom, this place sucks.
It's even worse than when Dad
sent us to 1940s comedy school.
Say, Corporal, what are you
writing in your diary?
It's private. Take a look.
Now, that's some good, clean fun.
Also in the 1940s,
six million Jews died.
That's it, we're done.
This show is not for the Bugsteins.
Good evening. Quite a battle brewing...
Clever news pun, doesn't really
work as I haven't yet mentioned
the subject of the story...
At Quahog's new cat café.
Asian reporter Tricia Takanawa
filed this report.
Tom, I'm standing here outside
of Quahog's new cat café.
Local resident Brian Griffin
has described the café
as a threat to public health.
That's right, Tricia.
And since I'm on local TV,
I'm gonna talk a little too loud,
and then occasionally
I'm gonna turn away
From the microphone
to point at things off-camera,
So my overall point is lost.
Powerful claims. Thank you, Brian.
Okay, Brian, I brought
everything we need:
water, sunscreen, Fruit Roll-Ups,
- batteries.
- Stewie,
you know you're not allowed
to have Fruit Roll-Ups.
Damn, I tried to bury it in there.
What are you even wearing?
Oh, this is what Princess Diana
wore to protest land mines.
It's sad she's not around
to watch her son go bald.
Brian, I'm glad you're here.
Based on the various public
health concerns you raised,
the city has decided
to shut this establishment down.
Really? You're closing the café?
That's right. Thanks to you,
I'm out of business.
I certainly hope you're happ...
Oh, nice top, Stewie.
Come on, lock it up.
Until the Board of Health
gives the okay, you're done.
Wow, I actually got the place shut down.
I'm glad I was here for this, Brian.
We've hardly done anything
together since we made
that fiber commercial and had
to use code words for pooping.
Wow, Brian, I've never felt so regular.
Yes, you seem exceptionally
active while maintaining
- proper body health.
- That's right.
Just two spoonfuls a day
to stay regular and active.
- More coffee, Stewie?
- Yes, please.
Oh, dear, that was a mistake.
You mean, you're about to be active?
Currently active.
Cut to the shot of them
stirring the product into water!
GurgleMax: Take a massive comfort.
Oh, God!
Oh, there's regular on the carpet!
Ah, there's so much regular!
How are those drawings of Jesus coming?
Okay, a little dark on the hair there.
Let's lighten it up. Lighten it up.
Eyes should be blue.
Remember, history says
that Jesus does not look like
a traditional man from the Middle East,
but rather someone
who sells raw milk online.
Okay, let's put those away for now.
I'd like to move on to having you all
sign your contracts with God.
Contracts with God?
Yep. It's a written commitment
to forgo all alcohol,
drugs and self-pleasure.
Yeah, I'm gonna have
my lawyer look at this.
I tell you, it's a good day, Stewie.
Now that that cat café is gone,
I can finally get back
to my favorite bar and do some writing.
Whoa, sorry. Can't let you in there.
What? I come in here all the time.
Well, apparently, due to some
recent public health concerns,
the city has said that no
animals of any kind are allowed
in any public establishment.
What?! You got to be kidding me!
Well, that's all right, Brian.
We can go to my writing spot.
Brian! Look at my jump!
Look at my jump! Look at my jump!
Whoa!
This place has the best
pizza and Pepsi, Brian.
Did you hear me?
The best pizza and Pepsi.
Oh, no, my pizza and Pepsi!
Oh, hey, Peter. Come on in.
Thanks for coming by.
Aw, no problem, buddy.
Here, I brought you something.
I figured anyone living alone
with 73 cats
needs to have a double-XL
Minnie Mouse sweatshirt.
Thank you so much.
This won't fit at all; it's perfect.
So, how's it going?
Well, not bad. Got plenty of company.
Well, that's good.
I haven't seen you at the Clam.
Well, I've been pretty busy.
So, can I get you something to drink?
Sure. What have you got?
Well, I've got water
with cat hair in it.
Eh, anything else?
I've got lemonade with cat hair in it.
Uh, kind of a summer drink.
Anything else?
Oh, sure. Cat hair ginger ale?
- Nope.
- Cat hair iced tea?
Uh, again, summer.
You want to just take a look
in the fridge, see what I got?
Sure.
Someone just had kittens in my mouth.
What's up? What are you doing?
Nothing. I'm just sitting here,
trying to figure out
why we have stupid purple couches.
Have you ever known anyone in your life
to own a purple couch?
I would assume Steve Harvey.
That actually sounds right,
but-but what is this?
A picture of a mountain?!
When have we ever been to a mountain?!
- What mountain even is it?
- That's Mount Quahog.
Yeah... I don't know, feels made up.
Brian, is this all because
you haven't been able
- to get a drink?
- I haven't been able to go anywhere.
No dogs allowed in public places.
Yes, I was thinking about that.
What if there was a way
for you to go out?
"Emotional support animal"?
Wear this, every place
will have to let you in.
- So long as I'm with you.
- Where'd you even get that thing?
The letters are iron-on.
The vest is from when I worked
at Office Depot.
One pen? You're buying one pen?
Yep.
You don't work in an office
you can steal this from?
I work from home.
Ugh.
Office Depot. We're coming, Blockbuster.
Mom, we don't really have to get
baptized, do we?
No, Meg, just hang
towards the back of the line.
- Good plan.
- Chris, stop relieving yourself.
You've got those pee eyes.
Brother Chris.
Do it again.
- Sister Lois?
- Oh, no, thanks.
Y-You'd have no way of knowing this,
but I'm actually having
a very good hair day.
When my hair gets wet,
I tend to look like
a frazzled Sandra Bullock
from one of her comedies.
My ex-husband had Nazi
paraphernalia and he left me.
So I said, "That shirt
looks really good on you,"
and he says, "Thanks, my
boyfriend got it for me."
It's like, whoa, all I said
was I like the shirt,
and he has to drop "boyfriend"
like a nuclear bomb?
- I mean, that's on him, right?
- Yeah. I don't know.
Ugh, you're supposed to be giving me
emotional support right now.
Let's just get to the bar.
No, no, Brian, say something
nice about me right now.
Come on, Stewie,
that's not what this is.
It is now. Say something nice about me
or I'll disappear like
a serial killer in a '90s movie.
Stewie, wait. I need you to get in.
I'm gonna do it.
Okay, who's ready for some breakf...?
Oh, crap, another one died.
Hey, hey, stop eating her!
Get away! Okay, new house rule.
Everyone look at me.
Don't eat the dead cats.
Oh. Hey, Quagmire.
We came to see how it's going.
Uh, "how's it going"?
I got a dead cat on a pitchfork!
I don't even know which can
to put it in!
Trash?! Yard trimmings?! Recycling?!
I just put whatever in whatever.
Hey, guys! Check it out!
Cat legs! Cats, arise.
Guys! It's working!
I'm not dead!
Okay, we're getting out
of this place tonight.
Everyone clear on the plan?
Yep. Meg and I switch faces
- like in the movie Face/Off?
- No.
Oh. Then we have an issue.
I told you we should ask Mom first.
Why would you think that?
Ugh... Just, you two follow my lead.
You know, Vera, I've been
so moved by my time here
at camp, I wonder if I could
perhaps say grace tonight?
Oh, that'd be lovely, Lois.
Well, I'd like to begin
with a moment of silence.
A fully counted-out,
Mississippi, 60-second
moment of silence.
And the first one
to open their eyes is gay.
Psst. Up here.
My eyes are open, too.
There was something
in the air that night
The stars were bright, Fernando
They were shinin' there for you and me
For liberty, Fernando
Though we never thought
that we could lose
There's no regret.
Ugh. Good riddance,
Christian family camp.
Totally. I will say, though,
it seemed like Chris
enjoyed himself there.
Well, Meg, you know Chris is
a little bit dumb,
and I know you're
not particularly popular
or beautiful, but you do have
a head on your shoulders.
So religion isn't gonna be
for people like you and me.
It's basically for:
stupid people like Chris.
So to summarize,
religion for you and me?
No good. But for idiots like Chris?
- Perfect.
- What are you guys talking about?
- How handsome you are.
- Really?
Swear to God.
You're a monster.
Stupid law. Banning dogs.
Kibbles and bits and bits and bits.
You! You son of a bitch!
This is all your fault!
- What the...?
- Ha-ha!
You thirsty, boy?
Yeah, you're a thirsty boy.
Wait a minute, we're fighting!
Aah!
And now, time to make my getaway.
Brian, oh, my God! Are you all right?
Here, let me mend you,
like in a 1990s action movie.
Aw, thanks. That is better.
Look at us. What are we doing?
I don't even know anymore.
You know what?
I'm sorry I destroyed
your dream, Quagmire.
I know you loved that café.
Wow. Um... thanks, Brian.
Why did you open that place, anyway?
Well... honestly, I just thought
that maybe I could put something
good in the world for a change.
What do you mean?
I mean that... uh...
I've always been about sex
and seducing women,
but you know what?
Someday I'm gonna be dead.
And, I-I mean, is that my legacy?
I just thought if I created something
that makes people happy,
maybe people would remember me for that.
You probably think that's stupid.
Quagmire... I'm here for you.
For emotional support.
Thanks, Brian. What do you say?
You want to go for a walk?
I always want to go for a walk.
Hey, does anyone know what's
going on with my brown crayon?
Because it disappeared
from the box for a while,
and now it's back.
It's a little... I don't know,
oily and misshapen?
I'm not a crayon scientist,
but it looks like it's seen some heat.
The city repealed a law
prohibiting animals
from public businesses today.
And finally, tonight...
We built this city!
There. Now it's in your head, too.
Well, I'm glad you get to go out
in public again, Brian.
I'm glad you, Chris, and Meg are
back from that Christian camp.
Hey, where is Meg, anyway?
Oh, she was so mad I dragged her
to Christian camp,
she ran away to live
with a Japanese family.
Damare, Meg!
Family Guy over! On-uh Foxuuu!